Previously on Gotham...
Told you, easy as pie.
- What?
- Sorry, Frankie.
Arnold Flass,
you're under arrest for
the murder of Leon Winkler.
You really think these guys
are gonna let you arrest me?
Shut up, Flass.
Penguin, come here.
You're a smart monkey.
But I'm the zookeeper.
I didn't think
it was going to be you,
my dear. You can come out now.
Right as usual, my friend.
- We got to go!
- I swear, Butch,
I'm gonna come back and kill Penguin.
Oh, no, please.
Don't, don't, please, please!
Ah.
You're sure, now?
Fish Mooney is done.
She tried to bring down Falcone.
She failed.
Last time I saw her, Victor
Zsasz had her cornered.
We can assume she's either
dead or extremely unwell.
Well, then. Salud.
Mmm. You know, this creates
some intriguing opportunities.
Falcone will struggle to
hold on to her territories.
If we move quickly...
My thinking exactly.
In fact,
I took the liberty of
claiming her nightclub.
In your name, of course.
You did, huh?
Good thinking.
A bird in the hand is
nine-tenths of the law, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Phone for you, boss.
Speak.
Hello, Sal.
Hey.
You sound surprised.
Let me guess... Your little friend Penguin
told you I was dead.
As good as.
Mm. I'm just on a vacation for a while.
- Huh.
- I'm not going to lie,
I thought I was gonna end up on top.
Instead, I got played.
Turns out, Penguin has been
Falcone's man the whole time.
They played us both for suckers.
Is that right?
Ah, indeed.
He told me himself, right
before I was about to gut him.
You understand why I might be skeptical,
considering it's you telling me this.
Oh, wake up, dummy.
You mean to tell me this whole time
you haven't suspected anything?
That he hasn't made one slip
that he's had to explain away?
Or maybe even you wanted
to believe his lies.
But it still gnaws at you, doesn't it?
The doubt.
It's right there. A smudge.
Don't let it happen again.
Maybe a couple of times.
It's time to get your
house in order, Salvatore.
And remember who put you wise.
Not bad news, I hope.
Nah. I got to go upstate.
See a guy about a thing.
Come with me.
We can talk about opportunities.
Sure.
- Just, uh, let me run home and...
- Bup, bup.
We got to go now. Right now.
Super.
I love a road trip. Yay.
Yay.
Harvey?
Captain.
What have we got?
Sometime last night, Mr. Lucky there
got tied to that chair, noose
was dropped over his neck
and he's heaved over the side.
Some suits coming up for a
smoke this morning found him.
How'd he get back up to the roof?
See that pulley there?
My guess: it was the killer.
Guy went to a lot of
trouble to get him back up.
Why not just leave him hanging?
Morning, Captain.
- Morning, Ed.
- The more you cut me
the bigger I grow. What am I?
We're on a rooftop, Nygma.
Don't tempt me.
A hole. I'm a hole.
Okay.
Relevance?
There's a hole, a surgical incision
in our victim's abdomen.
Certainly postmortem.
My guess: killer was looking for something.
I'll have to examine the body
more fully back at the lab.
You mean the medical examiner will.
Well, but...
You handle forensics, Ed.
The bodies belong to Dr. Guerra.
And he's made formal complaints.
I can't cover for you anymore.
I read you, ma'am.
Loud and clear.
So where's Gordon?
Personal stuff. He'll be in soon.
Hey, don't stand so near the edge.
You worried about me, Captain?
You know I don't start drinking till noon.
I got to spell it out for you?
Detective Flass had a lot of friends,
and your partner arrested him for murder.
Accidents happen.
You put the cuffs on him.
So we should all be careful.
To hell with them.
Barbara?
Hi.
Let go of me.
How long you been here?
Just last night.
And a couple times before.
I knew your girlfriend was gone,
and I heard you got sent
to guard that loony bin,
so I figured better here
than sleeping on the street.
- Have you seen Barbara?
- No.
Oh, so things are over
between you two, huh?
Sure you should be here then?
Maybe you're the one breaking in.
Came by to drop off
keys. Go get your stuff.
- Why? Where are you taking me?
- Well, you're not staying here,
and you're not gonna stay on the street.
I'll find you someplace safe.
Hmm. Safe.
Safe like Wayne Manor?
That was your last great idea.
So someplace else.
You're still my only
witness to the Wayne murders.
Hmm.
You haven't talked to
Bruce since he got back?
- No. Why?
- Because I told him already.
I didn't see anything. I lied.
Sucks about your girlfriend.
She's got some really nice stuff.
Hey, wait!
Stop!
Detective James Gordon
to see you, Master Bruce.
Detective.
Bruce, how are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
I would've come by earlier,
but things were a little crazy.
You were gone for a while.
Switzerland.
Probably wise.
I saw Selina Kyle.
She told me she lied.
She saw nothing.
Yes.
That's what she told me.
She made up the story to get out of juvie.
She could be saying this
now because she's scared.
It would be understandable
after what happened.
No.
She doesn't scare easily.
I believe her.
She didn't see the killer.
Look, this is unfortunate,
but it doesn't mean
we're back to square one.
Someone sent assassins after her.
Only a guilty person would do that.
Yes, and led her bloody
assassins to the manor.
Thank you very much.
Anyway, you need no longer
concern yourself with the case.
Bruce, this isn't the time to give up.
I'm not giving up.
I don't understand.
Months ago, you promised you'd find
who killed my parents,
and in all that time,
you've managed to find one witness,
who turned out to be a liar.
An investigation like this takes time.
I understand, but I don't
want you to feel bound
by an oath you can't fulfill.
I'm releasing you from your promise.
I'll pursue the matter on my own.
Bruce.
Yeah, no, I really wouldn't
bother, actually, mate.
Once Master Bruce makes up his mind,
there's no arguing with him.
He can't pursue this case on his own.
It's too dangerous.
Then I'll have to look after him.
Can I show you the door?
Hey, sleepy head.
We're here.
You smell that air?
That's country air.
Let's get some chow.
Chow.
Excellent.
So where's the guy?
Which guy?
The guy with the thing.
Oh, he'll be along.
You don't like the coffee?
I like the coffee.
How about the oatmeal?
Also delicious.
It's good to get out of the city, huh?
Away from the fumes, the noise.
I can finally hear myself think.
It's all so...
simple and clean and honest out here.
Fresh air, oatmeal,
good friends.
How true. In Gotham,
we never have any time to connect,
to reflect.
- You feel that?
- Absolutely.
Mm.
This guy with the thing...
What is the thing?
Stop worrying about that guy.
You know what I was thinking about?
This is crazy.
Indian Hill.
You know, that dump in Arkham
that I traded to Falcone
for your neck.
How could I forget?
I'm eternally grateful.
You suggested it, whispered it in my ear.
It's worthless land.
But was it so worthless?
I mean, Falcone snapped it up pretty quick.
It was a token.
He simply needed to save
face. After Nikolai died...
Ah, see, you wouldn't believe it.
That's the other thing
I was thinking about.
The fight with Nikolai
when Frankie was killed.
What was he stabbed, like, ten times?
I don't recall the exact number.
Only, it was a gunfight.
How'd Frankie get killed with a knife?
That always kind of bugged me.
Honestly,
I'm not much use when things get physical.
I'm sorry I couldn't save him.
I was just reminiscing.
Don't beat yourself up about it.
We all got our talents, right?
Yes, we do.
Me...
I'm deceptively quick for a big guy.
Yes, you are.
I'm gonna go get some air.
Wait for the guy with the thing, hmm?
The guy. Right.
How about getting
it right the first time
so we don't have to keep doing this?
Detective Bullock?
It's my name. Don't wear it out.
I'm Scottie Mullens.
You called me about Adam Jodowsky.
Oh... Oh, Miss Mullens, yes.
Thank you for stopping by.
- Uh, Miss? Mrs.?
- Miss.
Good. Good. Please.
So...
how did you know Mr. Jodowsky?
I was his sponsor, sort of.
We're... we're in a support group together.
He's dead, isn't he?
Why would you say that?
This is a homicide division.
You're a homicide detective.
We found his body this morning.
Your number was in his pocket.
I'd just given it to him.
I recently started being his sponsor.
Mm-hmm.
So, uh, what kind of group is this?
Uh, for booze, pills?
It's for people suffering from phobias.
You're joking. Fear can be debilitating.
It helps to talk to someone about it.
Don't be an ass.
- Excuse me?
- You were about to make fun.
Don't be an ass.
You're right. I'm sorry. I was.
No fun-making. Please.
Um...
what was Mr. Jodowsky's phobia?
Heights.
Hmm. So if he was found dangling
from the top of a tall building...
Oh, my God. Is that how he... ?
I'm gonna need the names of all
the people in the support group.
It's completely anonymous.
Adam was the only one I knew personally.
You don't think someone
from the group did this?
Could be. Killer certainly
seemed to know of his phobia.
Are you Irish?
Y-You seem like you could be Irish.
- What's it to you?
- I'm just curious.
- When's the next meeting?
- Tonight, 6:00.
And these things...
They usually run, what, an hour?
- Mm-hmm.
- So,
you could maybe go to dinner afterwards.
Hypothetically.
Okay, well, I'm gonna
keep working the case,
and I'm gonna call you if I feel
the need to go to this meeting.
We're gonna find who did this.
I promise, Miss Mullens.
Okay.
So I went through the
materials from the scene.
Ropes and pulleys can be bought anywhere.
For what it's worth,
I, uh, traced the chair
the victim was tied to.
Yeah. I'm listening.
Banker's chair, wooden, made
by some company in the Narrows
that's been closed down for years.
Great. Let's go.
You sure? That's a pretty thin lead, Harv.
Since when have you been
scared of a little work, huh?
What was he after?
Well, now.
There! See? I told you!
Oh.
Oh, dear.
Get your hand out of that corpse.
Now.
I was just passing by, and I, um,
uh... I was... I was just curious.
What was I thinking?
I... Sorry. Won't happen again. Promise.
Do something about this or
I'm going over your head.
I'm the medical examiner!
Not this gibbering loon!
I'm sorry, Ed.
Till further notice, you're suspended.
Finally.
But I found something.
So, word around the house is that
you and Doc Caliente have a thing.
Thompkins?
Yeah, kind of. I guess.
So you and Barbara are finally finito?
Yeah.
Dropped the keys off
at her apartment today.
Get any of that righteous breakup sex?
She wasn't there.
You notice I don't ask
you about your love life?
My love life is an open book
and a short and nasty one.
But I'm working on the vic's friend
in the phobia support group,
and unless she's the killer,
- I think I'm in there.
- You see why I don't ask?
Don't screw it up with the doctor.
I'll try not to.
Seriously, been willing
to forgive you on account
of you're not getting laid,
but you mean to tell me
this whole time you've
been making speeches,
raising hell, you've had a woman?
The thought of what you would do if alone
is truly terrifying.
GCPD!
Drop the knife!
What the hell?
Thin lead, huh?
Come in.
I hope everything is to
your satisfaction, ma'am.
It is. Thank you, Captain.
You can see
Gotham on the horizon if
you want to say good-bye.
No need. I'll be back soon enough.
Well...
if you need anything, just let me know.
I will.
This lucky fellow and the previous victim
are both part of the
same phobia support group.
Pigs. Go figure.
How is he?
He's at Gotham General,
scared half to death.
The medics had to sedate him.
The man you shot... Was
he in this group, too?
Nope. No I.D. as yet.
We're running his prints.
So is he our man or are we
still looking for someone else?
- Hard to say.
- He's our man.
These sort of wackos work alone.
I'm gonna run by the support group,
tell them it's been settled.
Hey, we don't know that yet.
You need to be more optimistic.
You do. You need to be more optimistic.
We have a perp.
The postmortem incision on
the first victim is weird.
The killer was after
something. I want to know what.
I'm gonna ask Nygma to take a look.
No. He's been suspended.
You got the report from the M.E.
The same M.E. who said my
last witness stabbed himself
to death in the back with an ice pick?
No. No, thanks. Nygma...
Is not the medical examiner.
I like him, too.
But there's nothing I can do,
not with the way things are.
What do you mean?
Look, I'm glad we took down Flass,
but there are people you go
after and people you don't.
So now everything we do is being watched.
You got the bad guy. Let it go.
I'm sorry you got dragged into it.
Don't be.
Felt good.
Did, didn't it?
Miss Kringle, I came to tell you that I...
Have you been crying?
No, no. I'm-I'm fine.
But I can see tears on your face.
Is it because your friend
Detective Flass was arrested?
What do you need, Mr. Nygma?
Yes.
I've been suspended and
won't be seeing you anymore.
So I wanted to return this pencil.
I took it from your office some time ago.
I kept meaning to return it.
Used to be longer.
You're an odd man, Mr. Nygma.
But I'm sorry that you've been suspended.
I wish something could be done.
Have a seat. We got to talk.
I feel that the time has
come in our relationship
when we should have trust with each other.
Real trust.
Total honesty between us.
No secrets.
I 100% agree.
So here's a secret to start off.
There is no guy with a thing. I lied.
I was beginning to wonder about him.
Now you.
- Me?
- We're being honest.
You have to tell me a secret in return.
Secrets from you, Don Maroni?
I have none.
Please.
Um...
Honestly... I don't really like oatmeal.
Good to know.
See, I like this game.
I'll tell you another secret.
Fish Mooney's alive.
I spoke to her.
Good secret, huh?
- What did Fish say?
- Oh, no.
You have to tell me a secret first.
That's how it works.
I don't much like coffee either.
Fair enough.
What did Fish say?
Said you and Falcone have been
working together all this time.
She said you've been playing me
for a chump since the first day I met you.
She would say that, wouldn't she?
The bitch.
You don't believe her, do you?
Well, she did put some incidents
in a different and
troubling light, I must say.
Uh-huh.
Well, that's too bad.
Your turn.
Tell me another secret.
A good one this time.
I took your gun.
I have it right here.
That's a good secret.
I took it because I figured
Mooney had called you somehow.
I knew you might believe her.
Doesn't mean she's telling the truth.
Is she?
Have you been playing
me for a chump, Penguin?
I think it's your turn to tell a secret.
You little dirtbag.
I treated you like a friend.
Like a monkey friend.
You're the zookeeper, remember?
Tell me a secret now.
Just one more then.
I'm tired of this game.
That gun is loaded with blanks.
Liar.
- You...
- Yeah.
Good secret, huh?
Hi.
Thank you for coming.
I was glad to get your call.
How are things at Arkham?
Little less interesting since you've left.
Oh.
How are things at the precinct?
Um, well, actually, that
was what I was hoping
you could help me with.
Um, we've got this case,
and I can't understand what
exactly our perp was doing.
And our medical examiner
is kind of a clown.
Uh, something wrong?
No, not at all.
Only, last time we met,
you were very passionate.
So when you called me, I thought...
Well, whatever.
I put on lipstick.
And you want forensic advice.
You're very confusing.
I don't mean to be. Uh...
Case is a pretext.
I wanted to see you.
Why didn't you just say that?
I should have. I haven't
done this in a while.
I'm a little rusty.
Sorry.
All right.
Well, good.
I don't like to put on lipstick by mistake.
So what's the issue?
Uh, no, no, no, forget the case.
- Don't worry.
- Please.
I'm interested.
Uh...
Excuse me.
Gordon.
When?
Uh, yeah, okay.
Take his statement. I'll be right there.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Yes.
I'll bring this back to you.
It's Harvey.
Harvey, second victim woke up.
Says he was abducted by two men.
There's someone still out there.
It's kind of you to come here
and tell us what happened.
No problem.
I just didn't want you worrying, so...
To be honest, you don't strike
me as the fraidy cat type.
Phobics are not fraidy cats.
I know. It's just, you seem
like a strong lady is all.
I am strong.
I just happen to be
terrified of swimming pools.
You're kidding.
Well, I can see how that might be a thing.
Nearly everyone has a thing.
I'm sure that you, if you dig deep enough,
would have issues that
you need to confront.
I'm a cop; the only thing
I'm scared of is decaf coffee.
Really? I've always found
that the best and bravest
people are the ones
that willingly acknowledge their fears.
Maybe you've just been hanging out
with too many timid and whiny people.
You are so bad.
I'm scared all the time.
And it's something I'd be
willing to share with the group
if you think it might be helpful.
Yes.
Yes, thank you.
I think it would.
First time?
Yeah. You?
No, I'm a regular.
So here's the deal. You go in the car,
the car's already in the crusher,
you get squeezed to death,
it takes a couple of minutes to die.
Whatever comes out, I send to Falcone.
Maybe he uses it as a coffee table.
Don Maroni, please listen to me.
Oh, this is the begging part?
Oh, good, 'cause this is my favorite part.
Go ahead and beg for your miserable life.
Just allow me to suggest some options here.
Mm-hmm.
Dead, I'm worthless.
If you factor in Falcone's
inevitable retaliation,
killing me will be a net loss for you.
This is not a business issue.
Me and Frankie Carbone go back 20 years.
You hurt me, Penguin.
You were right about Indian Hill.
There's more to it.
Falcone knows something.
I don't know what,
b-but I-I can find out...
Stop it. You're making me sad.
How did I ever fall for your crap?
N-No.
No. No. No.
Please. Please.
No. No.
Hey.
Say hi to Frankie for me.
I'm afraid every day.
I'm afraid I'm gonna die in an alley.
Bleeding out while some
scumbag goes through my pockets
and laughs at me.
And I try to speak, but nothing comes out.
And I just lie there,
staring at a small space of
sky between the buildings.
And then I die.
Alone.
I don't want to die alone in some gutter.
I want to die in a warm cozy bed
in the arms of a beautiful woman.
Thank you for sharing, Harvey.
Would anyone else like to share?
Tod, go ahead.
My name is Tod, and...
I've never spoken here before, but...
I have a horrible terror of failure.
I torment myself and those around me.
I'd crawl on broken glass to avoid failing.
About anything.
I inherited this illness from my father,
but I'm afraid I'm passing it on to my son.
We're here for you, Tod.
When I came home from work yesterday,
my precious son was crying,
and he said to me that he...
I'm sorry.
I can't speak.
- I'm so sorry.
- Tod?
Tod.
Tod?
Oh, you got to be kidding me. What?
Don Maroni, you have to listen to me.
Uh, see, no.
This is how this all
began, me listening to you.
I was telling the truth.
About Indian Hill.
And Arkham.
Whoever controls Arkham
will control Gotham! I can...
Would you shut up and take it like a man?
Yuh-huh.
Hello, is this Mr. Duffy?
Listen to me very carefully.
I'm the man in the car
in this ferocious machine of yours.
My name is Oswald Cobblepot.
And I work for Don Carmine
Falcone of Gotham City.
- Do you know who Don Falcone is?
- Yuh-huh.
Good.
I just called Don Falcone, and I told him
exactly where I am and what's happening.
So, Duffy, you better stop
this machine right now,
because if I die,
Don Falcone is gonna send a team up here
to skin you alive and
slaughter your family.
But Don Maroni said...
Don Falcone runs Gotham,
and you're about to
murder his right-hand man.
What the hell?
Hey!
Get back here!
Son of a bitch.
Is it just me, or have those two
been gone a while?
This has been real and
fun, but I got to go.
Oh, my God.
This isn't what it looks like.
Other members say our abductor's
been coming the last month.
Said his name was Tod, but group protocol
requires they remain anonymous.
So no real I.D.
And the guy you shot,
the one with the pigs?
Prints came back: career criminal.
Probably just the muscle.
The other guy was in charge.
He knew there was a cop
there at the meeting.
He still took her.
That's cold or crazy.
Either way, he's almost
sure to follow the same M.O.
He'll confront Miss Mullens
with her greatest fear.
- Which is drowning.
- Specifically in a pool.
There's hundreds of pools in Gotham.
We can't possibly get
- to every...
- That was her mother.
When she was seven, Scottie almost drowned
in Lemmars Park pool uptown.
It's a start, I guess.
That's where he took her, I can feel it.
- Boss?
- Uh, not now, Joe.
Wait.
Tell me that's not what it looks like.
You're brave.
I'd say you're an eight on the Crane Scale.
Profound fear.
12 is top.
Abject heart-stopping terror.
I'm surprised you're only an eight.
You do understand that
this is really happening?
I'm going to drown you.
Right now.
There! That's a ten.
Dad.
Jonathan, I said to wait in the van.
The parking meter ran out.
Look, son, I know this hard,
but we talked about it.
It's for the common good, for humanity.
I know. I just... I think...
This will be over soon. Here.
Go and feed the meter.
Go on, go.
Now, my dear,
don't think badly of me.
GCPD!
Don't move!
I'm on him! You get her!
He's alive.
I told you he was alive.
Praise the Lord.
Glory be.
What happened to you, boy?
Like the prodigal son,
ma'am, I have fallen.
Like Job,
I've been tested in the deepest pits
of the devil's perfidy
and survived.
Lord have mercy.
Are you headed to Gotham
City, by any chance?
Sure.
Come on.
Case files you gave me about that man
who was thrown from the roof.
Did you catch his killer yet?
Uh, no. He's still out there.
- Hi.
- I followed up,
and I had a quick look at his corpse.
A quick look at his corpse?
Yeah, its' just downstairs
at the morgue. No trouble.
So the killer removed his adrenal glands.
Adrenal glands? That's strange.
They have no value on
the black market, do they?
No. Kidneys and livers, yes.
Adrenal glands, no.
It produces cortisol,
the hormone that gives us
that adrenalized
fight-or-flight reaction.
Essentially, it's the fear gland.
And our man wants to
take it from the victim
when he's most fearful. Why do that?
All I can think of is that
at the moment of death,
the victim's adrenals
would produce a massive,
highly-elevated form of cortisol.
Fascinating, huh?
This is one weird dude.
A doctor or a nurse, most likely.
Takes some skill to remove
adrenals as cleanly as they did.
You really like this kind of work, huh?
I do.
Good.
Maybe there'll be more for you.
A full-time job, even.
Our M.E. has been fired
for stealing body parts.
- Can you believe that?
- Only in Gotham.
So, what do you say we
discuss this potential job
over dinner?
Nice segue, Mr. Smooth.
Thank you.
Dinner sounds good.
Are you gonna bring your case files?
Go ahead, mock my crude dating skills.
I'm doing my best.
You're doing fine.
I have a powerful urge
to kiss you right now.
Why don't you?
Because I'm on duty,
and, uh...
there's about 50 people watching us.
Scaredy-cat.
Damn straight. I have an image to keep up.
The heartless, by-the-book, hard man.
Kind of.
On the count of three, I'm gonna lean in,
so that it's subtle.
Then you're gonna kiss me
on the cheek or no dinner.
Come on. I'm serious.
One,
two,
three.
I'm not leaving after all.
What?
It turns out that the
medical examiner is leaving,
so Captain Essen decided to reinstate me.
Oh.
Okay, good.
Mr. Nygma?
You owe me a new pencil.
What's going on? What's happening?
I can hide you.
Quickly.
Sync & corrections by madhatters
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net