Previously on Gotham...
Welcome to Wayne Enterprises.
I have some questions
regarding Wayne Enterprises'
business affairs.
Where's Jim?
Don Falcone thinks you
don't know how to run a club.
Hi.
He'll help you out.
Those people out there
are using us as spare parts.
Unless we do something about it.
Alfred, can you teach me how to fight?
Yes, I can.
Pretty handy for a valet.
Butler, mate.
I'm a butler.
What the hell is that?
- I made it. Yeah.
- You made it?
- So what is it?
- It's a hood.
Thought it would, uh,
you know, spice things up.
When did we start wearing hoods?
- We didn't.
- W-Was I supposed to get one?
No!
Ladies... And gentlemen,
we are not here for your money!
We're here for the bank's money!
So just stay cool and no one will get hurt!
Don't be brave!
Don't be frightened!
Just do what you're told!
This will all be over
quicker than that time
I hooked up with a
cheerleader on prom night!
What are you doing up there?!
Getting 'em fired up.
90 seconds.
Nice and easy, ladies and gentlemen!
You know, banks like this
one... Who are insured
to death, by the way... Steal
from us every single day!
'Bout time a few of us returned
the favor, don't you think?
60 seconds.
You're being great, folks! Almost done!
40 seconds.
Nothing!
Not a scratch!
Th-Thirty seconds.
Let's get out of here!
You've been great, ladies
and germs, but we got to go!
Did you see that?
- That guy missed me with, like, six shots.
- He was, old, nervous.
No, no, no, it's the hood. I'm telling you.
Damn it. We're cooked.
Attention, citizens of Gotham!
What the hell are you doing?!
There you go, everybody!
Take back what's yours!
Follow me! Come on.
Well,
we'll never know how much cash was lost,
but I just saw a bum eating
oysters at Madeline's.
Another freak in a mask. Awesome.
Is that guard blind or wasted?
Clyde refused to wear his glasses.
Said they made him look old.
Missing a man standing 20 feet
in front of you with six shots
makes you look old.
- Who tripped the alarm?
- I did.
Why aren't you out there, Detective?
This brazen audacity cannot be tolerated.
They didn't go for the
vault... just the cash
in the registers. And
the crew was in and out
in under two minutes.
The red-hooded man seemed nice.
Nice?
He wasn't stealing our
money... just the bank's.
Then he gave a lot of it
back to people in the street. Like...
Robin Hood.
Oh, great. This bank hires Communists.
Robin Hood stole from the
rich and gave to the poor.
These armed thieves only threw cash away
to guarantee their escape.
It's very different, ma'am.
The thief
in the back here, was he
always checking his watch?
Yes. He was counting down.
They knew what our response time was.
They'd done their homework.
Has the alarm been triggered
for any other reason recently?
- No.
- Well,
there was that time with the smoke bomb.
Smoke bomb?
A week or so ago, a
small flare or firework,
or something, was set
off by the Mortgages desk.
It tripped the alarm. We thought
it was just a kid's prank.
We're gonna need you to
find the surveillance footage
from that incident.
Yes, sir. How can I help you?
Reggie?
Sorry for calling so late.
Forgive me.
Oh, my God, mate. How long's it been?
20 years.
I got picked up by the GCPD last night
for trying to sleep
under the Westbury Bridge.
- Here, mate.
- Cheers, mate.
One of the officers was
a Marine, back in the day,
so we got to talking. I told him
I was with Her Majesty's Special
Air Service back in the day.
So he took pity on me.
He says, "Why don't you look
up some of your old regiment,
you know, see if one of the
guys can... help you out."
Well, you know...
I'm pleased you looked me up, Reg.
If anyone would've told me
this is where I'd find you,
I wouldn't have believed them.
I like it here.
It's good for me.
I can see that.
I've missed you, mate.
Missed your ugly mug.
Cheers.
What happened, Reggie?
Vanessa died.
11 years ago now.
I just couldn't find the energy
to get back out there after that, you know?
A year later, I lost the house.
Moved back to Gotham.
I've had a few jobs.
Nothing I'm proud of.
It was the drink, Alfie.
It was the drink.
Alfred?
Um, Master Bruce.
This is, uh,
Reginald Payne.
We served together, sir.
Very pleased to meet you, sir.
You were caught in the storm?
Reggie's had a run of
bad luck, Master Bruce.
I-I don't wish to be a nuisance. I just...
I hadn't seen Alfie in a very long time.
N-No, I'm glad you found us, Mr. Payne.
Please, feel free to
stay with us a few days.
That's very kind of you, but...
I insist.
Please.
Where are you taking me?
This way, Miss Mooney.
Who chose these people?
Where'd you get them from?
Sit, please.
Sit.
There you are, Mr. Red Hood.
Armed robbery perps dating back ten years.
I took out the dead ones
and the ones in prison.
A who's who of scumbags.
They were casing the place a
week before they took it down.
Set off the alarm then timed the response.
He looks pretty young.
He might not be in here.
You see that?
No, 'cause you took my glasses.
Right there, underneath his coat.
He's wearing a work shirt.
"Kleg's Auto."
Idiot.
"The Red Hood Gang"!
It's got a ring to it.
- No, it doesn't.
- See those people?
They loved me.
They loved the money you threw at 'em.
Thanks for that, by the way.
Shall we take it out of your share?
You guys don't get it.
We're not just five mooks
with shotguns anymore.
We're the Red Hood Gang.
Taking from the rich and
giving back to the poor.
Mark my words,
the people in this town,
they're gonna get me.
- Us.
- Will you shut up?
All that prancing around
could have gotten us killed.
You're wrong. That guard,
he was 20 feet away from me.
Not one shot got close.
Luck!
He looked r-real nervous.
It's the hood!
It's good luck. I'm telling you.
I feel like a totally
different person with it on.
Eh, sit down, will ya?
We need to go over tomorrow's score.
Nah, this sets us apart.
It's a piece of cloth...
Two holes cut out of it.
It's a symbol!
Whoever wears the hood
should lead!
He's right.
Any objections?
So...
you're the one causing all of the fuss.
The one with the knife now.
This is your facility?
I manage it, yes.
But do you own it?
The doctor owns it.
Where are you going?
Back to the basement. We're done here.
Miss Mooney...
Take a seat.
I will talk to the doctor
and the doctor only.
He's away on a consultation in Gotham.
Then call me when he returns.
He expressly asked me
to attend to your demands.
His name.
I'm sorry?
The doctor. His name.
Dulmacher.
You tell Dr. Dulmacher
that the basement is mine.
No one will leave
unless I say so. It will remain that way
until he sits with me
and negotiates terms.
Perhaps...
you and I got off on the
wrong foot, Miss Mooney.
When was the last time
you had a shower? A
new set of clothes? Hmm?
Take Miss Mooney to my private bathroom,
and then pick up some fresh
clothes for her from storage.
Freshen up.
Come back to me.
And then perhaps we'll talk some more.
So the mortician says
to the waitress... No, the
waitress says to the mortician,
"He was always stiff."
That's it.
- Let's go.
- Wait. No.
Have a good night. See
you next week, sir. Okay.
- It's fine. We got, uh...
- Check, please.
cards.
Oh, okay. Um...
What's wrong?
Ah, Mr. Penguin. I mean
the Penguin. I mean...
- I...
- What is it?
We're out of booze.
What? Hello? Behind you,
there's a wall of booze.
Just colored water, sir. Always has been.
We keep the real stuff
down here, but we're out.
- So, duh, order more.
- We did.
It's just that...
It's Maroni's booze.
And he's a little grumpy
with you these days.
He was hardly a fan of Fish, either.
Why did he sell her booze?
Business is business.
But he hates you with a passion.
- But he can't kill you, so...
- That's...
This is ridiculous. There's a
thousand places to buy booze.
That's where it gets complicated.
See, Maroni, he supplies
this whole side of town.
No one would dare cross him to help you.
Help...
Get outta here!
Thank you. Bye. Sorry.
You're not funny.
You must take
great pleasure watching me fail.
On the contrary.
I was with Fish
when we took this place off a
Chinese bookie nine years ago.
It was used for cock fighting.
Took forever to get the smell out.
My blood, sweat, and
tears are in this dive.
Well, if you'll excuse me,
it seems as though I need
to procure some alcohol
for my dwindling clientele.
Be careful.
You've seen what happens
when you cross Maroni.
GCPD!
Looks like they were here last night.
Hey.
Your hot doctor friend, Thompkins...
- Leslie.
- Whatever.
Give me the double D... "dirty details."
Don't leave anything out.
Gotta hand it to you, partner.
You don't sit around moping.
You got right back up on the hobby horse.
Let's just hope you can
keep your head straight
whilst up there.
You had the purse. Now
you got yourself a nurse.
Well, looks like I found our friend Floyd.
What? If I don't drink it, Forensics will.
All right. This
was the guy with the hood.
He's wearing the same coat.
I wonder what he did to piss
off the rest of his crew.
Maybe they knew we'd catch up to him.
Well, he was the leader,
so it looks like we've seen
the last of the Red Hood crew now.
Good morning, everyone!
Get off me! I got it.
Okay. We're not here
for your money.
We're here for the insurance!
I mean the bank's insured money!
60 seconds.
Hey! You gonna share a little
bit of that cash with us, Hood?
Th-Thirty seconds.
Come on. A lot of us
are hurting here.
Ten seconds.
L-L... L-Let's go!
Aw, fine.
So long, Gotham!
Sayonara!
And then there were four.
People are gonna hang out
in banks waiting for handouts
from these idiots.
We're never gonna catch a
crew no one wants us to catch.
Call me old-fashioned, but when crooks
become more popular than cops,
- that's anarchy.
- Think about it.
As long as somebody's willing
to put that red hood on,
this gang can go on forever.
Hey, guys.
Got somebody here you might want to meet.
- This is Mister...
- Chaing.
Chaing, right. He's an eyewitness.
From the bank?
I work at a restaurant a block away.
The Red Hood Gang parked
their van there this morning.
I was throwing out the trash
when they ran back to it.
You see their faces?
Just one... the fat one with the hood.
He took it off to drive.
- I'll get the sketch artist.
- Well, wait a minute.
Got the armed robbery files already opened.
Maybe he can look through them,
see if he recognizes someone.
Maybe that someone is a
known associate of Gus Floyd.
Only problem is records are kind of
old... he might look different now.
We could pull a few based
off Chaing's description.
Get ourselves a good old-fashioned lineup.
Wait. Wait a second. What's in it for me?
I got all these parking tickets
because my ex-wife is a crazy bitch.
We'll see what we can do.
Training for a fight?
Just training.
Who's helping you?
Alfred.
Good choice.
Show me your stance.
Good.
Hit me.
Again.
And don't hold back.
You have a go at me, son.
Come on.
It should take more than
that to piss you off, son.
Come on.
Again.
Now, now. Never lose your cool.
It'll get you killed.
Now, you want to hit me, right?
You want to hit me, right?
Okay. Take a swing.
Take a swing. Go on. Do it.
Somebody gives you a free shot,
you got to make it count.
You hit me as hard as you can.
Oh. Better.
Put your shoulder behind it.
Put your full body weight behind it.
Go on. Do it.
Harder. Again.
Again.
Come on. Do it again.
Put me on my back, son.
Come on, you can do it.
Come on. Again.
- You're so much bigger than me!
- Then use that to your advantage!
You hit me low. Hit me
in the knee, the ankle.
Forget about the gloves!
Use whatever's around you.
Here. Here.
- Go on.
- Right!
That's enough of that.
Perhaps a shower's in order, Master Bruce.
M-Mr. Payne was just showing
me some alternative methods.
Yeah, I can see that, can't I?
Not methods that fit into our
curriculum, though, are they?
No, they're not; but they're effective.
Discipline, skill,
and hard work are effective.
How 'bout I start that shower for you, sir?
No.
You ever raised a child before, Reg?
- No.
- Me neither.
Hardest job I've ever had to do in my life.
Nothing prepares you for it.
Listen, I'm sorry if
I overstepped the mark.
I was just...
It was obvious how much
you've helped him s...
No, he helped me.
I'm a better person for knowing him, Reg.
Let's keep our past where it belongs.
In the past.
That's it? Just two workers?
This'll be easy. Make it quick, guys.
Well, this is inconvenient.
Whoa, Officer.
- Nothing going on here.
- That so?
Eh, your liquor license is out of date.
We're gonna be confiscating the shipment.
Hey, does Don Maroni
know you guys are here?
Walk away... before I run you downtown.
This town is truly going to the dogs.
Evening, fellas.
Why the smile, Butch?
First Maroni blocks our liquor,
and now the cops?
Oh, who, them? They're with me.
I always keep a few uniforms in the closet.
A lot cleaner than going in
guns blazing, don't you think?
You're welcome, Oswald.
Nice work there.
How you doing, Mr. Gilzean?
This over here, this...
Nothing to worry about.
You okay?
Of course.
Thank you for letting us stay here.
Sorry it got a little messy.
I was just about to go.
I like having you guys here.
Selina...
Come here.
You know, you're turning into
quite the beautiful woman.
No, I'm not.
Remove the dirt...
that old hood...
these ratty clothes...
I bet we find a princess undernea...
I have an idea.
Holy moly.
Take anything that fits you guys.
This is all stuff you've worn?
Most of it.
You sure must go out a lot.
I used to.
Come with me.
You're a true beauty.
Something you can use to your advantage.
Your appearance can be a weapon,
as powerful as any knife or gun.
Yeah?
What good's it done you?
All
right, backs to the wall.
Hold your numbers up.
No talking.
I thought they were
going to be similar types.
- They are.
- Uh-huh.
- Look closely, Mr. Chaing.
- I know how this works.
There, number four... The short, fat one.
- You're sure?
- That's your Red Hood.
Threw all that money away,
and I didn't get a cent.
Clyde Destro, 47 years old, conviction
for assault and armed robbery of a
convenience store three years ago.
- Let's book him.
- Wait a minute.
All we have is one witness outside
of the crime scene, that's it.
Now, Floyd was killed, so we know
they're turning on each other.
- Let Destro go?
- And tail him.
He takes us to the other gang members.
We use them against each other.
We catch the Red Hood Gang red-handed.
That's right.
Can I get a ride home?
My girlfriend will freak out
if I turn up in a patrol car.
Well...
don't you look lovely?
There's still business to discuss.
Of course.
The basement.
How do I resume operations?
We do have a business to run.
Yes, you're stealing body parts.
- For who?
- Oh!
We have clients...
all over the world in need of such things.
Also, there's the doctor's
personal experiments.
You have such a presence,
Miss Mooney.
Such a gaze.
Your eyes...
will fetch quite a penny.
You will take nothing from me.
Really?
Because the way I see it,
you have two choices: One...
we kill you and your little
friends in the basement.
That's an inconvenience
but an acceptable one.
Or, two...
we take your eyes now
and see how long a blind girl
can survive in the basement.
You forgot option three.
Stop her!
No!
I picked something out from the cellar.
I hope that's okay.
Well, that's, uh, extremely kind of you,
Master Bruce, but I don't think that we...
that I'll be, uh, drinking this evening.
I'm sure it's perfectly fine to have
a glass of wine occasionally, Alfred.
I-I picked an old one.
Seems a shame to let them
gather dust down there.
Domaine de la Romanée-Conti.
It's a rather nice Burgundy,
actually, it's 1966.
Yeah.
It's one of your father's favorites.
Why not, eh? Take a pew.
That's very kind of you.
- There you go.
- Cheers, mate.
Now, the idea, of course,
is to let it breathe for at least an hour.
Or not.
Ah. Delicious.
So he eventually opened his backpack
and he found the bloody snake.
We'd been waiting for it all night.
He didn't even flinch.
- What'd you do?
- Oh, you know,
I chopped its head off and
we ate the bloody thing.
He did.
What did it taste like?
Uh, a bit like, um, fast food.
It was horrible.
It was horrible. It was disgusting.
So, um...
so, Mr. Payne, you were in the Air Force?
Special Air Service... SAS.
Best soldiers in the world,
if I'm being honest.
So that means covert missions?
That's right.
Before a conflict, they dropped us
behind enemy lines.
We were quiet, precise, and deadly.
We never lost a man
and we always completed our missions.
Except that once, I guess.
Yeah, well, that's enough of
the old war stories, eh, Reg?
What one time?
There was a sandstorm.
We got separated.
Two of us were captured.
You?
He fought 12 of them off
before they cut him down.
Didn't you, Alf?
I'm here now, aren't I?
That's all that matters.
All right, gents, while I have to
say this has been absolutely lovely,
I'd like to,
I'd like to tidy up before I go to bed.
T-T-Tidy up?
Mr. Yes Sir, No Sir.
Mr. Queensberry rules and discipline.
Thank you, that's enough.
Alfred's right... it's time for bed.
Good night, Master Bruce.
Good night. Good night.
Sleep well, son.
Why are you hiding from
him what you really are,
who you really are?
You're a war dog, Alfie.
You're a cold-blooded,
lethal war dog, is what you are.
I found some fresh clothes for you, Reg.
I folded them and I put 'em on your bed,
and I've taken the liberty of packing you
a lunch for your travels tomorrow.
It's been really nice to see you, Reggie.
I see them, at night... when I'm alone.
The faces...
the faces of those we killed.
Do you?
I don't have to look for them, Reg.
They find me.
Holy crap.
You scared the snot out of me.
H-Had to see you.
I c-couldn't wait.
- Where were you?
- Out.
J-Just out?
What's it to you?
I need the hood.
What?
- No.
- M...
My-my girlfriend, sh-she
wants... she wants to leave.
She... she called me a loser last night.
Her ex is back in town. He's a b-bouncer.
I figured she-she sees me
in the hood, she's got... she's
got to take me s-seriously.
Did you ransack my place looking for it?
I need it, Destro.
They're talking about it on the streets
and in the news. She
sees me in it, and I'm...
No!
We have one last job before
we split up and skip town.
You have it on you, don't you?
You better use that thing
before I make you eat it.
He's alive.
Who shot you, Destro? Give us the name
- of the guy.
- I need an ambulance.
We'll get to that. Give us the
names of the guys in your crew.
I'm bleeding out.
Yeah, you're dying.
And, unfortunately, I'm
not getting cell reception.
You know what might help?
Giving us the names of
the guys in your crew!
I need an ambulance.
Java Heights and Homewood, apartment 466.
I might need some pressure on this wound.
Knock yourself out.
What do you got there, partner?
A stack of loan rejection
letters from the banks
that were robbed.
"Dear Mr. Destro, we regret
to inform you your application
for a loan has been denied."
"Mr. Destro, once again, we
must deny your application,
due to inadequate collateral."
What the hell would he need a loan for?
Pastry shop.
Get out of here. You're a baker?
A damn good baker.
And they all turned you down.
So these are revenge robberies.
Banks don't care about people like me.
Or you, probably.
You have to force people to see you.
Otherwise, you're nothing.
There's a third letter here.
International Savings Bank
of Gotham... this was the next target.
Where's my ambulance?
To new beginnings.
I'm not trying to poison you, son.
Forgive me if I'm a little cautious.
If this club tanks,
Falcone's not gonna
trust either of us again.
I don't know about you,
but I'm done playing the sidekick.
To no longer being a sidekick.
Do you miss her?
I do.
Even after everything she did to me.
Perhaps it's not our friends but...
our enemies that define us.
To Fish.
She got what she deserved.
You're stealing from us?
You could have just
asked me for money, Reg.
You don't know how hard
that is, Alfie... do you?
We gave you somewhere to sleep.
We put food in your belly.
I'm in trouble.
Real trouble.
I don't need a lecture right now.
What kind of trouble?
You don't want to know.
Right. Well, you put the bag down
and you leave.
Now.
Did you bring a gun, Alfie?
No.
If there was any other way...
Oh, come on... there's
always another way, mate.
I'm sorry.
Sorry f...
I'm so sorry.
Th-This is Bruce Wayne.
I need immediate help at Wayne Manor!
My friend has been stabbed.
Alfred... Alfred, Alfred, look
at me... you're gonna be okay.
Alfred, stay with me.
: Please.
Alfred!
There's only three of us.
I'm worried. If someone
makes a move in there...
Don't be.
I have this.
GCPD!
We have you surrounded!
This doesn't have to end
badly! Put down your guns!
Suck it, coppers!
Man down! Man down!
Hold your fire!
Drop it!
It's over.
Yeah?
Don't be so sure.
I need a Danish.
Yeah.
Which hospital?
: I can't lose him.
He's all I have.
He has nothing concrete.
Just faces, some dates,
some newspaper articles.
There's no grounds for an investigation.
Just... suspicions...
some cobbled-together theories...
Nothing.
Has he had outside counsel?
I don't think so.
And his caretaker, Mr. Pennyworth?
He's in the hospital.
For how long?
If he lives,
a few weeks, give or take.
Now's the time to make a move on the kid.
Thank you for your service, Mr. Payne.
I doubt we'll meet again.
He's just a kid.
A good kid.
Good-bye, Mr. Payne.
www.tvsubtitles.net