Previously on gotham...
Listen, there are
things I need to do.
If you stay, I stay.
Zsasz:
My name is victor zsasz.
I'm here for jim gordon.
Everybody out.
Essen:
There's not a single cop
in this city
Who'll help you.
I won't help you.
I'm not leaving.
You don't have to join me.
I figure I'm doomed anyhow.
I might as well
join the good guys.
Mooney:
I ain't looking for no girl.
I'm looking for a weapon.
Excuse me.
You want to start a war
over this punk?
The little guy amuses me.
Falcone:
Why go to war over trifles?
We'll let you have him.
Our gift to you.
(panting quietly)
Oh, god, oh, god.
(yells)
(grunting)
(choking)
(grunts)
(moaning)
(foghorn blares)
(helicopter blades whirring)
(seagulls screeching)
(coffee spills)
oh.
Hell of a way
to start the day.
I mean, I just cleaned this.
Harvey.
Hey.
Uniforms found the body.
No wallet,
no id, no watch.
He got beaten
up pretty good.
I'm guessing the cause of
death is that gigantic gash
In the side
of his neck.
You think? What's all
the black on him?
Ink? Paint?
Hmm.
Good morning, ed.
Detective.
Going by overall coagulation,
I'd say time of death
is midnight. But...
He's only been here
for a couple hours.
Rats have just
started on his ears.
Sneaky little buggers.
So, not a mugging.
Muggers don't
move the body.
Abrasions on
his knuckles...
Put up a fight.
Yeah.
Look at the suspenders.
I'm guessing he's
some kind of finance guy.
Maybe it was an abduction
ransom thing gone wrong.
He resists,
ka-chunk!
Do you want to talk to the
uniforms that found the body?
Uh, you do it.
We should canvass
The area, though;
a lot of homeless around here.
I'll get some unis on it.
I'll handle it myself.
Hey, joe!
Go smoke somewhere else, huh?
Come on, jim, that's what
we got uniforms for.
Let them do it.
And I'd rather handle it myself.
Detectives...
I'm guessing I should run
all the prints?
Yeah, ed,
run the prints.
This one, too?
Yeah, ed, that one, too.
It wasn't even a proper yacht.
No, it's more like a dinghy.
Can I help you?
What a lovely brooch.
Thank you.
May I have it?
(laughs)
I have a friend
who would love that.
Excuse me?
Oh...
(laughing)
I'm sorry.
May I please have it?
You shouldn't have.
Oswald:
I wanted to
make a gesture.
I hope, in time,
We can be friends.
Friends?
Hmm.
Sure.
Why not?
What's done is done.
I'm so glad you feel that way.
Don maroni
wants us
To clarify terms.
Well, it's business as usual.
Maroni still has
his drugs, his unions.
He pays tariff
for the ports.
If he needs favors
from the cops
Or the mayor,
don falcone will consider it.
And, of course, the families
still share arkham.
And there is to be no blood
spilled on either side.
Not a drop.
Hmm...
Maybe just a drop.
(laughing)
(clucks tongue)
Look at you.
Timothy,
Do you know this fellow
used to have your job?
Carried my umbrella
and thought it an honor.
Now look at him.
Has a seat at the table.
Things change, eh?
I've been blessed.
Perhaps I should open your gift.
(gasps)
My goodness.
That is beautiful.
Now I feel
Awful.
I didn't get you anything.
No.
Thank you.
Hmm.
Sweet.
That was uncalled for.
I brought you
into my family
And I treated you like a son!
And you betrayed me.
For which I suffered.
Not enough.
When I order some fool killed,
I expect him to stay that way.
Your boss, don falcone,
Expressly said...
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
he wants peace.
He's the only reason
why your ass is still alive.
And if I were you,
I would
Pray for his good health.
(laughing)
Oh, I do.
I do.
Good.
'cause remember...
...Things change.
Convey my respects to your don.
Likewise.
Peace...
Friend.
(school bell ringing)
(children talking, laughing)
Alfred:
Come now, master bruce.
Had to happen sooner or later.
Is this really necessary?
Homeschooling is
just as effective.
I can show you the data.
You need to be around children
your own age.
Why?
'cause you do.
You know I despise
that sort of answer.
Don't you miss your mates?
Not really.
I've always found them
kind of childish.
Well, that's what they're
meant to be, aren't they?
That's what they do.
Don't you want to be
Like a normal kid?
I'm not sure.
Define "normal"
and make a good case for it.
You're going to bloody school.
(bell tolling)
Now start walking.
Good luck, lad.
Gordon: Very sorry
for your loss, ma'am.
Can you think of anyone
Who would want to hurt
your son coleman?
No, sir.
Nobody.
He was a good boy.
Yes, ma'am, I can see that.
No arrests.
An honest young man.
What did he do for a living?
Uh, he worked in a coffee shop.
When we found him,
he was in a suit.
Suspenders.
He was looking for
a job in finance.
He was very ambitious.
First in our family
to go to college.
(crying):
Who would do this, sir?
Why?
We'll do our best
to find out, ma'am.
Gordon's finishing up
with the mother.
So far, nothing off
the severed thumb
And none of the city's ers
have seen any thumbless guys.
You think he went black market?
That's next on my list.
How's gordon?
Angry.
How would you feel if every cop
In the building ran out on you?
And now they
all treat him
Like he's got the plague,
'cause seeing him reminds them
Of what cowards they all are.
I'm sorry, cap, I...
I didn't mean you.
Nope.
You're right.
But he's gotta get over that.
Can't do this
job alone.
Lucky he's got you.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
(gasps)
So beautiful.
As soon as I saw it,
I thought of you.
Such a good son.
Put it on, put it on.
Oh...
(gasps)
Wh-what happened?
Who did this?
N-nobody.
It's just a scratch.
It's...
Is your mother a fool?
No. Someone
Is being mean to my boy.
Hey.
It's a tough business.
The restaurant business
is so tough these days?
Why is that?
My success makes
other people envious.
So tell the boss
on these people.
This person isn't
Scared of the boss.
Not like they should be.
I don't know why.
I know.
When I was
in school,
Magda himmelfarb
Was so mean to me
And teacher did nothing.
Why?
Because
Such a good dancer I was.
And magda,
With her nice hair
And her big bosoms,
A carthorse.
I meant...
Why did the teacher do nothing?
Why you
think?
"private lessons," they said.
I put
Stop to that.
You told on them?
Oh, no.
I denounced magda's father
To secret police.
(trap snaps, rodent squeals)
Ah...
Three weeks he's been
Turning up his nose at my traps,
And now, now,
today, a smidge
Of camembert
And mr. Rat,
He cannot
resist.
No. Oh, can you?
Can you,
my little
Greedy baby?
I found out your secret!
Yes.
Everybody has a secret.
(screaming)
Morphine!
They teach you that
in med school?
Oh...
Bullock.
Is that kenny suffield?
Smash and grab guy.
Also a real hound
with the ladies.
Who shot him?
I don't ask.
Well, me and my partner
doing all the rounds
Of you black market sawbones.
Guy we're looking for
Would've come in
early this morning
Missing a thumb.
Sorry.
You'd tell us if you knew,
wouldn't you, doc?
I mean,
that's the deal, right?
You give us info
and we let you keep operating?
That's a pun. Operating.
Bullock, black ink,
Just like on the victim.
Oh, doc.
Fine.
He came in about 3:00
this morning.
Didn't give a name,
But this dropped
out of his pocket.
Sionis investments.
What'd he look like?
Mid-20s.
Suit, suspenders.
Just like our dead guy.
Sorry, doc.
This is gordon.
I need an ambulance
And a black and white
at 1856 wilton.
Wait!
Just... Wait a second.
Just get me alvarez,
will you?
Alvarez: Bullock, bullock,
what the hell, man?
I got a deal with that guy.
Deal's off.
But I told you everything.
Yeah, after we
caught you in a lie.
He always lies.
You just squeeze him.
You're screwing
the rest of us.
Oh, yeah?
How's that feel? You like it?
Hey, enough, enough!
I get it, I get it, huh?
None of these sons of bitches
had your back when it mattered,
But where was I?
I was there, remember?
Falcone, the mayor,
blaze of glory?
Be nice for my sake.
I am being nice.
Haven't you learned
your lesson?
We're only alive
because falcone let us live.
You got to go along
to get along, jim.
No, I don't.
You think locking up
Doc scumbag there
is gonna make a difference?
I'm on your side.
I proved that.
Yeah, you did.
So I'm asking you, please,
Let the doc out and tomorrow,
You and I will go check out
This sionis investments
together.
All right, partner?
Sorry, harv.
This ain't right, harvey.
Alvarez, put a zipper on it!
(door closes)
(gun clicks)
(gasps)
jim.
Barbara, what are you...
I heard someone come in,
and you didn't turn
On the light...
So you got out my spare?
You were late!
I got nervous.
God.
Not the best idea
To be handling a firearm
when you've been drinking.
I'm sorry.
Look, you've been
through a lot.
It's over now.
I am scared, jim.
Everywhere I go, I can...
I can feel that monster, zsasz,
Stalking me, and I...
He's not a monster.
He's just a man.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
How can you promise me that?
Tell me it'll be okay.
(sighs)
Tell me there really aren't
any monsters.
Just...
Lie if you have to.
There aren't any monsters.
When are we gonna
get out of here?
That's up to you.
Morning.
(sighing):
Hey.
I didn't think you were up.
Look, last night was
just nerves...
And way too much to drink.
I said I wanted half your life,
and I've got it.
Leave the gun.
I wish it wasn't like this.
Do you really?
(sighs)
Ignore me. I'm just tired.
Go.
Catch some bad guys.
(softly):
Okay.
(door opens)
(glove snaps)
Forensic examination
by edward nygma,
8:42 a.M., gcpd morgue.
The room is approximately
19 degrees celsius.
I ate half
a cranberry muffin earlier,
Saving the rest for later.
What do a dead man,
a cruise ship
And emu have in common?
Correct, nothing.
Ever more curious.
Medical examiner:
He what?!
Nygma, how many times
have I told you
To stay the hell out of here?
But I discovered something.
You'll discover
Your butt in the street
if you keep doing this.
Out.
Your loss.
You sloppy ignoramus.
Hi, bruce.
Hi.
Brucey, how you doing?
Tommy, hey.
I'm well, how are you?
You know, chilling.
So, uh, your mom and dad
got killed, huh?
Yes.
You see the whole thing?
The blood and everything?
I'd rather not talk about that.
I was just interested.
I've never seen
a real dead body.
Was there guts?
I'll be going to class now.
(bell tolling)
Forgive me, mother,
for I have sinned.
Mooney:
Funny.
It feels weird, meeting here.
You don't want anyone
to see us together.
Falcone has his eyes everywhere.
So, where are we?
I cook for him,
I sing to him,
We go on walks.
I don't know whether
I'm his maid, his lover
Or his mother.
Or all three.
He cares about you.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Have you been
inside his private office?
Yeah.
A few times.
Inside the right bottom
desk drawer is a ledger.
Copy the last two pages.
It'll be locked;
you will need a key
Off of his key ring.
(scoffs)
how do I get that?
Behind you is a vial.
Give it to him.
He'll sleep like the dead
For two hours.
It won't kill him, will it?
(groans)
(chuckles)
Liza,
You haven't caught feelings
for the old man, have you?
Not at all.
No, it won't kill him.
Killing him now
would only create chaos.
I need to siphon his strength.
So when the time is right,
Taking over his organization
Will be like slipping
on a glove.
What if one of his men
Catches me snooping?
Then you're probably dead.
You leave first.
(indistinct chatter)
Man:
Right, right, right.
(overlapping chatter)
I'm under a lot of pressure.
(overlapping chatter continues)
Something tells me we came
to the right place.
You think?
Mr. Sionis will see you now.
Oh.
Richard sionis.
James gordon.
This is my partner,
harvey bullock.
How can I help you detectives?
I don't have much time.
You know this man?
Coleman lawson?
He might have interviewed
for a job.
Sorry, no.
Any of your employees
miss work yesterday?
Any of them show up today
with an injured right hand?
I don't take roll call,
detective.
You mind if we check?
Perhaps you can tell me
what this is about?
Coleman lawson was killed
two night ago.
The man who did it had
your firm's card in his pocket.
Well, there's a thousand ways
he could've gotten that.
What's with all
the warrior baloney?
It inspires me.
High finance is tough business.
In order to succeed,
you have to be a warrior.
No, you don't.
You have to be
a good businessman.
Warriors fight wars.
It's different.
So you fancy yourself
A killer?
Have you killed people,
mr. Sionis?
Only metaphorically.
So all this is just
juvenile play acting.
Exactly.
Thus speaks a man
Who's seen actual combat.
You've killed people
for real,
Haven't you?
True killers are easy to spot.
Yes, they are.
Why all the masks?
A shrink would say
you're hiding something.
To the contrary.
A mask hides the face,
But frees the soul.
A mask
Speaks the truth.
Deep.
How come so many
of your employees
Have scars
and injuries?
Our touch football games
get very rough.
You're a liar, mr. Sionis.
Such fire.
You must miss the battlefield
Desperately.
I imagine killing gets
quite addictive.
You murdered coleman lawson,
didn't you?
Prove it.
We will.
I'd give you a good cop routine,
But it's not in my tool kit.
(indistinct chatter)
(water running)
Gcpd.
(turns off water)
turn around slowly.
Let me see those hands!
(toilet flushes)
Don't move!
(both grunting)
You should've waited for me.
(door closes)
(school bell ringing)
(indistinct chatter)
Hey, brucey.
It's bruce.
No "y."
No parents, either, so I
can call you what I like.
Please, get out of my way.
Snobby little
jerk, isn't he?
For an orphan.
You're being very unkind.
I don't understand why.
Boy, you're a weirdo.
Your mother must...
(grunts)
Don't talk about my mother.
Oh, really?
Oh, is that timothy?
(chuckles)
we met at fish mooney's, hmm?
I'm the fellow who used
to have your job.
I was hoping to ask you
a few questions.
I don't know any...
(shushes)
They'll be time for that.
First things first.
(grunting)
(blows landing,
timothy grunting)
Bullock:
Most killers leave their prints
At the crime scene,
but not you, no.
You left your whole thumb
in the dead guy's mouth.
You got style!
I like you, kid.
This is your last chance.
Once we walk out that door...
It's over.
It was self-defense.
Bullock:
Of course it was.
Wasn't that what I said, jim?
Didn't I say it was
probably self-defense?
Talk.
Bullock:
Gordon's getting
the rest of his statement.
Apparently it was
part of the hiring process.
Sionis told the top three
candidates to fight it out.
They weren't supposed
to fight to the death, but...
This is unbelievable.
They all signed
confidentiality agreements,
So they're accomplices
to whatever happens.
Do we know where
the fight was held?
Some old office building.
The windows were boarded up.
And he was taken there
blindfolded.
Yes, ed?
Printer toner.
Do you know what
he's talking about?
The medical examiner's report
said it was black ink.
But I did my own examination,
and it was printer toner.
Also, I pulled staples
from his shoulders.
And found graphite chips
between his ribs.
Your man was killed
in an office.
Yeah, we're kind of past that,
ed, but thanks.
Is there something else?
Yes.
It made me think of a case
from a year ago.
Young man, business suit,
Esophagus lacerated
from index card
Shoved down his throat.
So, I did some digging...
How many other bodies were
killed with office supplies?
Four... In the last three years.
Essen:
Get that man
To sign a confession. Now.
I think we have a problem.
I explained to detective gordon,
as counsel to mr. Adams
I'd advised him
against speaking further.
Also, any statements
He has made will be
considered having
Been made under duress.
Uh-huh, and how much is sionis
paying him to take the fall?
Good day.
He showed up before adams
could sign his statements.
We got to figure out where
sionis is staging these fights.
I'll run all the buildings he
or his company owns in gotham.
This make any sense to you?
No, but how's it any worse
than the goat or the balloonman?
When did this become
normal for this city?
What changed?
Maybe nothing.
Maybe it was always
Just below the surface.
Only needed a spark.
Like thomas and martha
wayne being killed?
I'm not blind, gordon.
I know you're
still looking into it.
But how could their deaths
have caused all this?
Why were they so important?
I think it's
what they represented.
A different gotham.
Decent, hopeful.
Whatever it was, it's gone now.
When zsasz came for you,
I should've stayed.
I told you to go.
That doesn't matter.
I should've stayed.
Now, let's get this guy.
Yeah.
(door opens)
Tad late, master bruce.
Oi.
Oi. What happened to you?
I'm perfectly fine!
What happened?
Someone spoke disrespectfully
about my mother.
Oh, did they now?
Well, I hope you broke
their bastard teeth for them.
No.
He's much bigger
than me, and I...
I'm not very good at fighting.
Didn't hurt him at all.
Not at all?
Don't tell the school.
Not bloody likely.
Bullock:
Take a look at this.
Sionis owns half of gotham!
All right, we'll split up.
Focus on the buildings
that are abandoned
Or under construction first.
This son of a bitch
is not getting away!
I'll say one thing...
he has your number.
What are you talking about?
Sionis.
You may not have put down
cobblepot, jimmy boy,
But you got a demon in you.
You can call yourself a soldier,
but all this fighting falcone,
Fighting other cops,
You love it.
So, when you find something
That seems remotely possible,
call me.
(cell phone ringing)
Barbara, everything all right?
Fine. I just, uh,
I wanted to check in.
Can we talk later? I'm kind of
in the middle of something.
Of course.
(laughs)
I love...
(clicks, dial tone droning)
(phone beeps off)
Man:
Hey!
Boss wants his tea.
It's almost ready.
(lights buzzing)
(rattling nearby)
Gcpd!
(gasps)
Anybody else here?
(taser clicking)
(grunts)
That...
Would be a yes.
All right, cream and sugar.
Yeah.
Hey.
Uh...
Hi.
A girl's got to shop.
(siren wailing in distance)
This...
Is your father's watch.
Don't you lose it now.
Tommy elliot's house.
Don't you be scared.
I'm not.
I'm visualizing
what I'm gonna do.
'cause you if you don't want
to do this,
There's no shame in it.
There would be
immense shame in it.
(buzzer rings)
What the hell
are you doing here?
We have unfinished business.
Listen, if you think
you're gonna tell my parents...
(grunts)
are you crazy?!
Don't talk about my mother!
Alfred:
Master bruce!
Point well made, I think.
You all right, mate?
Any broken bones?
He-he tried to kill me!
That's right.
He did.
He tried to kill you.
Just you remember that
next time you see him.
And you remember
That I let him try.
Now, let's get some ice
On those knuckles.
What do you fancy
for your dinner?
Pizza.
Pizza?
Superb choice,
master bruce.
Jim, where the hell are you?
My list crapped out. Call me.
Nygma, gordon hasn't
called in, has he?
No. But if the detective
becomes the mystery...
Sionis (over loudspeaker):
Wake up.
Detective gordon?
Wake up!
So, three of you
Applied for a position
at my firm.
I explained then
You can use anything here
as a weapon
And the last man standing
gets the job.
However...
Tonight is special.
You see the man
Without the mask?
Whoever kills him...
Is the victor.
Listen to me.
I'm a cop.
So far, none of you
have broken any laws.
Let the games...
Begin.
(bell rings)
One last chance!
Nobody move!
Sionis:
Oh.
And I'll throw in a
million-dollar signing bonus.
Ah, crap.
Alvarez.
I need help checking
these addresses.
Gordon might be
in trouble.
Busy.
I'm gonna remember that
next time your wife calls,
Asking where you are,
you putz.
Collins.
Listen up, man,
can I have some help?
Now, listen up,
you sons of bitches!
So, you don't like gordon!
Fine.
He can be a total asshat.
But he is still a cop.
And not one of you, not one,
stood up when he needed it.
That ain't happening twice.
I need help checking
these addresses.
Now.
Give me a couple.
Okay.
But you cover
with my wife, right?
Yeah.
(grunting)
(cheering)
(gasping)
(exclaiming)
(grunting)
(murmuring)
it's over.
(sword unsheathing)
I knew you had a killer in you.
(murmuring)
So...
Where are your brother police?
Did they abandon you?
I don't need them.
(cheering)
Seems I'll have to give myself
the million dollars.
(sword clatters on floor)
Essen:
Jim?
(footsteps approaching)
jim?!
Jim!
(groans)
Thanks.
You're welcome.
♪ if I die ♪
♪ and my soul be lost ♪
♪ ain't nobody's fault
but mine ♪
♪ ain't nobody's fault ♪
♪ but mine ♪
♪ if I die ♪
♪ and my soul be lost ♪
♪ ain't nobody's fault
but mine. ♪
You'd better have a good
reason for being here.
Did you get what I asked for?
I want out.
No.
He's gonna find out.
Maybe not today,
but soon.
Is it worth it?
You are rich.
People are afraid of you.
Is that not enough?
No.
It's not.
I grew up not too
far from here.
One bedroom,
cold water.
Just me and my mama.
I used to sleep in a
bed behind a curtain.
It's where I would hide
when she entertained men.
And that's where I was
when he killed her.
One of falcone's men.
Didn't like the service.
I hid there,
Silent, until morning.
With my mama two
feet away from me.
That night, I made a promise.
To get revenge.
To never again be powerless.
To never let any man,
any man, be over me.
This is about keeping that
promise to that little girl.
So, what's this about?
(chuckles under her breath)
This is a thread.
I pull this
and falcone comes undone.
You're scared.
But I won't let
anything happen to you,
And that's a promise.
I want you to say...
"I believe you, mama."
I believe you, mama.
That's my girl.
Oswald: The thing is,
when I had your job,
Had someone asked me,
"what is miss mooney's secret?"
I could've answered.
Ooh.
(chuckles)
Timothy...
I think you're
holding back on me.
Okay, I...
I might've heard her
with butch.
Talking about what?
Whom?
Fal... Falcone.
She said, "our...
Our friend with falcone."
That's it.
She was whispering.
Please.
She has someone
close to falcone.
Of course.
Thank you.
No one can find the body.
No.
We are at peace after all.
No! No, please!
No! No...!
(distant siren wailing)
(low chatter)
Bullock: Alvarez and collins
are bringing in sionis' minions.
Pansies tried to rabbit when
they saw you cuffing their boss.
You okay?
Essen told me you made a speech.
I wouldn't call it a speech.
Said you called me an asshat.
I did call you that.
Thank you.
For having my back.
Now and before.
Just try not to be such
a pain in the neck.
Makes my day harder.
You know, you were wrong.
What you said earlier.
It's not that I love fighting.
But I'm not afraid to, either.
And if we don't fight
for this city, who will?
I'm not gonna stop, harvey.
Falcone, the mayor, every cop
I know that's dirty,
I'm gonna get them.
You should know that.
Go home, jim.
You were listening
tonight, weren't you?
You gonna get in
trouble, old woman.
Heard you telling
that girl stories.
A lie with a heart of truth
is a powerful thing.
Go on, it's late.
(phone rings)
(answering machine beeps)
Hey, it's me.
I'm coming home soon.
Everything is gonna be better,
I promise.
I love you.
Hey, gordon.
Got a minute?
Can it wait?
Kind of on my way
out of here.
Some unis brought in a perp.
Claims to know you.
Oh, yeah?
What's the charge?
B and e, some
fancy store uptown.
Pretty
professional job.
Kid didn't even
trip the alarm.
Kid?
Boy or girl?
Girl.
Said to ask if you been down
any sewers lately.
Hey, detective.
Miss me?
I enjoyed it.
I enjoyed hurting him.
Of course you did.
He deserved it.
I'm so angry all the time.
Will that ever go away?
That I don't know.
Alfred...
...Can you teach me
how to fight?
Yes, master bruce.
Yes, I can.
www.tvsubtitles.net