Previously on Gotham...
I'm sorry you had to
get mixed up in this.
'Cause I'm sure you're a
good, honest girl, really.
- I'm gonna disappear.
- You can't do that.
- I wasn't asking.
- You can't disappear.
You have to come back home with me.
When Detective Gordon finds the man
who killed my parents,
you have to testify.
I want these two alive for now.
You dare use my sainted
mother against me?
You'll suffer for that.
Say your good-byes quickly.
Miss Mooney has places to go.
Hello, Fish.
Well, you must be the B team.
We just handle transpo.
Bob will be taking care of you.
Bob?
One of our top guys.
You're in good hands.
Good morning.
You're up early.
I haven't made it to bed yet.
Word is you got caught
with Doc Thompkins
in the locker room.
Strictly business.
- Any word on Fish?
- No.
Club's all shot up, blood
everywhere, no sign of Fish.
It's her own damn fault.
She played the game,
she knew the risks.
Sorry, Harv, I know you
have a thing for her.
I don't got a thing for nobody.
My thing is for me.
If anyone can make it
out of a scrape like that,
it's Fish...
The woman's nails.
Come on, we got a case.
Yeah. What do we got?
Public service homicide.
Vic's a douche.
Flass. Gordon.
Gordon. Flass.
Flass works Narcotics.
Hence the bling and the,
no doubt expensive
yet somehow cheap-looking
Italian suit.
Bullock, still
dressing in the dark
and smelling like a taphouse whore.
One of Flass's connections
tipped him off on the body.
Why don't you tell
Gordon about the kid.
Pinky Littlefield.
Dealer from a crew known
as the Uptown Assassins.
He works this block. Well...
least he did.
Any drugs on him?
Didn't find any.
My big wild guess: Deal gone bad.
Kid like this, bound to
happen sooner or later.
Like I said,
public service homicide.
Well, boys, I've got another
case I've got to attend to,
so if you don't need
any more hand-holding.
I'm gonna walk you out.
Unis think
they may have found a witness.
Night janitor.
They're bringing him over.
Jim, Mr. Winkler.
Sir.
No need for the formalities.
Call me Leon.
Leon.
We really appreciate
you stepping forward.
My wife Louisa always says,
if you don't step forward,
you step back.
She sounds like a smart lady.
Yes, she is.
So, do I
give a statement?
A description of the killer?
I'm not sure how this works.
Would you be willing to
come down to the precinct,
work with a sketch artist?
That really is the best
way to catch the killer.
It'd be a huge help.
Of course.
Thank you, sir.
Yes, sweetheart, I'm
still at the precinct.
I know.
Of course, yeah.
Well... okay.
They send in the sketch artist yet?
No, not yet.
Louisa, I have to go.
Bye-bye.
But you did see the killer, right?
Yes, that's what I
told the detectives earlier.
I'm sorry, who are you?
How the hell did this happen?
Security cameras inside
and outside the room
were turned off.
Ed, you got any
thoughts on the weapon?
What's strong enough to smash ships
but still fears the sun?
Can it with the riddles, Ed.
I don't have the patience
today or any day.
- Ice.
- Correct.
Gauging by the small
circumference of the wounds,
I believe the weapon is an ice pick.
Carbon steel, six inches long.
Driven in deep enough that it
marked the surrounding tissue
with an imprint of a
distinctive hexagonal handle.
It's not your standard kitchen fare.
Fun fact, gentlemen:
Mr. Winkler's wounds here
are the exact same as the wounds
on the victim from this morning.
The drug dealer? Littlefield?
Him. Same weapon.
Same killer, one would suppose.
Damn it.
Right in our house.
Okay.
What is your name?
You know who I am.
It's just a formality.
I...
like to be sure.
Bob?
Is that short for Robert?
You have any family, Robert?
Two lovely daughters.
I'm putting you down as Maria
Mercedes Mooney, aka Fish.
We'll be extracting a very
sincere apology from you today.
Shouldn't take too long.
How old are your girls, Robert?
I bet you they're some
ugly little creatures.
Now, come on, Fish.
No call for rudeness.
Only my friends call
me Fish, darling.
And you and I,
we're not friends..
Yet.
Sync and corrections by: KDragon
www. Addic7ed. Com
Gotham SO1E13
Original air date 26/01.
You go get him.
I got to find the keys
to the incinerator.
Marco.
Where's... Fish... Mooney?
How is anyone gonna trust
us to keep them safe?
We can't protect people
in our own house.
Upside is the place is
crawling with criminals,
so we got beaucoup
suspects to choose from.
That's an upside?
Security cameras were turned off.
Could've been a cop.
Probably was.
You do not even think
something like that.
The second that those guys
out there hear that
you're looking at a cop,
they are gonna turn on you.
Bullock's right;
You start pointing fingers,
you could jeopardize
your reinstatement.
You need concrete
evidence to even think
of accusing another
officer of murder.
I'll start with the
guard duty logbook.
Jim... Winkler was my witness.
No way I'm letting this ride.
I asked him to come in here;
I'm gonna find his killer.
No matter who it is.
Proceed with caution.
Yes, ma'am.
No big moves without my say-so.
I do believe
this is the second time
we've been around this block,
Master Bruce.
Selina likes to hang out here.
It's worth doubling back.
Besides, you got what you wanted.
I went out of town like you asked.
For weeks.
Yeah, well...
it wasn't safe here, was it?
The assassins weren't after me.
They were after her.
Yeah, and we'll be back
on that plane straight back to
the bloody Alps the
first sign of trouble,
I tell you.
Master Bruce.
Master Bruce, get
back in the car now.
Can we walk around
the block just once?
Then I'll get back in the car.
Please, Alfred.
Once around the block and then home.
Thank you.
Got the rest of your life
like that to get whipped
into a frenzy by the females.
I don't know why you
want to start now.
It's not like that.
Out of my way.
Ivy?
Steady, Master Bruce.
Looks like she's got the mange.
Look who it is.
Billionaire Bruce Wayne.
Who are you, his bodyguard?
If needs be, miss, yes.
What's in the bag?
It's for Selina.
Have you seen her?
Sure. I can give it
to her if you want.
Perhaps you could pass
on a message for me.
Tell her I'm looking for her.
20 bucks.
Alfred.
There we are, miss.
Delightful friends you
have, Master Bruce.
Home.
That's all you got?
You are gonna bore
me to death, fella.
That's impressive.
Different strokes?
You know, me,
I can't stand hot spicy food,
but my wife, you know, she loves it.
Hotter the better.
Now where, where
are we gonna begin?
Now, taking off a hand,
that's devastating.
But I've found
that taking out a knee...
You okay, Fish?
A page is missing from this logbook.
Now, that in and of itself
is grounds for dismissal
from the force.
So my question to you is
who was on guard duty
outside of interrogation
this morning?
No idea, man.
Nobody's talking.
They're protecting their own.
Or they just don't like you.
Face it, Harvey.
Leon Winkler's killer is a cop.
Not proven.
Come on, you know these guys.
You've known them since way back.
Give me some leverage.
Give me an angle.
You really want to
work with a murderer?
Somebody gets whacked in the GCPD.
Somebody's gonna get fired for this.
Not me, pal.
Grover.
We got a reliable guy
says it was you pulled the page
from the guard duty logbook.
No way.
Where did you get that?
- Who said that?
- Alvarez.
If he said that, that
son of a bitch is lying.
Why would he lie?
Look, six years ago,
I had a thing with his wife, okay?
Six years ago.
He is a vindictive bastard.
Well, look, that's none
of our business?
Look at it from our point of view.
We got to find the culprit.
Brass demands one.
But it wasn't me.
Then who was it?
Delaware? Anybody seen Delaware?
Saw him go to the garage.
Delaware.
You're gonna regret that.
You were guarding interrogation
this morning, weren't you?
Screw off.
Jim.
What the hell are you doing?
You couldn't bring
him in here quietly,
put him in some back room?
You making some kind of statement?
Damn right I am.
I warned you and you didn't listen.
I have evidence: The same drugs
I found in Littlefield's shoe
at the crime scene
yesterday morning.
That evidence is part of an ongoing
undercover narco investigation.
You expect us to believe that?
Jim, narco's been knee-deep
in the Uptown drug trade
for months.
I've got a matrix of undercovers
that have put their lives
at stake for this investigation.
Your little stunt
gets out, you unravel
the whole operation.
Not to mention, the
search was illegal.
So we're ignoring Delaware's
involvement in Winkler's death?
Is that what we're doing, Cap?
No. But this isn't the way, Jim.
I'm turning over the
case to Internal Affairs.
I.A.?
Two old drunks in the basement.
You and Bullock
are no longer investigating
the Winkler murder.
What about the Littlefield murder?
Or, wait, is that also
a part of an ongoing
narco investigation?
All you, buddy. Let me
know if you need any help.
I'm sorry about the confusion.
Can I help you with something?
Did you know, Miss Kringle,
that the earliest greeting cards
dated back to Germany in the 1400s?
I have a lot of work to do.
This is for you.
Doesn't say anything weird, does it?
No, ma'am.
Take it easy.
I'm fine, Butch.
Here, try this.
You okay?
I'm starving.
You are one tough cookie.
Thank you, Butch.
Listen, we should hit the road.
I figure we've got about
an hour before Falcone...
I'm not going anywhere
until I find Penguin.
He's the one that told
Falcone about Liza.
Boss, I
don't know if you remember,
but as of last night,
we don't have any men.
Falcone's gonna have the
whole city looking for us.
I'm not going anywhere
until I cut Penguin's throat.
One... two... three.
What do you think, Mother?
It's beautiful.
So classy.
Like an opera house.
A chandelier.
Like home.
Someone left a scarf.
It's beautiful with my dress.
Finders keepers.
And now you are in
charge of this club?
Spoiled my surprise.
No. No, no, liebchen.
No, don't be angry. No.
Such good news.
My boy has a club.
Will have a club.
There's still a few
loose ends to tie up,
but... soon it will be mine.
I am so proud of you...
I could spit.
Listen, Jim, there's
something I got to tell you.
A few years ago,
Flass and his people
started busting drug dealers,
taking over their stash houses,
running them themselves.
Now?
You tell me this now?
Look, I respond to
crises as they arise.
I'm not a forward planner like
you. I didn't tell you then
because I didn't want to
get you all riled you up,
but I'm telling you now
because I want you to stop.
Flass is protected.
By who?
Serious people.
Really high up. Big money.
For all I know, the
commissioner gets a piece, too.
You mess with Flass, you can
forget going back to Arkham.
These guys
do not play.
These stash houses-
think you can get me
a location on them?
Did you not hear a word I just said?
The stash houses could give
us evidence linking Flass
to Littlefield's murder.
We nail him for Littlefield,
we can nail him for Winkler.
I can't let it be, Harvey.
You should know that by now.
Mick, it's Harv.
You know that thing you
and Donnie were working on?
The Flass thing?
I need your help.
Prime spot for a stash house.
Yeah.
Delaware,
hand over the boxes.
You don't learn, do you?
Get out of my face.
No need to
rough each other up, gentlemen.
I got a warrant.
Giving us the legal right
to search and seizure.
Seems this warehouse was
being used as a home base
by the Uptown Assassins.
You expect us to believe you got
a signed warrant to clear
your own stash house?
On the commissioner's request.
Signed by Judge Bam-Bam.
Guess you don't have
a leg to stand on...
homicide.
- So what's our next step?
- Next step?
We got nothing to tie Flass
to the drugs or the murders.
Murder.
Just one.
Internal Affairs just ruled
Winkler's death as a suicide.
They're releasing the body
to his wife.
Leon was so very happy.
This just can't
be right. Can't be...
A suicide?
He stabbed himself in
the back with an ice pick?
That's absurd!
A ruling this quick means
the commissioner was involved.
Screw the commissioner.
Going forward with this
puts all of our jobs at risk.
Look,
I want to help you, Jim.
There are people here in
GCPD who want to help you.
- So why don't they?
- They have.
I have.
And we learned the hard way.
With men like Flass,
you need more than words.
You need results.
And that's not gonna
happen this time around.
So do us all a favor and move on
to the next vic.
Please.
Where you going?
Back in an hour.
Listen to this. This is classic.
Stop it. Come on.
Come on.
"Dear Miss Kringle,
"your eyes are as green as a meadow.
"Your smile is as bright as the sun.
"Your skin is as white
as a snowflake.
It seems like your life is fun."
Really?
It's the writer himself.
It's a real piece of
work you got there, perv.
I wouldn't quit your
day job if I were you.
Roger, dodger.
- Roger, dodger?
- Stop it.
What a creep.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
One, two, three. One...
Now... now you are getting it.
You are so graceful
for such a big man.
Isn't he graceful, Oswald?
Yes, Mother.
Jim.
Welcome.
Come in.
Another handsome man at the party.
I am so lucky.
This is Jim Gordon,
the detective friend
I was telling you about.
So nice to meet
a friend of Oswald's.
I am Gertrud Kapelput.
Nice to meet you,
too, Mrs. Kapelput.
Mother,
Jim and I have very important
- business.
- No.
Sad. How sad.
A little soon
to be celebrating, don't you think?
Well, don't just stand there.
Sit.
This won't take long.
I insist. Sit.
I'm so very glad you
called, Jim Gordon.
It's been far too long
since we've seen each other.
I was beginning to think
you'd forgotten about me.
I need a favor.
Do you know anything about
a narcotics detective by
the name of Arnold Flass?
I've heard the name.
I'm investigating him
and his crew for murder,
but I've hit a wall.
He's too well-connected.
I figured since
Maroni runs the drug trade,
maybe you could find somebody
with the goods on Flass?
But...
Say no more.
Favor is done.
I'll make some calls.
And what do I owe you in return?
Friends don't owe friends, silly.
They just do favors
because they want to.
Because they're friends.
- Nobody gets hurt.
- Of course.
No one gets hurt.
Champagne.
Dear me.
What happened here?
Call Falcone.
No kidding.
Thank you.
Thank you, boys. Lovely.
No. I-I am dancing still.
- You may go.
- Why you make them go?
Gabe, on your way to
help my dear friend Jim,
could you be a gentleman
and take Mother home?
Sure thing, boss.
Come on, Mrs. K.
A palace.
My boy has a palace.
Such a good boy.
Don't worry.
I will be back.
Ladies and gentlemen, friends,
celebrities from around the world,
my name is Oswald Cobblepot.
Here we are at last.
It is with deep and sincere pleasure
that I bid you welcome to
the official grand opening
of my newest night spot, the...
Not bad.
I do believe you need
to project more.
Just to create a bit more
excitement for the audience.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Fish Mooney's!
Like that.
What kind of
weirdo plays chess with himself?
Don't you have a butler to do
that kind of stuff with you?
He's making lunch.
I got your message.
I'm glad you're safe.
Alfred made me go out of town.
Switzerland. We have a house there.
Chalet, I guess.
A chalet?
It's basically a house.
Why did you want to see me?
We're friends, aren't we?
You've been driving
around looking for me,
sending messages. What's up?
I got you a present.
It looks like the town we stayed in.
Thank you.
Also, I wanted to know if,
if you wanted to stay here
in my house.
Why?
I figure we can help each other out.
You can help me find the
man who killed my parents,
and I can give you a
better place to live.
What's better about it?
Listen kid... chill.
I came here to tell
you to stop hassling me.
Hassling you?
Yeah.
You're beginning to bug me.
I thought we were friends.
Listen, I lied.
I... didn't see who
killed your parents.
I didn't see his face.
I don't understand.
I lied so I wouldn't
get locked up in juvie.
So it's no use
buying me presents or
sending me messages
or trying to hang out.
There's no point because
I can't help you.
Pinky Littlefield was
light two weeks running.
If you don't pay up,
there's consequences.
Flass killed him to send a message.
But please, please! I
swear that's all I know.
You sure?
I swear, man, I swear!
I believe you.
But I think I'll need
something a bit more tangible.
No, no, no! Please, no!
No! No! Please, no!
I swear, man! I swear!
How are you liking
show business now?
Please, Miss Mooney.
You're making a mistake.
I beg of you, let me speak.
I know we've had our differences.
We could combine our forces.
Think how'd we fool everyone.
Me... work with you?
I found you.
I made you.
When you walked in here, you
were a sad little wannabe.
Remember that, Butch?
You were so afraid.
Shook like a leaf in fall.
You're a servant.
An umbrella boy.
You're... a nobody.
This nobody still
outfoxed you at every turn.
I was working for
Falcone the whole time!
And you didn't have
the sense to see it!
Hello.
Seems like Mooney's is
the place to be today.
Come on, come on!
No! Come on!
Go, go, go!
Here.
You got to go!
I'll slow them down.
- No, no!
- Go!
Hello again.
Where is she?
What do you think, girls?
Should we kill him...
or should we take him
home to play with?
Mr. Nygma?
Miss Kringle.
Am I interrupting?
Yes. I'm surgically
removing the onions
from my takeout, so
if you don't mind...
Mr. Nygma, I owe you an apology.
I didn't give
Arnold the card.
He found it in my desk.
He has a strange sense of humor.
I thought your card was...
very...
thoughtful.
I guess.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
Miss Kringle, would you...
No, no, no, no, no. Please,
don't say anything else.
Just, please.
There's hope.
What's this?
Murder weapon and a tape of
Delaware rolling on Flass.
Smart cookie, that one.
Flass gave him the ice
pick to throw away.
Delaware kept it in case
he had to cover his own ass.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Master Bruce?
She was lying.
I see.
Shall I get a broom, then?
Or would you rather continue crying
over the shattered
fragments of your...
young dreams?
Yes, Alfred.
A broom.
Very good, Master Bruce.
I'll find other leads.
No doubt.
I knew she was a wrong 'un.
Arnold Flass.
You're under arrest for
the murder of Leon Winkler.
Keep walking, mutt. You got nothing.
That's 20 years upstate right there.
Delaware gave you up.
Jimbo...
you really think these guys
are gonna let you arrest me?
These are my friends.
This is my house.
This is not your house.
You're a drug dealer and a murderer.
You don't belong here.
You don't deserve the badge.
You believe this crap?
How long you been here?
A few months?
Why don't you come preach to me
in five years?
He murdered Leon Winkler,
an innocent man who trusted us!
Who trusted this.
Enough to step forward
and help us solve a case.
A man who died so Detective Flass
could protect himself.
I.A. ruled it a suicide.
I'm arresting this man.
Get real, dumb-ass. I'm protected.
You can help me
or you can try and stop me.
Either way,
I'm doing my duty.
Back off, all right?!
I'm protected! Get out of here.
Shut up, Flass.
Arnold Flass, you're
under arrest for murder.
The hell do you think
you're doing? Are you crazy?
Read him his rights.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and
will be used against you...
You can't keep me in here!
You know how many people I got?
Thanks, Cap.
Here.
So what's the plan?
I'm gonna leave town,
lay low for a while.
Then I'm gonna come
back and kill Penguin
when the time is right.
Listen,
you know I have your
best interests at heart.
- Don't come back.
- No.
You will see me again.
And in the meantime, do me a favor.
Find Butch.
And if he's alive, help him.
I will.
See you soon.
Be good.
Always.
Good night.
Night, Detective.
Yo.
That big guy visit you?
Give you the package I sent?
Yeah. Thanks. That was...
Yo, this... so this
means we're even?
I ratted out Flass like you wanted.
So now you back off, right?
Nothing more is gonna
happen to my wife?
She's safe? My family's safe?
I don't understand what
you're talking about.
Okay, okay, no worries.
Look,
never mind I pressed.
I won't say nothing to no one.
I'll-I'll pretend this
conversation never happened.
Okay? Just...
keep my wife and kids out of it.
I'm-I'm begging you.
Please.
Please! Please!
Sync and corrections by: KDragon
www.Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net