- Previously on gotham...
- I've been sober for a year.
That doesn't erase
the things that I did,
But I still care about you.
"dear jim, I thought I could be
"strong and brave for you,
"but I can't.
"I'm going away for a while
To get myself together."
Trust me, and I'll trust you.
In the meantime,
Each of your tariffs
will increase 25%.
Reach out to saviano
and turski.
They are worried about
ending up like bannion.
The old man is herding
his sheep toward me.
Arrogant clown.
Try to take
me down?
You do not know
where the edge is.
Arkham asylum?
Security guard for nut jobs?
It's that or quit.
So quit.
That's what they want me to do.
Falcone, the mayor...
I'm not gonna stop, harvey.
I'm gonna get 'em.
If thou neglect'st
or dost unwillingly
What I command,
I'll rack thee with old cramps.
Fill all thy bones
With aches,
Make thee roar
That beasts shall
Tremble at thy din.
Go, go.
No.
Pray thee.
I must obey.
His art is of such power...
Such power...
"it will control my dam's god."
It would control
My dam's god setebos
And make a vassal of him.
So, slave, hence.
Hence.
♪ Full fathom five ♪
♪ my father lies ♪
♪ of his bones are coral made ♪
♪ those are pearls ♪
♪ that were his eyes ♪
♪ nothing of him ♪
♪ that doth fade ♪
♪ but doth suffer a sea change ♪
♪ into something ♪
♪ rich and strange... ♪
Oh!
Get back!
Get back.
Yah! Yah!
Ha!
Don't kill me!
Stay down.
This is the fourth inmate
outburst in as many weeks
As you've been stationed here.
I understand
this is
Punishment duty for you,
But I expect professional
standards nonetheless.
This is unacceptable,
gordon.
Unacceptable.
It's my fault,
mr. Lang.
The play was
too upsetting.
We'll stick to comedies
from now on, I think.
Thank you,
nurse duncan.
It's "director" or "dr. Lang,"
As you prefer.
Recreational
activities
Are not pertinent
to this conversation.
Officer gordon
is responsible
For security
on this wing,
A task which he seems
unable to manage.
What have you to say
about this, gordon?
This man needs
medical attention.
I'd see to him myself,
But there's rules.
I dispense meds, not treatment.
He needs a doctor.
Very well.
I'll send one in.
Any more
incidents,
And I'll have you placed
on the remedial duty roster.
Think you can't fall
any farther?
Think again.
How is he?
He's fine.
Will be.
And you?
I'm good.
Few bruises.
What?
You're the famous
Detective jim gordon,
aren't you?
That's my name.
I'm not sure about "famous."
Notorious, then?
Nearer the mark.
Who are you?
Leslie thompkins.
Dr. Thompkins.
You work here?
I'm not an inmate.
I haven't seen you
on infirmary duty before.
I work in the female ward.
I come over here
when they're short-handed.
All the girls
are talking about you.
Brave detective brought low
By fighting city hall.
Ah.
They say that, do they?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to make light of your situation.
It's okay.
Personally, I think
what you're doing is admirable.
I'm guarding lunatics.
No. You're not quitting.
Not yet.
Who are you?
Oh, sorry.
I didn't mean to blurt
all that out like I did.
It's none of my business.
Uh,
dr. Thompkins,
You sure this inmate's
gonna be okay?
He's fine.
He's just sleeping off his meds.
I'm trying.
Get a room, you guys.
I should go.
It's nice to meet you, jim.
Likewise.
Ivy?
How you doing?
I... I'm good.
I'm good.
You look sick.
Like you need a doctor.
No doctors.
N... Never, ever again.
I-I'm fine.
I-I was resting.
I got a place we can go, ivy.
Come on.
I-I-I, I'm
shivery is all.
Okay.
Come on.
They're gone.
It's safe.
Sure?
Sure as sure.
We'll only stay until
you feel better.
Come and lay down
on the couch there.
Wh... What if the real
people come home?
There's dust on
everything
And something
smells rotten.
Nobody's
coming.
Whose place is
this, anyways?
How come you ask so
many questions, ivy?
I'm trying
to help you.
Now lie down
and I'll get
you a blanket.
Morning, gentlemen.
Have you considered
my proposition?
Uh, yeah.
No.
No?
We already pay enough.
Don maroni set the rates
last year.
And now I'm raising
the prices.
Inflation is a bitch.
Maroni said...
Maroni, maroni....
You're beginning to irk me.
You're talking to me,
the penguin.
So you're penguin.
So what?
I called the cops on you.
It's the penguin.
And that was a very
naive call to make.
Hello, we own the cops
on the waterfront.
Tell that to the cops, buddy.
Boys.
Why the frowns?
Jones?
Jones.
Hey, frogman.
Hey.
These are electrode wounds.
This man was
given a crude,
Invasive kind of
electroshock therapy.
Metal needles were
inserted into the brain
And electricity was applied
to his frontal lobes.
What for?
Surgically, it's used
to modify aberrant behavior,
But in this case, way
too much voltage was used
And his brain is
completely fried.
Another under your watch,
gordon?
How did this happen?
You rushed
into opening,
And now you're
running this place
With skeleton staff
and zero surveillance
In an unsafe and unsecure
200-year-old maze.
Excellent. Excuses.
That's that nature
of municipal operations.
You inherit problems
And you use the resources
at hand to do with you can.
Well, our resources don't
stretch nearly far enough
To cover a criminal
assault investigation.
We should call the gcpd.
No, this is
an in-house medical issue.
He still breathing?
Well, yes, but he's
effectively brain dead.
What does...
He's still breathing.
Unaided.
For all official purposes, well,
He's still alive.
Keep him comfortable, doctor.
Officer gordon?
I want you
to find out which one
Of our charming inmates
did this.
I want a report
on my desk Friday.
Another day, another dollar.
Really? This is rather usual
And sinister, isn't it?
Yes.
So, who are we looking for?
What does it take
to pull this off?
Uh...
Some basic knowledge
of human anatomy.
Um, basic electrical skills.
A circuit board,
Some wiring.
Is that all?
And the door keys, of course.
"the door keys."
Right.
No, man, I got
my keys right here.
Look at me, steven.
Look at me.
Tell me the truth.
Why you picking on me?
There's five other guards
with keys to this wing.
True, and you're
the only one who looks
And smells like a hunted animal.
Look, steven.
Whoever fried frogman had keys.
Now, we've searched
all the inmates' cells.
No keys.
But I know they're out there.
And I need to know where.
I'm backed up
against the wall here.
And I'm starting to lose my
patience... do you understand?
That fight... During the play.
Right after, I noticed
my keys were gone.
You lose equipment,
that's a big deal.
They dock me a week's pay,
so I tracked done a spare set!
Who took the keys?
I don't know.
Anyone could've taken them.
Walk away.
Sorry...
Walk away!
And then he raises our taxes
After his money blows up.
Killed bannion like
he was nobody.
I'll say it.
I wish something would happen
to old man falcone
Before he comes after one of us.
That's where this is going.
Slow down. Now, let's imagine
God forbid anything
happened to falcone.
Just for kicks...
Who would take over then?
Who would take over?
I do.
You?
Now, that never occurred to me.
What never occurred?
I'm next in line. Seniority.
That's the way the system works.
That's how the system used
to work back in the day.
It's a new dawn,
a new city.
I would believe we would need
Some fresh thinking at the top.
And who is the fresh thinker
that you got in mind?
Let me guess.
Who?
Her.
She's talking about her.
Oh.
Really?
You don't think
I could run the family?
Hey, no, why not?
Woman's lib and all that.
But fair play,
jimmy is next in line.
Well, there's no need to argue.
It's all hypotheticals anyhow.
We're just talking, right?
Inmate 5075 jack gruber.
Inmate gruber?
Did you take
officer wenger's keys?
You're looking into
the sad demise of the frogman.
The frogman disrupted
your play last night.
Yeah.
You didn't like him
very much, did you?
Well, I had no
opinion of him.
He was called the frogman
because he believed
A giant bullfrog lived
inside his abdomen,
Controlling his thoughts.
He was already dead.
I don't waste psychic energy
on the dead.
Rape, murder...
You're no stranger
to violence, gruber.
Your psych evals say
you're a grade-a sociopath.
Why should I take your word
for anything?
You shouldn't believe
everything you read, jim.
May I call you jim?
Did you take the keys?
Please,
Search my cell if you do
not find me trustworthy,
But, no, jim, I did not
take anyone's keys.
Thank you.
Guard?
Did you take
officer wenger's keys?
No.
Hey. Hey!
Settle down.
S-settle down.
- Settle down.
Did you take off...
You have the keys?
Get the straps!
Need a restraint!
Keys?
Yes.
Keys. Did you take
the guard's keys?
No. Am I in trouble?
No, aaron,
Unless you're lying to me.
Lying?
Aaron never lies,
Mr. Gordon.
He doesn't have the concept,
Poor peaceful soul that he is.
He killed his family
with an axe.
Isn't that
what you did, aaron?
Never harmed a fly before
or since.
I said sorry.
Okay, aaron.
You're free to go.
Thank you. Guard?
You saw how that went.
Saviano's the problem.
Now, on his own, janacek,
I can turn him around.
And the junior capos
will follow him.
But that saviano,
we got to deal with him
Before we make our move
on maroni.
Why not let me talk
to saviano
On my own?
Me and jimmy go way back.
That's true. You do go way back.
What would you tell him?
I'd say you're
the best candidate.
He knows that.
He just can't admit it
to your face.
Too proud.
Okay then.
Talk to him.
Will do.
Butch,
You're not turning on me,
are you?
Ho!
What kind of question is that?
Why would you even joke
about something like that?
I'm just asking.
A girl gets insecure
once in a while.
Royston, what are you doing
out of your cell?
Hey, cut it out!
Full fathom five
thy father lies.
Of his bones are coral made.
Aw, hell.
Royston,
is that your name?
Sea nymphs hourly ring
his knell.
Fascinating.
The poor man can walk and talk,
but all he remembers are lines
From the play.
Same electroshock technique
As frogman but with slightly
less drastic results.
It's like whoever's doing this
is improving their methods.
Or maybe their process
is so haphazard, they don't know
What kind of outcome
they're gonna get.
One man ends up
a vegetable,
While the other one
recites shakespeare on a loop.
I don't understand
what an inmate gains
From scrambling up
another inmate.
You should stay
on the female wing for a while.
There's no reason
to put yourself in danger.
I'm perfectly capable
of protecting myself.
Besides, my patients need me.
There's gonna be some drama
around here.
The missing keys
Made me focus on the inmates,
But I think it's a misdirection.
I think I should be focusing
on the staff.
Oh. I see.
There will be some drama.
But, wait, I'm staff.
What if it's me?
It's not you.
How can you tell?
You're not the type.
Cop skills, huh?
You can read people.
Some people.
A staff member?
That's absurd.
It was an inmate.
I don't think so.
Your job is to oversee
inmate security.
You're not authorized to
conduct an investigation
Of the staff.
Whoa. You're trying
to force my hand.
You want me to
call the police.
No.
I already called 'em.
Barbara, you need to wake up.
Morning.
I got you coffee.
Mmm, extra sweet.
You always remember.
Yeah.
Have you spoken to jim recently?
Why would I?
Renee, you don't
Have to be jealous of jim.
I'm over him.
This was a mistake.
What was?
This. Us.
I should have never let it
go on for this long.
I'm s... I'm sorry.
Oh, I-I see.
Look, barbara...
No. No. I mean, you're...
No, you are absolutely right.
This-this was a mistake.
This has been a really
long process for me,
And I've worked too hard
to get right with myself.
I-I wanted this to be good,
but I can't fall back now.
The drinking,
the drugs.
We're toxic together,
you and me.
Please, renee, stop.
There's no need
to say another word.
I am sorry that I interfered
with your process.
Barbara,
you need help
I can't give you right now.
Let me call jim
For you, please.
No.
Where's my purse?
You don't need
to go. Stay here.
Take time to get yourself
together. I'll go.
I am perfectly together,
thank you.
I am just toxic, that's all.
Now, where's my damn purse?!
Barbara, stop.
Calm down, please, all right?
I'll go.
Please.
Fine.
Do what you want. Go.
I'm sorry...
Just go.
Hey, pal.
In a cow slip's
bell I lie,
There I crouch
when owls do cry.
All right.
I can dig that.
Detective...
Jim!
Partner. Mwah!
Let me take
a good look at you.
Lord have
mercy, a screw.
Excuse me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, you weren't exaggerating.
Freaky as advertised.
Nobody of authority
called on you, sir.
This is not a police matter.
You must be
director dr. Lang.
See, I beg to differ.
This is third degree assault,
at the very least.
A friend of yours,
is it?
Egregious insubordination.
Your job here was already
hanging on a thread.
This is the end of your career
in law enforcement.
Count on it.
Whoa!
Take it easy,
hot shot.
Officer gordon did
the right thing.
Why wouldn't he
call the police?
Anyone would
think you'd want
To keep
this business quiet.
Gerry... It is
gerry, isn't it?
Now, did you do
this terrible thing, gerry?
That doesn't even
merit a reply.
No, I did not do
this terrible thing.
But you have the skill,
though, as a doctor.
I mean, you could do
it, lickety-split.
Now, why would I do this?
Why would anyone?
Exactly,
officer gordon.
Gerry, I think we're
gonna have to take you
Down to the precinct... you're
raising a lot of questions
That need clearing up in
a more formal setting.
Well, you can't
do this...
Sh-sh-sh-shush.
As of this moment, this is an
official gcpd investigation.
You, sir, will cooperate
or face arrest.
Would you mind going through
the, uh, staff records
While I take gerry, here,
downtown for a chat?
Will do, detective.
Sir?
Jimmy.
Butch.
Good to see you.
Come on.
Like old times, huh?
All we need is
a bottle of applejack.
What happened, man?
In my head, it's...
We're still kids, chasing
girls in harlow park.
Yeah.
We caught a couple
of hot ones, huh?
Especially me.
Thanks for
meeting with me.
What did you tell
your boss-lady?
I suggested I reach out
to you. She agreed.
Talk some
sense into me?
It's a new dawn.
Yeah, like that.
She's not wrong, you know?
City's changing.
You really want falcone's job?
Since we were kids, I
love you like a brother.
I love you, too.
Always. You know that.
I do, I do.
That's why
I trust you.
And that's why I say
to you with love...
Fish is doomed.
There's no way she gets the
chair. It ain't gonna happen.
She's a smart
cookie, but she's
Overreaching. I mean,
come on, butch, without
You and your crew,
what's she got?
Very little.
Everybody knows it. You know it.
Maybe.
What's it gonna take
to make you make a move?
What are you offering?
Name it.
Drop fish, come over to us.
The club... all the businesses
attached... they're yours.
That's day one.
A welcome bonus.
What else you want?
That's a good question.
Let me think it over.
Yeah.
Hey, brother.
Don't think too long, huh?
Detective bullock.
Wait here.
Penguin.
It's good to see you.
What are you guys doing?
Old friend.
Thank goodness you're here.
There's been some silly mistake.
Looks like it.
Unless you irritated
someone important...
You didn't do that, did you?
Me?
Of course not.
You sure?
Examine your soul, penguin.
Wait!
Don't go. Please, sir,
I-I beg of you.
My patron, don maroni,
is obviously
Unaware of my predicament.
A simple phone call would
Resolve things, I'm sure.
But, see, I like
having you here.
'cause I can sit at my desk
And look at you.
It's soothing.
Like a bonsai tree.
What's a
bonsai tree?
♪ ♪
So...
Did you see our friend?
I saw him.
And?
Eh.
I'm working him.
He's a stubborn cuss, that one.
Just give him a little time.
Time, hmm?
Okay.
He can have time.
Yeah.
I'm optimistic.
Good.
All right, doctor,
Pretend I'm an ignoramus.
Shouldn't be too hard, hmm?
Explain to me this whole crazy
electric needle business.
When a real doctor
like you does it,
What's it supposed to do?
Electroshock therapy
is a common procedure
For mood and behavior
alteration.
Like mind control?
Of a sort.
Blue sky experimentation
on humans
Is considered unethical,
So we know very little
of the hard science.
Okay.
But skilled
Surgeons can elicit
very specific responses.
Uh-huh.
But those inmates
Weren't treated
by a skilled surgeon.
You sure about that?
There are no
Skilled surgeons
amongst the inmates.
Or the staff.
You're a skilled surgeon.
What...
we've been over this.
I haven't opened a body
since med school.
I'm just messing with you.
I don't think
you're the man behind this.
No, you're not the
type to break rules.
Too scared of authority.
But you're hiding something.
What is it?
Well, everybody's
hiding something.
Don't play tag.
You're right, detective.
I am afraid of authority.
And the things I'm hiding?
I'll never tell you.
Sounds heavy.
Heavy?
Yes. And if you know
what's good for you,
You won't dig any deeper.
All right.
I don't want to hit
any power lines.
Don't have to
tell me twice.
No digging. Unless, of course,
It has something
to do with the case at hand.
Nothing.
Oh. Great, thank you.
Oh, you poor thing.
You look so pale.
Any joy?
Not so far.
The files seem to be incomplete.
I'm wondering if there's
more in the basement.
Blueprint says there's
a records office down there.
Oh, the basement's closed off.
Unsafe chemicals.
Nobody's been down
there for ten years.
Do you know the way down there?
All right,
suppose you had to pick out
One member of your staff
as the culprit.
Who would it be?
It wasn't a staff member.
Whatever. Just the first face
that pops to your mind.
Nobody.
They're good people.
I know them well.
They've all been with me
for more than five years.
We all came to arkham together.
Th...
Wait.
Hold that. You just
saw someone. Who was it?
Oh.
No, she couldn't..
She?
Who?
What's that?
Everybody's
in their cell.
Dorothy.
Jim, hi. What's up?
Hi, leslie.
We're going
on an adventure
To the basement.
Oh. Well, that
sounds fun.
Can I come?
No.
But...
Dr. Thompkins,
what did I tell you earlier?
You should go home.
Why? What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
Go home.
I don't understa...
Oh.
Whoa!
You okay?
I need you to find
the main entry guard,
Tell him to
hit lockdown,
Then get out of the
building, quick.
Okay,
Hit lockdown.
Get out. Will do.
- Yeah.
- Jim, listen,
Dorothy duncan isn't staff.
She's an inmate.
I know. Get over here now.
Leslie!
Guard!
Guard! Help!
Dr. Thompkins.
Jim, behind you.
Men!
Men! What the hell
Do you think you're playing at?!
Go back in your cells
Right now!
You hear me?
That's an order!
Remember, I'm a vegan...
no butter.
Yeah, yeah.
Hi.
Hi. I-is this...
Is jim gordon there?
Yes, he is.
But I'm sorry,
jim is kind of busy right now.
Can I take a message?
No.
No, that's okay.
I...
Who is this?
I'm a friend of jim's.
Who's that?
Go to hell!
M.E.'s got her
in the morgue.
When dorothy duncan was a
16-year-old nursing student,
She killed five kids
with poison candy...
For homework, she said.
She's spent over half
her life at arkham.
When the asylum closed,
there was chaos.
She must have just
hunkered down in the basement
Until it reopened.
Forensics is sweeping
the basement level
Looking for her lair.
Poor soul.
- What was she trying to do?
- Who knows?
Maybe she was just
trying to find a cure
for her own madness.
She was crazy.
Enough said.
It's good
to see you, jim.
And you got a win, huh?
Still fightin'.
Nice work.
Yeah, I don't think my boss
is gonna see it that way.
He's working for the king
of all cheese grinders.
It's a crying shame, cap...
we need to get him
back on the job.
You know I'd bring you back here
in a second... If I could.
I know.
It's all good, captain.
You do look spiffy
in the uniform.
Yeah, if spiffy
means dorky.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
How about a drink
for old times' sake?
Sounds good.
Penguin.
Hi. Sir.
Uh, don maroni.
Thank heavens you're here.
You look kind of frowsty.
Uh... Forgive me.
I've had nothing but
a moist towelette
Since yesterday morning.
A very sad picture.
You know why you're in there?
I have no idea.
A rhetorical
question.
You're in there
because I put you in there.
But, don maroni, wh-why?
What did I do?
Do you know what hubris is?
Do you know?!
Sorry.
I-I thought that was another...
Rhetorical...
Question.
Yes, I do.
H-hubris. It's when...
It's when
limping little
Chickenbutt second bananas
think they're hot stuff.
Sir...
When dumbass underlings
Raise taxes
without asking me first.
Yes, sir.
On fishermen.
You raised taxes on fishermen.
They're out there
in the freakin' ocean
Risking their lives
for us,
And you raise their taxes
without asking me?
That's hubris, my friend.
I'm sorry, don maroni.
Deeply... Sorry.
I will never do it again.
All right, then.
Hey, you.
Let my friends out.
Excuse me?
What, am I
Talking hungarian?
Open the cage, mook.
Come here.
Holy mother, you stink!
Let this be a lesson
to you, yes?
Yes, sir.
You're
a smart monkey...
But you're a monkey.
And I'm the zookeeper.
Yeah, you're all right.
Captain, you should see this.
Look here.
Dorothy duncan.
Electrode wounds,
Both sides.
Same gauge as the
other victims.
About a month old.
They were hidden
by her hair.
This is crazy...
how could she have done this
To herself?
She couldn't.
Not humanly possible.
Which means she
was just another victim.
She couldn't.
Aw, crap.
Hey, aaron.
What's up?
Hey.
Where'd you get those...
Hey!
Well done, aaron.
Exactly like I told you.
Oh, now you are my
best work so far.
Mm.
Hello, dr. Lang.
Lang?
Lang!
They're gone.
Get an ambulance.
- Go!
- Not...
Staff.
Don't speak.
Just breathe.
Breathe!
Gr... Gruber.
♪ ♪
Dear officer gordon,
Sorry I had to run.
I very much wanted to enjoy
A proper chat with you
before I left, but...
That's show business.
I've been practicing my skills
on these sad creatures
For a while now.
Electricity is
an amazing thing.
It can work wonders.
Nurse dorothy
was an early success.
This last time, I think
I finally got one just right.
Bravo to me.
But time to go.
It was nice to meet you... Jim,
And I hope to see you around.
All the best, jack gruber.
Barbara?
♪ ♪
How you doing?
Well. You?
Tip-top. Always.
So, what's the deal,
brother, are you in?
Yeah.
I'm in.
Ah,
That's my boy!
Name your terms.
You remember
when we were 14,
We stole all that meat
from satriani's?
Yeah, I do.
It was, like,
50 pounds of pork and whatnot.
Never seen my mom so happy.
Yeah.
Thing is, when
I was sharing it out,
There was, like, 15 pounds of
prime angus beefsteaks in there.
And I kept it all
for myself.
I didn't give you any.
Gave you all the cheap cuts.
I never knew that.
Yeah, it's been bugging me
ever since.
Hey, we're talking
a long time ago.
I want
to say I'm sorry.
I apologize for cheating you
out of your beefsteak.
Forget about it.
Nah. Nah.
Brothers don't do that.
Why did I do that?
Hey,
Forget about it...
it's okay.
Apology accepted.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net