My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
I wrote it for you.
It's so beautiful.
I have an electro-plasmic
Continuum Fingerboard.
Happy helped me build it.
Does Happy know about...
Us? In the broadest of terms.
So pretty much everyone
in the garage but my brother.
You said you want to tell him
yourself, but you know
Walter comes here
every Friday, right?
He sees
one Super Fun Guy comic,
he is going to know that we've
been spending time together.
So I'll just bring them all
to my apartment,
and you can read them there.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna
be leaving here less and less.
I thought
we were thinking positive.
Especially
with Walter's research,
you still got a good chance.
This morning I was told
that I won't get my braces off.
I'm never gonna walk
without them again.
I'm never gonna dance again.
Ugh, but, hey...
I have no time for regrets
and no time for secrets.
Don't be nervous.
He's gonna be fine with it.
You're right.
I will find
the right time and...
I will tell him.
Everybody! By the monitors!
Uh, hey...
Yeah, you... you look like
you're about to say something.
No? Okay, great.
Everybody by the monitors.
I'm Lorraine Arroyo.
Hey, that's the sign.
We had a chance to sit down
with the leader
and founder
of this remarkable team,
Walter O'Brien.
That's the garage.
I don't think it's a
coincidence, Sylvester.
197 IQ,
statistically one of only
four people on Earth.
Are you just always thinking
of amazing things?
When did you do a TV interview?
Well, I'm involved
in many projects simultaneously.
But when I use my intelligence
for the greater good,
that's when I'm most fulfilled.
This is the dramatic footage
of Walter O'Brien
saving the life
of a young boy who'd been
trapped in a sinkhole
on Zuma Beach.
I remember
all of us being there.
This is the jack that I used
to free the boy's foot.
- The jack I built.
- Is it fair to say
that boy was saved by genius?
Absolutely.
No. He was saved
by four geniuses.
And Cabe and Paige.
Is that arm
a little sore
from patting yourself
on the back?
But as brilliant
as he is, O'Brien chooses
to surround himself with other
highly gifted intellects.
Less so than himself, of course.
Math whiz Sylvester Dodd...
Statistical theoretician.
Tobias Curtis,
- psychologist...
- Psychiatrist.
Harvard-trained.
master fabricator
and genius electrical engineer,
Paige Dineen; and lastly,
what O'Brien termed
the team's supernanny,
Happy Quinn.
Pardon me while I go bury
my head in the dirt.
Is it that bad
being mistaken for me?
Although "supernanny" does sound
like I change diapers.
We're gonna be flooded
with work.
Given your astronomical IQ,
I didn't think it was necessary
to discuss the difference
between a psychologist
and an M.D.
I told them
you were a psychiatrist
and where
you trained.
It just got lost in translation.
A few things.
They're TV reporters.
You have to expect
some mild inaccuracies.
Can no one see the greater good
in this scenario?
It's great for the team.
It's great for you.
Your qualifications
were stated perfectly,
and the entire report was
a firmly gripped stroke
of your narcissistic egomania.
You didn't
tell them.
You didn't include them.
They only asked to talk to me.
I-I didn't even think
to ask you guys.
Exactly!
A fresh shovelful
of narcissistic egomania
onto the pile.
I did my job.
I got media coverage
for the team.
This is childish!
Hey!
We got a case.
That is Richard Elia.
Billionaire
tech mogul.
Yeah, I know who he is.
And his first impression
of us is that we're idiots.
My daughter Zoe.
10 days ago, she was kidnapped
by the La Plaga cartel in Mexico
while on a journalism
assignment.
They're an emerging drug gang.
Particularly violent.
They've killed before.
They left heads
in the street.
I'm sorry.
They're modern.
Tech savvy.
They like to show off
their exploits-- murders--
to other cartels
via social media.
That's Advertising 101.
New kids on
the block want
to make it known that
they mean business.
Publicity whores.
Been seeing a lot
of that lately.
How did an heiress
cross those guys?
It's trite,
but when Zoe turned 20,
she started saying that
I was a capitalist fascist
and guys like me
were the source of
all the world's ills.
And we didn't speak for months.
Ten days ago,
I get a call from her editor
saying she's down in Mexico,
wants to blow the lid
off this big drug cartel.
You want us to find her?
In drug cartel territory?
There are ongoing,
very sensitive
border sovereignty talks
between the U.S. and Mexico.
The last thing the State wants
is us sending in a paramilitary
group to rescue a citizen.
Well, they must know
who you are.
They know who Zoe is.
There must be a substantial
ransom; pay it.
- I did.
- $2 million via wire transfer.
As soon as they got it,
they called it a "down payment."
Then this morning,
they reached out
and asked for
another installment,
due in 10 hours, in cash,
delivered to coordinates in
the northwest Mexican desert.
I've had my best people working
on tracing their communications
and they hit wall
after wall.
But if you can
just locate her,
even the city that she's in,
I have contractors.
They'll go in and extricate her.
Do you have the, uh,
the wiring instructions
- for the ransom money?
- Yeah.
Can I see it, please?
Thank you.
Sly...
Yeah.
If you keep paying it,
they'll probably
string you along,
providing "proof of life"
videos of Zoe
in different clothing
and locations.
They'll probably be taken
over the next few days.
The likelihood is that
she'll be killed within a week--
keeping a hostage
is a liability.
But there's
no certainty of that.
Yes, of course.
Nothing is, uh, certain.
I did a sweep
of Mr. Elia's bank
and traced the routing
and re-routing.
The kidnappers made it
bounce between 15 countries,
but I am 97% certain
that your daughter
is somewhere near
Culiacan, Mexico.
Oh, my God.
You said they were good.
I'll have my men there
in four hours.
You will be well
compensated for this.
Mr. Elia?
Um...
Simply arriving at the airport
will not guarantee
getting your daughter back.
But I may be able to pinpoint
to the location
where she is.
But because of the time crunch,
we'll need to
split up, collect
the necessary technology
and then meet up
back in Culiacan ourselves.
I'm sorry, what?
If you can pinpoint
her location,
I'll double your fee.
Walter, can I have
a second, please?
Drug cartel territory?
You trying
to get us decapitated?
Or is this the,
uh, opportunity
to dazzle some deep-pocket
tech mogul with rich friends?
Yeah, this would fit in nicely
to your "PR at all costs"
campaign.
I have a plan; my plans work.
Because time is
of the essence.
The cartel's expecting payment
in a matter of hours.
If you do not want to assist,
it's your decision, Toby.
Wow, that's it...
your way or the highway?
Walter, that was a local
morning news show.
We have to move fast.
What is your answer?
How many jets do you have?
Two.
We'll need them both.
And $2 million, in cash.
♪ ♪
Please... don't.
It's just a little sunshine.
It's just a little reminder that
we are 36,000 feet in the air.
Explain how this works again.
Well, these holographic strips
are a fairly rudimentary
anticounterfeiting measure.
Right now, they are programmed
with information
that only contains
the denomination of the bill.
But these strips,
when originally manufactured,
had microscopic
solar cells implanted,
so they were charged
and programmed
with GPS tracking software.
It was a secret
government program to
track how money was spent.
We track these strips with GPS,
stick 'em in
Elia's cash,
the cartel picks up the money,
and then we've got a shot
to track them back to Zoe.
It's a smart
idea, Walter.
Butt kiss much?
Walt,
I have major concerns
that Cabe isn't with us.
Well, he's the only one
who can requisition the strips
from the Treasury Department,
Happy.
He will meet
us an hour
after we arrive,
the Mexican Federales
will escort us into town.
I can handle whatever comes up.
Even gunfire from drug warlords?
We're not going
to encounter that.
We program the strips;
we implant them
into the money;
and then the professionals
track down
the cartel and rescue Zoe.
Done...
and done.
Perfect. Great idea.
I'll be up front.
So I don't barf.
We've started our descent.
Buckle up, everyone,
and we'll be on the ground
in 20 minutes.
La Plaga has really been
consolidating their power
over the past year.
The gang runs rampant
and the population is terrified.
For good reason.
Fantastic.
I would lay low as best you can.
We will not be handling
any of the dangerous
elements
of this operation.
We'll be in the hotel
most of the time.
That's good.
Here we are.
Uh... what is this?
You are ten miles from town.
The bus comes on the hour.
Usually.
Uh... whoa, whoa, whoa!
This is crazy.
You can't just leave us here.
This uniform puts
a target on my back--
and on yours,
if you are
spotted with me.
Public transportation is safest.
Good luck.
Whoa, ho, hold on.
Hold on.
Okay, okay.
Well, you heard him.
It's safer this way.
Unarmed.
Carrying $2 million in cash.
I'd kill us.
Not to mention,
I didn't get a good vibe
from our escort.
I'm pretty sure I picked up
some deceit leakage.
Yeah, well, I'm picking up
paranoia leakage.
Looks like things
can't get much worse, huh, boss?
I've been trying to find
the right time
to tell you something.
That's an impossible
and inefficient goal.
If you have something to say,
then say it.
Guys, I don't think
this is the bus.
Uh, not good.
The money! Now!
Walter, I'm dating your sister.
♪ Scorpion 1x17 ♪
Going South
Original Air Date on February 23, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Well, this reporter
is stunned to convey
that in spite of
his stratospheric brilliance,
Walter O'Brien managed
to lead Team Scorpion
right into a buzz saw.
I have no idea
how they knew we'd be there.
You know that friendly Federale
who was so worried
for our safety?
He got paid off.
He's upset with me
because of Megan.
Or because he just got robbed of
two million dollars at gunpoint.
Si.
A room under O'Brien, por favor.
Un momento.
I did not set up
the federal escort.
We have eight hours
before that money
is supposed to be delivered,
or Zoe's life is over.
So we can fight later?
Tabled for now.
Hey, check it out.
Is that the first thing
you think of
when you think of Mexico?
The clock making?
Buenos Dias.
I got the GPS strips
and wired us up a car.
Why do you all
look like hell?
Where's the money bag?
You've got to be kidding me.
Your Federale, bro.
He's not my Federale.
He's fourth-generation CI,
handed down from Homeland.
Right. What department
of government do you work for?
The post office?
Can Elia replace the money?
Good luck finding
a bank near here
with two million American
dollars in small bills.
Just got off with Elia;
he's devastated,
but I convinced him
we can get it done.
Don't make me a liar.
How are we doing
with the wireless?
Just went up.
He also sent a file
to our secure e-mail.
It's a new video of Zoe.
Got it.
Dad...
if the money isn't delivered
to the coordinates
by 6:00 p.m. tonight...
That's today, in six hours.
We can't get the money in time.
Say it.
No.
I won't say that, okay?
He knows what executed means.
I don't need--
Say it, damn it,
or I'll kill you.
They said they'll send me home
in pieces.
Wait, if we can trace
the point of origin
of the file they sent Elia,
maybe we'll have the whereabouts
of their headquarters.
And then we can do the recon.
If we can locate her,
Elia's contractors
can extract her.
They're due here in three hours.
Ah, whatever server
this e-mail was sent from
has a 30-point encryption
key that changes
every three minutes.
So somehow we got to come up
with the correct 30 numbers
in three minutes
or it resets and we start over?
You're really learning.
I won't say that, okay?
He knows what executed means...
Ah, Sylvester,
that audio is boring
a slow hole into my brain.
But I...
But nothing.
Please, just change it.
Thank you.
You're right.
He might be upset with you.
He's gonna have to suck it up,
because I know this bird.
Aix sponsa, the wood duck,
here on its winter migration.
Uh-huh.
Well, it feeds on algae
specific to a shallow marsh,
but average flock size dictates
that the marsh
needs to be at least 60 hectares
to be a proper feeding ground.
Sylvester, you're insane.
The Aix sponsa's feeding ground
can be as little as 47 hectares.
60 is way on the high side.
You know this bird, too?
Not personally.
The point is how many
shallow marshes
are there in this general area
between 47 and 60 hectares.
What we need now
is satellite imagery.
Enjoy that coattail ride,
O'Brien,
because Sly figured that one out.
Really?
We have six hours to find Zoe,
and we're fighting about credit?
Found. Proper size marsh
with adjacent barn.
Let's hit it.
I just spotted
two sets of fresh tire
tracks heading out.
Most likely a pickup
and minivan.
Could've been a drop-off.
No telling how many people
are inside.
I'll check it out.
It's clear!
Oh, they absolutely shot
the video in here,
but I mean, we got nada.
We gotta come up
with some clue to where
they went, or we're out of here
in two minutes.
Time's wasting.
We got nothing out here.
You know, Sylvester has every
right to be upset with you,
but you seem upset with him.
He thinks it's because
he's seeing Megan.
You're not happy about it?
I'm not pleased.
La Fuente de Piedra.
The stone fountain, exciting.
No, but it is interesting.
According to local lore, it's
water ran red 200 years ago
when a conquistador drowned
his unfaithful wife here.
Or old clay pipes changed
the water color.
Either way, who cares?
That is the most famous
landmark in the city.
It was very specifically
positioned over Zoe's
shoulder in that video.
These kidnappers were smart.
They wanted us to see it,
but not make it too obvious.
See, not being from here,
we had no idea what it meant.
But after the cartel
screwed Elia
with the first ransom payoff,
They must have assumed
he'd hire local mercenaries
to come after them, and they
would know about the fountain.
Why would they lure us here if
they weren't planning an ambush?
You were saying?
Get down! Get down!
Get down, get down,
get down, get down!
Whoa!
Get down! Get down!
Okay.
What we're looking at are
motion-activated machine guns,
but we're all behind
stationary objects,
so we're safe, right?
Uh, well, we can't
stay here forever.
If we move, the gun shreds us.
If we stay, whoever's watching
us from those cameras
will eventually come and get us.
La Plaga set the trap.
They saw us here,
turned on that motion sensor.
Walter, you have a plan yet?
Just don't move; let me think.
Okay.
Paige! Paige!
Oh... Oh, God!
The fan's movement's
drawing fire.
Happy, how long can those drums
provide protection?
That steel's rusting thin.
One minute, tops.
Cabe, can you take out the gun
that covers
our half of the barn?
Shoot-out with a robot gun?
It's rotating
on a gate hinge.
Aim for the lag screw.
She'll be riddled
with bullets in a few seconds!
Paige, on three,
you get up and you run
in a straight line to me, okay?
No, I'm scared.
You should be. One...
two, three.
Go, go, go!
Ow.
Am I all right?
Well, you are.
I'm not.
Okay, what we need to do now
is carefully assess
our situation.
They clearly know
we're in town,
they know we're coming
after Zoe,
so we need to find
a new plan.
Anybody else looking
at the time?
We have two hours until the
money needs to be delivered.
It actually keeps
pretty good time.
Elia's contractors,
they backed out;
they won't come into the city.
Even armed mercenaries
are afraid of this place?
We have to get her ourselves.
How? We don't have
a location on her.
The welding on
the gun's hinge,
it's smart but rough-hewn.
I'm guessing local work.
How many metal workers are
in this town, you think?
Happy, no one will talk to you.
You want to find someone,
hit the street,
talk to the people.
I bet you they're
on our side.
They don't want the cartel
on their ass.
I grew up in
neighborhoods like this.
I can handle myself.
No, we stay here.
I will crack the encryption
on the e-mail sent to Elia.
We will find her.
In our timeframe,
that's nearly impossible.
There's another e-mail
from Elia.
Get down! Get down!
They were filming us--
the cowering Americans.
We unwittingly participated
in an advertisement
for the La Plaga cartel.
That was the whole reason
for the setup.
Social media promotion.
Okay, I'm gonna crack the code,
but I need all of your help.
Where's Happy? Happy?
Hola.
¿Habla ingles?
Do you know who made this?
It's beautiful work.
Are you kidding me?
Who are you?
A very embarrassed person.
What?
I got kidnapped
by a fourth grader.
Now who in America
is your family?
To pay the ransom.
Ransom?
Like the La Plaga cartel.
They kidnap rich Americans
and they make millions.
You will get me in good
with them.
I hate to burst
your bubble, kid,
but my dad owns
a failing body shop.
Maybe he can give you
a ratchet set.
This is not funny.
I'll shoot you.
Not with a gun
with no firing pin.
You are clearly a stupid kid,
a wannabe,
but if you move,
it's gonna get ugly.
I'm sorry.
I have no parents, no family.
I just need money.
Believe me, I've never done
anything like this before.
Clearly.
I'm up to 16 characters
on the encryption code,
but then...
I run out of time.
Zoe's running out of time.
She's right.
In an hour,
the thugs expect their money.
I'm getting worried.
Where the hell's Happy?
Where you been?
I... got kidnapped.
What?!
Kidnapped by who?
This guy.
He wasn't good at it.
Get in here.
Close the door.
Have a seat.
What were you thinking?
That I could find someone
who knows the cartel members.
The kid's harmless.
He was just trying to be
one of the big boys,
make a few bucks.
By abducting you.
Does he know
the cartel or no?
He knows the guys who made
that gun for them.
They're from the
same neighborhood.
Then bringing a known felon
back-- that was dangerous.
He's a good kid.
He's a criminal.
There's no way that he will
lead us to whoever has Zoe.
Actually, Walter...
I don't agree
with that assessment.
This groovy little gaming system
is anything but little.
It's tricked out with
voice command capability,
high-def graphics,
fingerprint
vibration technology
that'll enable you
to feel the kickback
of any virtual
weapon you fire.
But you can't experience
major league gaming
on a minor league
screen, so...
a high res, 85-inch TV.
All this and more.
This can be yours just for
playing "Give Up the Cartel."
You'll give me this?
Mm-hmm.
We got Uncle Sam's
checkbook, kid.
Just tell us where
the bad guys hang their hat.
I know you're torn.
You look up to those guys--
they got cash,
and they grab headlines.
But they do it
in a very evil way.
And deep down, I know you're not
anything like them.
I'm not sure I trust you.
You better be right, Doc.
Okay.
You don't trust us.
Here's how much we trust you.
You sit in here
and think it over.
We'll be next door.
We fresco?
Si.
How did it go?
He's considering.
I don't think this'll work.
Shocker.
The Genius King
doubts his underlings.
I'm not doubting you, Toby.
No. Just my plan.
Aren't you the one who says,
"We are our ideas"?
How about
we all stop fighting?
How about we wait
and see what happens?
I know what
would've happened.
He would've helped without
you bribing him.
You're biased because of your
own Oliver Twist upbringing.
Besides, what do you know?
According to the news,
you're just our supernanny.
You're playing with fire, Doc.
I'll be shocked
if it works.
It astounds me
that I have to remind you all
that I had a medical degree
from Harvard
before most people
have their driver's licenses.
Oh, really?
You went to Harvard?
You hardly ever mention it.
My point is, I am certain
that little urchin next door
will give us
the information we want.
He's gone.
And along with all
our I.D.s and our cash.
Told you it'd work.
Little bastard's fast.
He can't wait to give our I.D.s
to his cartel buddies.
From his fake gold jewelry
to his knockoff sneakers
that kid is dying to be
something that he's not.
And the best way to do that
is to curry favor
with the fellas
he so desperately
longs to join.
The metallic strips
we put in our cash
are working perfectly--
GPS signal is strong.
I can't believe he did this.
He's heading off the street,
into a tenement
about two miles from here.
If that's where the cartel is...
Hopefully, where Zoe is.
Sylvester, can you pull up the
schematics for the building?
You think there are county
registered blueprints
in a Mexican slum?
We need to study the layout
of that structure.
Best I can do is Bing maps.
Happy?
Three stories,
four units per floor.
13,000 square feet, tops.
There's a tricycle
in the courtyard.
There's likely
civilians in there.
And from what I can tell,
only on the bottom two floors.
Look what is wired
into the side of the building
on the third floor--
cables for
ambient light sensors.
They got the whole top level
lasered off.
So, if they're all
in their apartment,
they can tell if someone
steps on the floor.
We can't even
get to the stairwells.
This configuration most likely
leads to a central hallway,
and central hallways
have guards.
We walk around
the wrong corner,
we're dead, and so is Zoe.
If we can't see around the corners,
we'll see through the walls.
Sorry, Sylvester.
My souvenir.
Your souvenir...
contains
a light-receiving diode,
so when it's nighttime,
it doesn't chime
and wake everyone up.
We fire a laser pulse
into the wall
at the end of the hall.
The pulse scatters
in a million directions.
It bounces off
any object around the corner,
including possibly the guard,
who won't see it
because it's invisible
to the human eye.
The photons bounce off walls,
all the way back to that diode.
Which will be wired up
to my tablet.
The tablet's camera will
simultaneously send the data
to Sylvester's laptop
in the car.
I have to stay
in the car, alone?
Would you rather be
in the building
with the gun-toting
drug dealers?
Enough.
Go on, Walter.
The laptop will then read the configuration
of the photon bounceback
and give us a rough image
of what's around the corner.
It's easy,
so long as this diode works.
So whether we walk
into an ambush
depends on the craftsmanship
of a knock-off
motel cuckoo clock.
Effectively, yeah.
I will also need
some plumbing supplies.
We're about to enter
three stories,
about half a dozen
cartel members,
a dozen automatic weapons and
a few thousand rounds of ammo.
Not to mention that Paco's
already given them
our names and I.D.s.
Probably already seen this
morning's little news piece
and know exactly
what kind of untrained
non-mercenaries we are.
Well, no such thing
as bad press, right?
Yeah, well, we don't have
a chance in hell
unless we start working
together.
Forget working together.
We'll have to work magic.
Getting a girl
off the third floor
without stepping on
the third floor?
That's crazy town.
I'm still concerned
about the courtyard.
It has
a five-foot retaining wall,
which could possibly be
trapping us in a death box.
Courtyard is
the only way to do this,
so long as Happy
took care of her end.
When have I not?
Happy, don't question Walter.
Didn't you see the interview?
He's better
than us, remember?
Damn it! What about
a young girl's life
isn't registering with you?
You all had ideas on the plan,
it came together,
and now you need to be a team.
We better
get our heads on right,
or we're not coming
out of that building alive.
Yep.
Diode's picking up
the laser bounceback.
Sylvester, you getting this?
Receiving data now.
Getting an image.
There is a man
around the corner,
six feet tall,
sitting in a chair,
two yards in from the corner,
either a dust buster
or a gun in his lap.
Why would he have a
dust buster, potato head?
Shut it.
Oh, nice.
He'll be out for a while.
I take the east stairwell here.
You take the west.
It's not a dress rehearsal.
Be prepared.
Copy that.
Let's hit it.
Be safe.
You, too.
You sure about Sofia?
It's the most popular female
Hispanic name last two years.
Roll the dice.
Here goes nothin'.
Hey, scumbags!
Okay, he's out in the hall.
I know you're loving this.
Happy! Hurry the hell up!
I'm seriously outmanned!
I'm going as fast as I can.
It's okay-- we're gonna
get you out of here.
Happy? You there?
I lost communication.
While she just
waltzed right in?
You come into our home.
You try to take
what's ours.
Now you're gonna
die with pain.
You need to leave town
as fast as you can.
Now!
We gotta hurry up!
I can't hold them off
much longer!
Walter, how are you on time?
Because Cabe is in big trouble.
Happy, we're almost there.
Status?
I'm dangling a human being
by a bed sheet.
That is my status.
All right, Cabe,
we got her-- bug out.
Coming in three, two...!
One!
Everyone okay?
All right,
we gotta hurry.
Sylvester ever
get set up?
Just did it--
I'm on my way to the car!
Okay.
You messed with the wrong
group of people, my friends.
Before you do anything rash,
you should know...
You recognize that gun?
The motion sensor is calibrated
to not shoot anything
before the door,
but it will take out anything
that moves on the other
side of it.
And fortunately,
that's the side you're on.
I improved your gun.
You so much as move
a trigger finger, you're dead.
Lying puta.
I can see you're all scared--
that's good.
It means you won't
do anything stupid.
Like move again.
So here's
how this is gonna go down.
My friends and I are gonna walk
Zoe right out that door.
And none of you are gonna do
a damn thing about it.
You try to intervene,
it'll be the last thing
you ever do.
Come on.
They can't hurt you.
I've put a 24-hour battery
on the motion sensor,
so, for your sake,
I hope that you
and your men
are disciplined.
Now remember...
your nose does not itch.
Toby.
Coming.
That was really cool.
We should get a clear
signal in a few miles.
We'll call
your dad, okay?
Thank you.
Stop the car.
What? Why?
Just stop the car up there.
Give me your watch.
This is a $5,000 watch.
From the U.S. ambassador
to Paraguay.
The kid saved my life.
Sell the watch, buy a train
ticket, and move far away.
Gracias.
Okay-- vitals are good,
but you're still dehydrated.
So drink up over
the next few days, okay?
Dad...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry
about everything.
Um... we should, uh,
give them a minute.
Can I, uh...
So, um...
along the, um...
along the same lines of,
uh, reconciliation,
I wanted to, uh, apologize
for the whole...
interview thing.
I, uh, should
have made sure
that you were
all included.
Everyone.
Uh... I just
wasn't thinking.
Distance between family
is never good.
I don't like fighting
with you guys.
Yeah, I'm sorry
I was such a pip.
Ditto.
If we don't look out
for each other, who will?
Right?
I wasn't really fighting
with anybody, so I'm not sorry.
But I'm glad
everyone's made up.
Uh...
That was evolved of you.
So while you're in the spirit,
go talk to Sylvester.
Please--
he's dying inside.
Hey.
Why aren't I good
enough for your sister?
I know the obvious--
my stress, my anxiety, but...
I'm a good person.
Good should count
for something.
It hurts me.
Sylvester, you are, uh,
kind and generous
and a better human being
than I will ever be.
But I have spent a long time
preparing myself
for the fact that Megan
will very likely die.
My research isn't going
as fast as I had hoped for.
And I don't know
if I can save her.
Now, I can handle
the fallout.
But you are not designed
to process the pain
that you're gonna feel.
Getting close to her
is-is dangerous.
For you.
But she calms me, Walter.
She makes me feel
good about myself.
And I know there's risk.
But if there's one thing that's
worth the risk, it's her.
I'm glad she's found
such a good guy.
Oh, okay.
All right, buddy.
Hey.
Sylvester,
what are you doing here?
I got you something.
It's a cuckoo.
Slightly used.
I love it.
It's very subdued.
What are you doing?
You like to dance.
So I would be honored
if you would dance with me.
♪ ♪
Love those moves.
Oh, yeah.
Get up on this.
Sly, I can't.
Yeah, you can-- come on.
Come on.
I can't.
Put your feet on my feet.
Oh, God.
I got you.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
I'll support you.
I just want to
thank you...
again, before we leave.
Of course.
So what's all this?
I'm working toward
the Kármán Line Prize.
$15 million award for
aerospace development.
I actually know the
anonymous benefactor.
I'm on his board.
I can put in a good word.
Oh, I appreciate it.
I'd-I'd prefer to win
fair and square.
That shows integrity.
How'd you like to come
work at my think tank?
State-of-the-art equipment,
world-class labs.
I'd be insane not to try
and bring you in.
That's an incredible
offer, Mr. Elia.
♪ ♪
I'm happy here.
Okay.
But please think
about it a spell,
because you never know--
maybe you could
be even happier.
Thank you.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net