My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
Now that this
has happened between us,
we can't let it
confuse Ralph, you know?
Uh, you coming into Ralph's life
has been so important to him.
You know what I'm saying, Drew?
Walter.
What are you doing here?
You know why I'm here.
Because you've been
thinking about me.
What the hell?
Book.
Three words.
Dead Sea Scrolls.
Darn it, I knew
it'd be too easy.
Morning.
You look frazzled.
Thank you.
Grumpy, too.
Sorry, I didn't sleep.
I had a weird dream.
About what?
I don't remember the details.
That's unsurprising.
Our brains often
protect us
from disturbing dreams
by suppressing
our memories of them.
What does it mean when
you remember a dream vividly?
Means that we enjoyed it.
Hey, relax, you can play
charades with us--
it'll be fun.
Playing charades
with geniuses is never fun.
Come on, we need
fresh blood.
Okay.
Movie.
Three words.
Sleepless in Seattle.
See what I mean?
Cabe, charades.
I told you never again.
Besides, we got a case.
And this one's not
from Homeland.
CIA?
Their internal affairs division
intercepted an encrypted message
that was sent by someone in the
Agency's Los Angeles office.
They have no idea
what it contains.
A leak.
A leak...
that has given
classified information
to a very dangerous
foreign government.
Yemen.
Could be battle plans,
state secrets, or Intel
that could jeopardize
national security.
CIA wants you to find the leak
and recover whatever was given
to the enemy before it becomes
a potential catastrophe.
Why does one of the world's top
spy organizations need our help?
They can't use their
own encryption analysts
because the leak could be
anyone inside the agency.
Bingo.
No more games.
It's time to get to work.
This is a black box
combinatorial pointer tree
encryption algorithm.
So you can't get in?
No, I cracked it.
Guys.
Okay...
no names or markers
to identify the source
or recipients.
But we do have the text
of the message.
“A minute away from you
is a lifetime.
“I love you with all my heart.
“Soon we'll be together.
B.O.O.”
It's a love letter.
It's a code.
“B.O.O.” could be
“base of operations.”
Or “black ops officer.”
Or “boo,” like
a pet name.
Maybe whoever sent it
is in love.
Paige, I've read a lot
about espionage,
including every issue
of Robo-Spies--
definitely a
top-five comic
of the spy robot genre--
and “boo” is not how spies would
normally refer to one another.
They encrypted
and anonymized the message perfectly.
If they were to add sentimental
verbiage, it would increase
their odds of getting caught--
it would be illogical.
Love is illogical.
It's a code within a code.
But this has random text,
it could take
days to break.
So, to plug the leak,
we first go to the
L.A. branch of the CIA
and selectively profile to see
who would betray their country.
And once we have found them,
then we dive into their system.
How do we
profile those guys?
It's the Central
Intelligence Agency.
They have highly trained agents
and state-of-the-art technology.
Yes, but we have you guys.
Internal Affairs knows the leak
came from this CIA office,
but it could be anybody
in any division.
Division five--
psych ops,
division nine--
languages,
division 12--
skunkworks,
where we create
our classified technology.
But we have eight
more divisions,
plus field agents
and support staff
that also...
Shouldn't have mentioned
the technology.
Pen pick.
Looks like a pen,
but can pick any lock.
All I need is a paper clip.
Gecko hands.
For climbing walls.
Even those made of glass.
Catsuit not included.
Do you own a catsuit?
Wearable electromagnetic
bullet shield.
It won't dampen
concussive force,
but it does deflect the
path of a metal bullet
by up to four inches.
Which can be enough
to save a life.
Oh!
Can you do that
with a paper clip?
Field trip's over, kids.
We got work to do.
Hey, did you see that?
A woman who's pretty,
mechanically inclined
and nice.
Shut up.
I brought in our top agents
from around the world.
You'll have carte Blanche
to question them.
Send them home.
I'm sorry?
Your top spies, the ones
in expensive suits
who travel the world
on exciting missions.
They may be experts at
disguise, charming people,
chasing bad guys, but they
could never program the level
of encryption
that message had.
The leak isn't one
of the cool kids.
It's someone like us.
Someone who does the coding.
The grunt work
that makes them look good.
Where are the guys
with the faces for radio?
Our people.
Toby, you getting anything
from these guys?
Did they rush Mozart
when he wrote a sonata?
You got nothing,
do you?
Not a thing.
Humor me a sec.
What if the code
wasn't a code?
I mean, call me crazy,
but maybe
“soon we will be together”
really meant
“soon we will be together.”
If the leak was in love,
how would you profile him?
Well, for one thing,
love increases serotonin,
which means more
energy and alertness.
So I would eliminate those
three guys along the east wall.
They're exhausted;
no joie de vivre.
Probably married.
Has anyone here
recently lost
a lot of weight trying
to look good for someone?
Well, Tim, Leonard and Susan
have all dropped some weight.
Any vacation days?
Especially Fridays and Mondays?
What would that indicate?
Romantic three-day weekends.
Ever had one?
Kind of, yeah.
She left after one day.
Susan and Tim have taken just
four vacation days between them,
but Leonard's taken
five personal days
in the last
three months,
plus four sick days--
all on Fridays and Mondays.
Paige is right--
he is a man in l'amour.
That's all the information you
needed to make that assessment?
No, look at his nails--
he had a manicure.
Only one thing'll make a man
sit through one of those--
a woman.
So the guy's got
the hots for someone.
Doesn't mean he'd do
anything unlawful.
We need to talk to him.
Leonard...
you got a moment?
Yes, of course.
You're in trouble, Leonard.
We searched your computer,
we searched all your files.
Why would you be sending
encrypted forget-me-nots
to someone
in a hostile government?
Never heard of Hallmark?
I know my rights,
I don't have to help you.
We got your access card;
we read your magnetic code.
You've been making trips
to the CIA chem lab.
Internal Affairs is searching
to find out what went missing.
If we discover that you gave
dangerous materials
to foreign nationals,
you'll face treason charges.
Okay.
I did sneak out
some chemicals.
But it was just to give them
to an aid worker.
You're a CIA analyst admitting
to a major violation,
yet show no markers
of shame or embarrassment.
Why?
Because I didn't do
anything wrong.
Now, it's technically illegal,
but it's for a legitimate
humanitarian cause.
This is to help
poor people in Yemen.
What do the poor
need chemicals for?
Because of embargos.
Yemeni farmers can't get
these chemicals
to make basic pesticides.
Which means that
they can't grow crops,
which is why
they are starving.
Now, I-I got her two chemicals,
I was gonna get her one more,
so that she could save
millions.
If they are used
to make pesticides,
why can't she just buy them?
They're toxic--
they're tightly regulated.
And-and I would do
anything to help her.
We're in love.
Love is imaginary.
What's real are
those chemicals.
Which ones did you give her?
Phosphorus trichloride and
liquid trans-methyl propylaxine.
Now, the third one that
I haven't brought her yet
is O-ethyl methyphonic acid.
Combined, these chemicals
make pesticide.
They can also
be adjusted.
If you methylate
the phosphorus trichloride,
it forms methyl phosphorus
dichloride...
Which, when combined with the
liquid trans-methyl propylaxine
and the O-ethyl
methyphonic acid,
creates tiny particles.
Very deadly, easily aerosolized,
and completely different
from pesticides.
It's nerve gas.
What...?!
I-I-I didn't know that.
N-No, it's irrelevant.
Y-You guys have it all wrong.
Sima is a good person.
She targeted you, man.
That's ridiculous!
No, Sima is...
She's playing you.
She made you think that
she was in love with you
so you would give her
those chemicals.
You're wrong.
And if I'm not,
we can't stop her...
millions could die.
♪ Scorpion 1x14 ♪
Forget Me Nots
Original Air Date on January 18, 2015
Sync, corrected by StoneSub
CIA and Interpol are
checking Sima's background,
but so far they've got
nothing on a woman
that might be
making nerve gas.
All you need is a few teaspoons
to kill tens of thousands.
He took pounds of this stuff.
Yet we show him strong evidence
that Sima might be trying
to manipulate him,
and he's still blinded
by emotion-- I don't get it.
Love makes you do
crazy things.
That is why there are
so many songs written about it.
“Crazy Love”
by Van Morrison,
“Crazy in Love” by Beyoncé,
just plain “Crazy”
by Patsy Cline and Aerosmith.
Love is a semi-euphoric,
temporary chemical reaction.
Aw, how romantic.
What is that
under your shirt?
Nothing.
You stole
the CIA's electromagnetic
bullet shield.
The pretty science lady
gave me a prototype.
I guess she likes
the cut of my jib
and my understated
sexual charisma.
We don't need prototypes;
we need a plan.
Soon Sima will wonder why
she hasn't heard from Leonard,
she'll get suspicious.
Once that happens,
we won't find her.
Leonard's not cooperating.
He may not talk to us,
but we can make him talk to her.
We're gonna
keep looking into this,
but for now
we're letting you go.
But before we do,
we need evidence
that you were given your rights
and were questioned
according to protocol.
Read it out loud.
I'm recording it.
“My name is Leonard Carlton.
“I admit to violating
CIA regulations
“but no criminal wrongdoing.
Today I was questioned...”
Is this going to work?
Yes.
When Walter was in high school,
he created
a similar voice converter
to sound just like his mother.
He used it once
to call in sick to school.
Walter O'Brien played hooky?
There was a quantum physics
lecture in Dublin
that he didn't want to miss.
- Of course there was.
- Don't judge.
The heart wants
what the heart wants.
So does the brain.
So...
this is sort of a weird request,
but you are a shrink, and...
well, I-I need someone
to talk to.
Of course.
Lie on my couch.
It's about a guy.
Go on.
See, I had a dream.
Some disturbing,
inappropriate thoughts
about someone I shouldn't,
someone who probably
isn't good for me.
I get it.
Drew's handsome.
Not bright or loyal,
but handsome.
Right.
See, Leonard in there,
he is letting his feelings
cloud his judgment,
and I don't want to do that.
Any advice?
Paige,
I'm a brilliant doctor.
I'm brilliant enough to know
you're not telling me everything
about this dream.
Either you're being deceptive
or you're embarrassed, but...
I can't help you until you're
ready to tell me everything.
A mason can't build
without bricks, Paige.
I'm not a miracle worker.
“I acknowledge
no wrongdoing
and hereby certify
the aforementioned is accurate”"
Did we get everything?
Here, read that.
“Purple monkey dishwasher.”
What the hell does that mean?
Now we got everything.
Hey, I thought
you were letting me go.
Nope. See how easy it is
to get played?
Okay, I've downloaded
his recording.
Within seconds
my software will break it down
phonetically, and...
transmute my voice so that
on the other end,
it will sound exactly...
like Leonard.
Now, with Leonard's phone,
I'll call Sima,
pretending to be him,
and set a meeting
so we can find out
where she has the chemicals.
Are you sure you should
be doing this?
She calls him “boo”"
That's-That's
playful and fun.
Two words that don't exactly
describe Walter O'Brien.
It's setting an appointment.
I can handle this.
Now...
his voice will come through
her phone instead
of the speakers.
Hey, baby.
Hello...
you.
Did you have a good day?
Average. I hope you've had
an efficient day yourself.
You're going
to give it away.
Hold, please.
What?
I'm making conversation.
Be romantic, tell her you can't
stop thinking about her.
Leonard?
I can't stop thinking about you.
Aw... really?
- That's what I just said.
- Oh.
Honey,
I miss you so much,
your face, your mind,
your body...
I wish I were with you
right now just,
just touching you,
kissing you.
That sounds so good.
We should be
recording this, too.
When do I get to see you again?
Soon,
but, honey, uh,
I've hit a snag.
We have a problem
with the final delivery.
What happened?
They moved the third chemical
to a higher security lab.
I don't have clearance.
The guy who does,
Marvin, would never help us.
He's by the book.
Does he carry
the same security card as you,
only with
the necessary clearance?
Yes.
If I get you that card,
can you get the chemical?
Sure.
But...
how are you gonna get it?
Don't you worry about that.
Just ask Marvin to meet you
for a drink at my hotel,
and then,
at the last minute, cancel.
Will you do that?
Anything for you, honey.
You're such a good person.
I have to go now, my love,
but I'll be in touch soon.
I love you, baby.
I love you, too.
That's how it's done.
We have her on tape
admitting to doing this.
We can arrest her now.
Well, we might have enough
to arrest her,
but there's still two canisters
of dangerous chemicals
out there somewhere,
and that's two-thirds of the way
to making nerve gas.
We can't bring Sima in yet.
We need her to lead us
to those chemicals.
Okay, so, who's gonna be Marvin?
Well, Interpol's still doing
a background on Sima,
but there's no question
she's probably dangerous.
So I'll do it.
No, you're-you're Homeland.
You're former FBI.
She could have Intel
on our agents.
We can't risk her
I.D.'ing you.
Sylvester can't do it;
he's a nervous wreck.
He'd barf all over her.
I would.
Well, I guess
I'll have to do it.
I just hope she doesn't
fall in love with me, too.
No, Intel indicates
that she probably works alone,
but we can't be too careful.
We need someone to profile
the crowd in that bar
and make sure
she has no collaborators.
So we're down to Walter?
Am I the only person
who just heard that phone call?
Oh, I learned a lot
from that exchange.
Okay, we hack the
security cameras at the hotel,
we put an earbud
in Walter's ear, and we track
- the entire meeting.
- And while he distracts her,
Toby and I search her room
for evidence
of the stolen chemicals.
After hearing your
performance on the phone,
you're gonna need help.
I'll be your Cyrano.
The story of the guy
with the rhinophyma,
the large nose disease.
You missed
the whole love story?
I was focused
on his medical condition.
Come with me.
This is not gonna be easy.
Here, this color's good on you.
That color is nice on you.
Yeah?
Now, to give Happy and Toby
time to search her room,
you'll need to
stall her in the bar.
If she detects anything off,
she could flee or make a call
and those chemicals
could disappear forever,
and if she did what
we think she did,
she did it by using her allure.
She'll do the same thing
with you,
so you'll need to pretend like
you're falling for her charms.
Copy that.
Engage with her
on a personal level.
No.
No engaging-- flirting.
Do you even know how?
Look, you need to pick up
her vibe and return it.
Let's practice; I'll flirt
with you, and you flirt back.
Go ahead. Flirt back.
I am.
I mean, you need
to give off a vibe
like you're interested in me.
Copy that.
How's this?
Okay, moving on.
Uh, she'll probably try to steal
an access card from you,
even though you don't have one.
She'll probably try to...
touch you.
Feel your pocket.
No, I don't enjoy contact.
I know,
I've seen you hug people.
It's like
you're in a leper colony.
You need to be ready
for whatever she might do.
I can handle it.
Can you?
What if...
she does... this?
Or...
...this?
Why, I would be okay with that.
And if she got...
close?
I...
I think I could
handle that.
This could happen.
I will be r-ready.
I will be ready.
Good work.
Any sign of collaborators?
Those three are
legitimately loaded.
Spies do not get drunk
on the job.
That couple
has a baby.
That's a definite
espionage no-no.
And those guys
are actually USC fans.
You can tell
by how depressed they are.
So, coast is clear.
Sima's alone.
Speak of the devil.
That must be her.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
Walter's a dead man.
Hi.
Meeting someone?
Yeah, I was supposed to. My...
He, uh, texted me
he can't make it.
Good.
Then you can buy me a drink.
I'm Sima.
Sima, Marvin.
Pleasure.
What are you having?
I'm having...
water.
He doesn't drink.
But that's good,
because I want
to remember the moment
a beautiful woman
asked me to have
a drink with her.
But that is good, because
I want to remember the moment
a beautiful woman asked me
to have a drink with her.
Smoother
than the Scotch
they're serving.
Interpol report just came in.
Sima's just an alias.
Her real name is Fatima.
They tracked her activities.
Tokyo, Berlin, Minsk?
She has honey-trapped
half the agents
in the Western world.
She's wanted for two
unsolved murders in Prague.
You got to be careful, Walt.
Scratch your temple
if you copy.
Sylvester, you're up.
Did you say she was wanted
for two murders?
Go!
Come on!
A shovel pass on
third and long?!
That was an ineffective choice.
It's not reading
the access card.
Try moving the phone around.
Get out of there!
Got it. She's in 1002.
What the hell
are you waiting for?
Go see if there's any sign
of those chemicals.
So, then the eight
told the seven,
“What do you expect from me?
I'm a square root”"
So, you enjoy math humor.
I love it.
Man, she's good.
Uh, Walter,
she flipped her hair.
That's a flirtation marker.
Smile back.
Less.
He looks like he's birthing.
What do you do, Marvin?
I...
work for the government.
I'm an analyst.
So, you're smart?
I like smart guys.
Don't-don't-don't freeze.
Put your hand on hers.
Slowly move your fingers
back and forth.
Slow down.
Just let her know you're there.
Perfect.
Hold her gaze.
And look at her like you want
to know everything
there is to know about her.
Look at her
like you've never known
a woman like her before
and never will again.
Tell her...
from the moment you saw her
your definition
of “stunning” changed.
You know, from the
moment I saw you...
my definition of
“stunning” changed.
Perfect.
What's taking so long? Open it.
I can't. She booby-trapped it.
We open this,
an alarm will notify her.
We have no other way in.
Actually, we do.
Come on.
The gecko gloves from the CIA?
She gave me those, too.
I'm charming like that.
Huh.
It's a full moon out tonight.
Not funny.
You know, you look hot.
Come on, why don't
we get that jacket
off of you?
She wants to search your jacket
for the access card.
You need to stall.
Do it.
Yeah, why not?
Beautiful jacket. Yes.
You know, on second thought...
do you want to get out of here?
Oh, you want to go
to another bar?
She means upstairs, Walter.
You know, I never...
do this.
Maybe it's the drink,
I don't know, but...
I'm just going
to say how I feel.
I want you
to come to my room.
She thinks the card's
in his pants.
And those pants
won't stay on long.
Happy! Toby!
Where the hell are you?
Happy's climbing up
the side of the building
to Sima's room right now.
Hurry up!
I'm sorry.
Am I not scaling the building
by hand fast enough for you?
Where's Happy?
Oh, God...
Happy!
Aah! No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Happy?
The stupid glove
stopped sticking!
You know your little girlfriend
at the CIA
who designs this stuff?
Yeah.
Yeah, she sucks!
Oh, not good.
- Come on, man.
- Sylvester?
We have got to catch
her if she falls.
From 30 feet?
She could kill us.
Sylvester, think of something!
Okay, okay! The force of gravity
is 9.81 meters
per second squared.
If she swings hard to her left,
then her right hand
would completely
disengage from the building.
And for 2/10 of a second
she won't be
attached to anything.
But she can use that time
to get to the balcony...
or plummet to her death.
Very reassuring!
Okay.
If you get enough momentum,
it could work!
Or not!
It's 50/50!
It's natural to be scared.
You should be scared!
You're the one
who gave me these gloves!
You're slipping!
Do it now!
Ah...!
How did she pull that off?
'Cause she's Happy
Frickin' Quinn.
Clock's ticking, Happy.
What do you got?
Nothing.
You better hurry.
They're in the elevator.
Walter, Happy's
in the room right now.
You have to stall.
Mm...
You're impatient.
I like that.
- Mm...
- Walter?
Tell her there's another woman
that you care about.
Listen, there's, um,
there's this other woman...
and, um, what you and I
are about to do
could complicate
an already complicated
situation.
Marvin, let me assure you,
what you and I are about to do
will be the least complicated
thing you'll ever experience.
Okay.
Uh, how much longer do I have?
Two minutes. Tops.
There are no cameras
in the room.
Fill me in.
What are you doing?
I'm checking her stuff.
There might be a secret hollow
or something.
Just leave everything
the way you found it.
They're stepping off
the elevator.
I just found a key
for a Lock-Ur-Stuff facility.
Now, why would
an international spy
who's always traveling the world
rent a storage facility?
'Cause maybe that's where
she's keeping the chemicals.
Happy, get the hell
out of there!
And, uh, how do I do that?
The gloves are useless.
I'm not Spiderwoman.
They're coming down the hall!
They're almost there!
Hide now!
Uh, where?
And do not tell me
under the bed,
because that's the worst...
Happy still hasn't
gotten out, Walter.
You can't let her in.
You need to do something!
Think fast!
Oh, no...
Something wrong?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
That is a humdinger.
I'm out! Where's
the closest Lock-Ur-Stuff?
Two blocks away.
You and Toby are with me.
Sylvester and Paige,
keep your eyes on Walter
and help him distract Sima
until we get those chemicals.
I'm not sure he needs any help.
I hate to disagree, but
she's not that into it.
No hands on the back
of the head.
No fingers through the hair.
Maybe Walter's a bad kisser.
Okay, let's go.
Hold down the fort, kid.
We'll be back in five.
I'm going to go slip into
something less constricting.
We're gonna lose visual!
No bedroom, Walter.
Ha-Happy wasn't able
to put everything back.
If Sima sees,
your cover's blown.
There's no point.
Whatever you put on,
you'll be out of it
in a matter of minutes.
Oh...
Tell her you want her
on the couch.
I want you on the couch.
Mmm!
Tell her you can't wait
to have her.
I can't wait to have you.
But first...
tell her you want to order
champagne from room service.
What? No.
What do you mean “no”?
Uh, what?
Nothing.
Just, uh... you know...
You...
Oh...!
...just need to sit there
and watch.
97% certain sure I just heard
an extended zipper pull.
Most likely a dress.
Thank you, Sylvester.
You're welcome.
You will never forget
this night.
Say...
“I've wanted to be with you
since the moment
I laid eyes on you.”
I... I love hearing
your voice in my ear.
Thank you.
Careful.
She might've
booby-trapped this thing.
Yup. This is the stuff.
We got a problem.
Look at that.
It's a pressure alarm.
Not good?
Definitely not good.
Hmm?
What's that?
Oh, nothing.
It's just an alarm.
I can never
get it set right.
That is a strange watch
to be outfitted with
modern electronics.
Walter? Walter?
Walter, say something!
Now that our relationship
has evolved,
maybe you should tell me
your real name.
I've already told
you my name, Fatima.
That's not my real name, either.
Are we going somewhere?
I'm going home.
And if your associates
can follow my directions,
so are you.
I don't have any associates.
No?
While you were sleeping,
we made a deal.
They bring me the two canisters
from my storage facilities,
and Leonard gets the third
from the CIA lab.
They give me
all three chemicals,
I let you go.
Everybody wins.
And they're coming here?
You'd better hope so.
Got it.
Tail number: N888C41.
Are we sure this is a good idea?
You got a better one?
It's better than handing over
latent chemical weapons
to an anti-American agent?
Give me a minute.
If we don't give her
what she wants, Walter dies.
We got to do whatever we can
to get him off that plane.
She's far too cautious.
she'll keep him as collateral
to get out of American airspace.
It's time to get our man.
Welcome aboard.
Where's Leonard?
Uh, we didn't need him.
The CIA gave us
the third chemical.
There's all three chemicals
in the satchel.
They're the real thing.
There's a litmus test
in there to prove it.
Let's go, buddy.
Uncuff him.
New plan-- once we've landed
safely in neutral territory,
he'll be released.
We had a deal.
Yes.
And the deal was Leonard was
supposed to come with you.
How? Leonard's on his way
to a federal penitentiary.
She has an emotional
connection with him.
She knows you
could have gotten
the chemicals
without Leonard,
she only wants him here
because she loves him.
You uncuff my man...
...and I'll work out a deal
for you for Leonard.
You are a liar.
Cabe!
Ah...
Oh, my God,
that was a muzzle flash!
Look!
Let's go.
Cabe! Cabe, are you all right?!
Cabe! Cabe!
Damn glad she gave you
this shirt.
But right now,
we gotta figure out
how to stop that plane,
or Walter's as good as dead.
I got an idea.
♪ ♪
What the hell are you doing?
Walter,
what did you do?
Come on, come on, come on.
You gotta hurry.
You think?!
100 miles an hour,
147 feet per second,
which means they're gonna
run out of runway.
Got it!
Oh... my God.
Hey!
Walter!
Jump! We'll catch you!
If the chemicals blow up,
they will combine
and aerosol,
and kill people for miles!
Get ready!
Walter, no!
Do not throw me
deadly chemicals!
One, two, three!
Oh! God...!
Nice catch, Sly!
Hey, man, if that fire
hits the fuel tank,
the whole plane's gonna blow--
you got to jump, Walter!
I know! Hold on!
We got you, buddy, come on!
Come on.
Walter!
Jump!
Okay!
Be careful!
Okay, okay!
Walter!
Get me up!
You're all right.
Cabe said Sima will make it.
Maybe she and Leonard will be
in adjoining penitentiaries.
So she loved him.
It's not logical.
It's actually
totally logical.
It's called
the Wiseman Effect.
If you pretend you're
in love with someone,
sometimes you actually
start to believe it.
That's why she wouldn't
really kiss you back.
Heart belongs
to Leonard.
The good news is that you're
probably not as bad a kisser
as I theorized.
She had the chance
to get away,
but she gave it up for love,
for something that's not real.
It was real to her.
♪ ♪
I'm gonna write you a script
for antibiotics, too.
Why I'm doing that, Ralph?
'Cause burns cover
more surface area than cuts,
so more easily infected.
A-plus.
Jumping out
of a burning plane.
Yeah.
When did we become
action heroes?
I have no idea.
You're set.
Thank you, pal.
Mm-hmm.
How about a story?
Yes, please.
Yeah?
Robo-Spies,
issue one.
“The dawn of a new breed
of secret agent:
half-spy, half-robot”"
“It was a dangerous time
for spies.
“And human spies could
“no longer do the mission.
“Their skin,
and their mortality,
the way they thought...”
I know my advice earlier
wasn't real helpful.
Uh, let's try this.
The most important thing
to Sima, or whatever her name was,
was getting those chemicals
and making the nerve gas
and bringing it
back to her country.
And she was on the
verge of achieving it.
And then she threw it
all away for love.
Love can make you stupid.
The question is-- what's
your most important thing?
Ralph.
Then this is my advice:
whatever thoughts
you're having about Drew
or anyone else...
you ask yourself,
“Could this hurt Ralph”.
And take care of your
most important thing.
Huh, still here?
Uh, FAA--
you blow up one plane,
and the paperwork's
mind-boggling.
Where are you off to?
UCLA Research Lab.
It's almost midnight.
Yeah, I know, I'm late.
Don't work too much longer.
So, uh, pretty nuts--
a trained spy gets caught
because of love.
That's silly, huh?
The notion of romantic love
is a fairy tale.
The thought that people
can be affected
in some meaningful way by the
affection of others is... is...
Kiss, touch...
uh, the, uh...
Whatever, it's, um...
it's junk science.
It's not even that.
Yeah.
Like I said, silly.
Okay.
As my mother used to say,
sweet dreams.
Oh, Paige.
Can you, uh, record a new
outgoing message on the machine?
Sure.
Why?
Nothing.
Just realized recently
what a nice voice you have.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Sync, corrected by StoneSub
www.tvsubtitles.net