My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
In the past 24 hours,
you have broken over two dozen
state and federal laws.
You've dealt Homeland Security
a public relations nightmare.
And you destroyed
over $100 million
worth of private property!
Which is why you
ironically named geniuses...
The wrong use of “ironic.”
...are hereby ordered for
psychological evaluation.
That evaluation
decides your future.
From what I see,
you're too mentally unstable
to handle this job.
Anything else
smart you want to say?
No.
So much for your
little experiment.
And as the psychologist
assigned to this case,
I will interview each member
of your team individually.
You will take me through the
events of the past 24 hours
and explain your decisions.
Happy to help however I can.
Lying is one hallmark
of antisocial
personality disorder.
So, first off,
I suggest you be honest.
Honestly?
I'm looking at your diploma,
thinking I could have got
into your Alma mater
when I was seven.
Let's start
at the beginning.
Okay, but first
I-I should mention
that I also have a PhD
in clinical psychology.
Perhaps our time would be
better spent talking about you.
I don't think so.
Say more about that.
Ask me anything.
I'm an open book.
It all started yesterday.
One sec.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
All right.
From the beginning.
Well, it all began
with costumes.
Hmm, do you have the summary
document on our last job?
Good morning
to you, too, Walter.
How are you today?
Oh, you prefer
a different greeting.
Okay. Good morning.
How are you?
Do you have the summary document
on our last job?
I'll send it to you.
And thank you for asking.
I've been preparing for Ralph's
school Halloween party tomorrow,
but he doesn't want
to go 'cause he has
no one to go with.
Mm-hmm.
Come on, it's Halloween.
Exactly.
What does that mean?
It's a holiday
based on 16th century traditions
of warding off evil spirits.
It's not exactly progress.
To say nothing
of contributions
to tooth decay,
juvenile diabetes, early death.
You asked.
Good news.
Your friend the governor has
recommended you for a new gig.
And unlike the last few,
this one's cushy.
The Westside Museum of Art
is having a new exhibit of
a masterpiece by Franz Biermann.
I love his work.
Never heard of him.
The Verstand
Museum in Germany
owns the painting,
but while it's
within our borders
it falls under the
purview of Homeland.
We picked up some chatter
on some dark-net sites.
It's a highly coveted
target for art thieves.
We need you to upgrade the
security systems at the museum.
I'll fill you in on the
details on the way.
And Merrick granted
your request.
What request?
This is great.
Traveling together will
increase efficiency.
This is on trial loan
from the department,
so go easy on it.
Cushy gig aside,
isn't security work a little
below our pay grade?
The painting's worth
a hundred million bucks.
How is $32 of paint and canvas
worth a hundred million?
It's one of humanity's great achievements.
It's paint and canvas.
Art critic
Leslie Reinman calls it
“an exquisite rendering
of late 19th century
“small-town tranquility
“whose rhapsodic gestures
connote optimism
“and...
possibility.”
Um...
Are you okay?
My hypersensitivity and
overactive emotional quotient
are at times triggered
by works of art.
Don't tell me you
have a problem
with Halloween
and art.
They're both make-believe.
All ascribed value.
I took a
night school class
on Gauguin.
Ever seen his
paintings of Tahiti?
They're mind-blowing.
Well, in the time period
of the Biermann painting,
there were grain shortages
and starvation.
That old woman looks
like she has gout.
That ten-year-old girl--
middle-aged.
Hmm.
You can't openly mock things
99% of the world enjoys.
If you want to grow
this business,
take on private clients,
even be a functioning
member of society,
you have to learn how
normal people work.
Yes, but to what end?
You being more human could
help us get more jobs
and improve relationships
with superiors,
make my life more sane.
Think of it as
an experiment.
I'll give it a try.
Geniuses have
low EQ, or emotional quotient,
hence their difficulty
relating to us.
Sure, they have their issues,
but they're also
brilliant
and-and brave and special.
You're protecting
your job.
If I thought they were unstable,
would I allow my son
around them?
Your son... is them.
Thank you.
I think he's special, too.
Take me through
Walter's behavior at the museum.
Um...
This is
an exceedingly rare work
by an artist whose other paintings
have all been destroyed
during World War II,
so as curator,
its security is
my responsibility,
and forgive me
for saying so, but...
they don't seem like
typical law enforcement.
We're not typical
law enforcement,
Dr. Paulson.
We're better.
Very excited
to protect
your beautiful
and important art.
Right.
Was that supposed to be normal?
Experiment's begun--
not bad, huh?
Terrifying.
Good luck with this.
Take a look at this.
He's getting
awfully close to it.
Maybe he's enjoying it.
Walter may have some EQ.
No!
And...
I stand corrected.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I was doing my job.
Slashing a canvas
is your job?
Or evidence of your lack
of emotional maturity?
Both. I don't
have emotions.
I read that
in your file.
But how can you
protect something
if you don't
care about it?
I care about my paycheck.
I can't really tell if you're purposely
being contemptuous,
of maybe you are unstable.
Well, if you dismissed
every government worker
who was unstable,
Washington would cease to exist.
Giving these responses,
how do you expect me
to approve you?
I don't.
But to fail us would be
to disregard the fact
that no matter
how many people got upset,
my actions had a purpose.
I cut the painting
to thoroughly examine
both sides of the canvas--
it was efficient.
Efficient?
Are you out of your mind?
Do you have any idea
how much this painting is worth?
Yes-- as I
said, nothing.
It's a fake.
And there are several
reasons why
we knew this,
starting with Paige.
She loves this artist.
Seeing the painting
should have made her happy.
But when she
looked at the painting,
she displayed
the same repulsion markers
our sense of smell gives us
to rotting meat
when it exudes an odor.
Her subconscious
instinctively knew
something was off, but she
didn't know what it was.
Then I did a quick count
of the brushstrokes.
There's one thousand,
three hundred
and eighty-seven,
which is
48 less than the original.
And...
the type of nails
in the frame
weren't even manufactured
until four years
after this painting
was supposedly made.
Rotting meat...
brushstrokes...
and nails?
That's all you had to go on
before you destroyed
a masterpiece?
A fake masterpiece.
He's right.
Special Agent Carey,
FBI Art Crimes.
We just analyzed
the paint
and carbon-dated
the frame.
The painting
is a forgery.
Thank you
for repeating
exactly what I said
63 minutes ago.
That is a lovely windbreaker.
We may be able to I.D.
the forger by fingerprints
left in the paint.
Well, you won't find
any fingerprints in the paint,
because this painting
wasn't made by hand,
it was made by machine.
A forgery of this quality
made by a machine?
Not possible.
You're right.
It's not possible, it's certain.
Since there's no longer
a painting to protect,
I'm gonna ask you... to leave.
We very much thank you
for the opportunity to...
Go.
How else was I supposed
to tell him it was a fake?
Perhaps by saying,
“It's a fake.”
When delivering bad news, most
people try and do so gently.
Waste of time.
How'd the knife work for you?
Miraculously,
Special Agent Carey
wants you to stay
on the case.
So she appreciated
my efforts.
She found you smug, arrogant
and several other
choice adjectives.
But the FBI is lacking
expertise on this technology.
Explain your theory.
Thrilled to help anyone who
thinks we're smug and arrogant.
The force of a human hand
applying brushstrokes
would result in tiny
broken canvas fibers.
But that canvas was
perfectly intact.
Only a machine arm could
paint so delicately.
Plus, the mathematical patterns
in the paint were so precise
that they couldn't
have been executed
so flawlessly by a human being.
So, we follow the technology
to track down the forger.
And I'll have
Art Crimes investigate
who swapped the original
for the fake, and when.
We know the original
was authenticated
by Customs at LAX
at 6:42 this morning,
so we know the swap occurred
sometime after that.
But they'd have to canvass
airport staff, art handlers,
transport personnel--
Th-that could take days.
Well, the problem is,
most stolen art
leaves the country
within 24 hours,
never to be seen again.
I know someone who can help us
track it down,
but I want you all
on primo behavior.
A fake Biermann?
Does no one have any respect?
Real or fake, it doesn't matter.
If the people looking
at it can't tell,
what's the difference?
Believe me, I know.
Tell me about your
machine theory.
In order to create a
high-quality forgery
using a machine,
you'd first need
a three-dimensional scan
of the painting,
capturing every detail
from the brushstroke direction
to the thickness and volume
of the paint.
Then a spectral camera
would create
an algorithmic breakdown
of the colors,
to be mixed by the 3-D printer
and applied by machine arm.
But first the forger would need
an extremely high-res image
of the original.
Do you know how we can get
our hands on one?
When I was a costumer in London,
I used to visit
the Royal Stuart Museum.
They keep digital images
of major artworks.
Those images have
high enough resolution
to be used
by the forgers.
I'll just hack in.
Or... you could use
my account number.
Thank you.
Unfortunately, the
Biermann's been stolen before.
This is the actual
provenance of the painting.
“1936, Eckhart Mueller,
a Jewish shoemaker
“from Warsaw, buys
the painting directly from
“the artist Franz Biermann.
“1942, the Nazis seize
the painting from Mueller
and send him to Auschwitz,
where he's murdered by the SS.”
“1946,
“the Verstand Museum
takes possession
“of the painting.
“Since then
three generations
“of the Muellers
have tried
unsuccessfully to get it back.”
This family has spent a lifetime
trying to get
this painting back.
Art has meaning.
Found the image.
4K resolution.
More than enough
to create the forgery.
According
to the manifest,
this file's
been downloaded by
Ecole des Beaux-Arts students,
art book publishers
and once by
somebody from... Galactic Toys.
Oh, here we go.
Okay,
Galactic has the greatest
superhero pantheon in this
or any
other universe,
including my personal favorite,
Super Fun Guy.
I'm getting to it. Walter,
I'm getting
to it, okay?
They manufacture
these little masterpieces
using state-of-the-art,
cutting-edge
3-D printers and scanners.
They have everything
one would need
to create the perfect forgery.
The forger must work there!
And he is so... lucky.
We'll scan
their network
and I.D. the employee
on the way.
Thank you, Hetty.
Thank you.
It, uh, was an experience.
Okay, guys, come on! Let's go!
I've never seen
him move so fast.
Okay, Galactic Toys.
The I.P. address and LAN subnets
have narrowed it down to...
ten employees,
four of which work
in administration, which means
they lack the skill set
to even run
the technology.
Well, eliminate anyone
with a title of VP or above.
They wouldn't risk their pension
on criminal activity.
Well, that leaves five.
Only three
have art backgrounds.
That one!
Look at that knockoff
designer sweater.
He doesn't care about the difference
between real and fake.
A man after my own heart.
Phil Daniels.
Married, three kids.
Needs money, has
ability and motive.
Hey, Cabe,
I'm gonna go with you.
You're all staying here,
and that's an order.
I'll be back
in ten minutes.
He's been waiting for this his whole life.
Well, then he should
be used to it. I don't need
a bunch of geniuses
to help me detain
an unarmed artist.
Could you at least get me
a Super Fun Guy T-shirt?
He's really...
Cabe, he's really fun!
I am 50 feet from Valhalla,
but I might as well be 50 miles.
Maybe you should
emulate Sylvester.
He might be extreme,
but at least... he emotes.
That is not ideal to me.
So if Walter
has no emotional
quotient, you have...
Infinitely too much.
What are you looking at?
That bookshelf's not anchored.
If there was an earthquake,
it could fall,
it could crush you, causing
massive trauma, a concussion.
Plus, I wouldn't want to see
any of that blood.
I'm sorry.
You asked me
a question?
Does your anxiety hinder
your ability to do your job?
And if so,
how can you work on this team?
Well, because of Walter.
He keeps me out of my head,
keeps me focused on the work.
But if I were you,
I would...
I'd just move the chair just,
like, a couple inches.
I don't get it.
Because the parrot
has a hat on.
Oh, that's funny.
Uh, technically.
It's funny completely.
No. Break it down logically,
bringing a parrot into a bar
makes no sense.
You're disappointed.
Just starting to see the scope
of what needs to be done.
In the meantime,
I can still solve this case.
Cut him off at the corner.
Okay.
I'll get Cabe!
It's faster to call him!
What?
I can't hear you!
Hey! Hey!
Stop! Stop! I'm a federal agent!
Hey!
Are you working out
some issues?
Shh!
Ow.
Hey! Hey!
I can't...
I looked
everywhere for you.
Are those chicken feathers?
This is all fixable.
Whether or not I'm stable--
fascinating question.
I've personally treated
many mentally unstable people.
Dated some, too.
You're trying to game me again,
Mr. Curtis.
Answer my question.
I'm rock steady.
The only reason
we disregarded Cabe's orders
is because we had
to chase Daniels.
He could have led us
to the painting.
Through busy downtown streets.
Government employees are
supposed to protect property,
not destroy it.
You can't make an omelet
without breaking a few eggs.
That's not
a metaphor.
I'm just stating a fact
about breakfast.
You know another sign
of antisocial behavior?
Witty humor?
Addiction issues.
That's my favorite kind.
All I know is
I'm in good hands
in the employ of Walter O'Brien,
one of the most intelligent
human beings in the world.
From my file, it seems like
you're in competition with him.
No. He's infinitely smarter
than both of us.
When I met him,
I was gambling
every night,
in jail pretty often, too.
I'd still be there
if it weren't for Walter.
He's pretty exceptional.
Don't tell him I said that.
You spooked him.
He won't talk. The FBI
gave us one hour with him
and we're at zero.
That's what happens
when a guy gets chased
by a bunch of weirdos in a van
covered in chicken feathers.
The FBI searched
his house,
his storage locker, his records,
everything, turned up nothing.
The painting's
worth $100 mil.
If he doesn't
talk fast,
we'll never see it again.
Give me 30 seconds with him.
So, Agent Gallo in there
thinks you stole the painting.
I know
you didn't do it.
Well, finally,
someone who believes
I'm innocent.
I didn't say you're innocent.
You graduated CalArts
nine years ago,
dreaming of becoming
the next Picasso.
Then you had
a few small shows, but...
the decision makers in suits
didn't get your brilliance.
Then you slipped one past
the goalie with your girlfriend.
Diapers
are not cheap.
So you took a job
with Galactic Toys.
It's hard to believe you've been
there nearly a decade,
watching your dreams
slip away. But the calluses
on your right thumb and
middle finger tell me you still
paint every day.
You're
an artist.
All artists want the same thing:
recognition.
So when someone offered
to pay you to forge a painting,
that felt good.
Finally, someone recognized
your skill.
In fact, you could have done
that whole thing by hand.
You only supplemented
your skill with a machine
because they made you.
I want a lawyer.
Sure,
that'll convince people
you're innocent.
Whoever paid you
to make that fake
stole the original themselves,
making you an accomplice.
Whoa.
I was hired to make a copy
of a painting,
which is not illegal.
What the guy did with it
after that is his business.
The irony is
he's not gonna take the fall
for it-- you are.
Just give me his name.
Jacques Labeaux.
Real estate tycoon.
Friend of the mayor. He paid
Daniels to forge the painting.
Most of Labeaux's
online accounts
were impenetrable,
but we discovered
that he pays
two electric bills,
one for his main house
and one for a separate
climate-controlled room.
It's a wine cellar.
No, that's not a wine cellar.
Look at the electricity usage.
It's a huge room.
Much more suitable for...
storing art.
Gonna have to trust Happy
on this one, Toby.
Trust me on
this, Walter.
We're talking wine,
one of my specialties.
Doesn't really
matter right now.
All we have
is the word
of an admitted forger.
We'll never get a search warrant
with that alone.
I'll call in
some favors
and see if I can't get
a wiretap,
but that'll take some time.
You hang tight until you
receive further orders.
I'll update you as soon
as I have something.
Okay.
So Labeaux commissioned
the fake,
so we have to assume
he has a real painting.
Chances are he's
trying to move it.
Any idea on his whereabouts?
Uh...
I'm digging,
I'm digging...
Okay, got some thing.
He's at home, preparing for
a big charity gala tonight.
Guys!
This is happening
right now.
He'll be hosting
hundreds of people,
three bars, live music...
And us.
Cabe told us...
Cabe is gonna cost us
an opportunity.
Are we really
going to smuggle
a painting out
during a party?
There will be equipment
coming in and out,
trucks, commotion...
The whole thing
could be a subterfuge
to try and smuggle that painting
out of the country tonight.
Now, Happy,
Toby...
you'll slip in,
try and locate that painting.
If you can't find it, then,
we're gonna need all the details
that we can get
on Labeaux
and his business dealings.
Paige, I'm gonna hack us
onto the guest list.
Try and get as close to Labeaux
so we can clone his phone.
Sly, you'll QB from the van.
Without Cabe,
we won't get the gear we need.
And I have nothing to wear.
I am not being a diva.
I was a broke waitress
six weeks ago.
I literally have
nothing to wear
for a fancy party.
I know someone
who can help on both fronts.
You were smart to come back.
This party, I'm sure, will have
a fashion-forward crowd.
And in the wrong clothes,
you'd be
spotted immediately as fakes.
It's Halloween weekend.
Why isn't Labeaux
having a costume ball?
'Cause rich people are smart.
They know
that Halloween is foolish.
Aren't you a ray of sunshine?
And I'm a waiter.
Wow.
Sometimes
I even surprise myself.
Is this okay?
Brava.
Really?
Yes.
You silver-tongued devil, you.
Well, what about...
what about, what about me?
Well, you're
in the van, so
you can wear your stupid shirt.
Yes.
Uh, do you have any
Halloween costumes for
a nine-year-old boy?
Like a... like a
zombie or a ninja or
a pirate?
Um, I'll keep looking.
These comm devices
are on an encoded
frequency.
There you go.
And there.
Thank you.
Out you go.
Before I start to regret
loaning you
my things.
I've never been
to a party like this.
Don't worry.
We'll fit right in.
Thank you.
Of course.
Sorry.
There you go.
What about the guest list?
Oh, I took care of it.
Last name?
Gauguin.
Looks just like
my apartment.
Focus.
We may never
recover that painting
unless we get Labeaux's
data, wherever he is.
Mesdames et messieurs,
bienvenue.
I'm your host
Jacques Labeaux.
And tonight
we will be raising money
for the
Arts Are Fundamental Charity.
I hope you'll all
open your hearts
and your wallets
for this great cause.
For is there
any more noble pursuit
than the arts?
Science, mathematics,
professional wrestling,
anything besides art.
You're missing the
point about art.
Happy and Toby are in position.
Here, time to go,
time to go.
...literature,
writing, music.
Alarm off
in three, two, one.
I'm unlocking the door.
To get to the storage locker,
take the northwest
stairs to the basement level.
Now, to clone Labeaux's
phone, we have to get this
within five feet of him
for three
uninterrupted minutes.
Easy. We'll just
stand near him.
Where'd he go?
Oh. I don't know.
Got him.
Oh.
Let's dance next to him.
Come on. There has to be
a more efficient way.
This is the most
efficient way.
I don't dance.
Here's the storage locker.
It's a 96-bit triple-encrypted
TD9 lock.
Do you know how
impressed I am when I have
no idea what you're saying?
Remind me to dumb it down
next time.
You ready?
- No.
- You need to stay within
five feet of him
for three minutes starting now.
We're a couple, remember?
Do you know where
to put your hands?
You're not pushing
me on a swing.
Lower.
Put your hand lower.
Good.
Keep it there
at the small of my back.
Oh, it's not bad.
It's easy, right?
Basic mathematics.
Count the beats,
four-four time,
uh, 76 beats per minute.
That explains it.
We're in.
It's a wine cellar.
Do you know why
geniuses can't dance?
'Cause we have
two left brains.
Walter, did you just
make a joke?
I used wordplay to
manipulate a common phrase.
Well, it's a start.
I think your experiment
is starting to work.
Download
will complete in 15 seconds.
Oh, no. Malfunction!
Walter, the cloning device
reset! You have
to start the download
all over again!
We have to keep dancing.
Okay.
May I cut in?
I can't not dance with the most
beautiful woman at my party.
90 seconds.
Stall, Walter.
Oh, well,
if it's all right
with you, honey.
I-I'd be delighted.
I'll-I'll just be
over there, honey.
Okay. How much longer?
80 seconds and counting.
It's a cover.
No one keeps
such fine vintages this cold.
It's not just
a wine cellar.
There's got to be a door
or cabinet or something.
How much time left?
30 seconds.
Will you stop asking?
That's, like, the fourth time.
What's gotten into you, anyway?
This was recently installed.
It's got to be hiding
a secret door.
No door.
Come on.
Walter, we got it.
Okay.
Excuse me.
May I?
Merci.
Okay.
Download complete?
Download complete.
There's nothing behind there.
No.
Oh.
It's just a wine cellar.
What was that noise?
Oh, no.
Somebody go
check that out.
Someone's coming.
That's the only exit.
What's going on?
Time to go.
Sylvester, we're about
to get made. Do something!
I'm on it.
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
What happened to you guys?
We got out through the kitchen,
I ran into
a giant cake.
I don't want
to talk about it.
We didn't find the art,
but we cloned the phone.
Step on it!
It was an easy mistake.
How could I have possibly
known that was a wine cellar?
The painting could be
somewhere else in the house.
No, not anymore.
By now, Labeaux's found
the broken wine bottles,
he knows someone's hacked
into the power.
He knows we're onto him.
He's gonna try
and move that painting fast.
Sylvester?
You search his
call history?
Art world's supposed
to be rarified air,
but instead
it's full of thieves.
This guy stole it
from the museum,
who stole it
from the Mueller family.
This is supposed
to be the intellectual elite?
I thought you didn't
care about art.
I'm faking. Remember?
Sounds awfully real.
Somewhere along the line,
you had a breakthrough.
You're improving.
Okay, Labeaux made
half a dozen calls
to one number in the 48 hours
before the original painting
disappeared.
The name is encrypted,
but I think I can break it.
In how long?
That long.
And I thought I didn't like him
'cause he was a know-it-all
art jerk.
Here's an e-mail
from Labeaux to Paulson with
his bank's routing
and account numbers.
Labeaux provides access
to the fake,
Paulson provides access
to the original.
We didn't find the painting
at Labeaux's because he never
had it. Paulson does.
As curator, he could
easily pull this off. He plans
all the museum's exhibits.
The Biermann's worth nine
figures. He wouldn't
move it by air. There are more
security gaps at the docks.
We'll call Cabe from the van.
Paige.
Take this to Hetty.
It can't be discussed over
the phone. She'll understand.
What's this about?
Read it, you'll see.
Oh, I'm gonna need to take your
car as well for the Wi-Fi.
You take the van.
And hurry.
I appreciate it.
I never thought
I'd hear him say that.
Safe to say this is when
the mission went
from the frying pan
into the fire.
Safe to say anything
you want,
unless it pisses me off.
You're guilty
of breaking and entering,
trespassing,
larceny.
Do you even think how Walter
puts all your lives at risk?
We're geniuses.
All we do is think.
Ever think about how none of you
have anywhere else to go?
Especially you.
Since, from what I can tell,
you have no family to speak of?
There's always a plan,
and we follow it because
we believe in Walter.
And besides,
as soon as we knew the
play with the curator,
we called our superior.
- Paulson? The curator?
- We've got him, yeah,
we're on his tail right now.
We surveilled him, followed him
to his house, where he put
the painting in his car.
You went through
private property
without a search warrant.
Anything you saw
is inadmissible in court.
Actually, it is admissible,
because we're not
working at your behest.
We're operating
as private citizens, so the more
we defy you,
the more legal it is.
That's good to know.
We got to remember that
for next time.
All right,
I scanned the manifests
at the San Pedro docks.
There's one ship leaving
for Shanghai in an hour.
And guess who booked
space in the cargo hold.
Paulson.
If that boat leaves
with the painting, it's gone.
We're accessing his car's
operational mainframe. Okay,
meet us on
the 6th Street Bridge.
We'll cut
Paulson's engine.
All you have to do
is arrest him.
You'll find the stolen painting
in the trunk.
No drama, no high-speed chase,
no risk.
Okay, but
do not engage.
We don't want
to endanger the public.
We'll keep it safe.
Just like the painting.
Use the built-in Wi-Fi.
Got full bars.
We're in.
We got control
of his car.
Cutting engine power.
Raising engine temp.
You're under arrest.
Painting's in the trunk.
Agents are
en route,
they'll take it
to the museum.
Another unit is apprehending
Labeaux right now.
Well done, guys.
You sure know your tech.
Oh, no, the painting.
That might be our fault.
Something must've gone wrong
with the frequency
- or the F6 diode or...
- I don't care. What I
care about is this.
And you destroyed a
$100 million painting.
Where are you going?
Well, I told you the whole
story, so we're done.
Forensic gave me
your cloning device.
I carried it in my
bag, I jostled it.
I even dropped
it. Not once
did the device
accidentally reset.
Which is why
I find it odd
that it got reset while
you were dancing with Paige.
It was probably
some radio wave interference.
Know what I really
think happened?
You enjoyed dancing with Paige.
Holding her.
Being close.
You didn't want it to stop,
so you reset the
device yourself.
You risked
the entire mission
to dance with her
for 30 more seconds.
I would never
jeopardize a mission.
I have met with
all of your team.
They rely on you,
they defend you.
They're brilliant,
they're talented,
and all I've ever tried
to do is protect them.
Together we can do things
that no one else can do.
And it's up to you to decide
whether you'll allow us
to keep doing that.
Now, excuse me.
Okay, so I ran
the potentialities, and the
likelihood of us passing
this test is very low.
All right, the good news is,
either way, we got this.
It would pair
beautifully with
a leg of lamb, but given
our higher-than-normal
anxiety levels, I think we
should pop this open right now.
Guys.
You passed.
Aah!
Oh.
Yeah!
Give me some.
Yeah, let's go pop this.
Good idea.
Enjoy.
So, um...
Dr. Davis thinks we're okay?
Well, I wouldn't go
that far. She passed you
because, and I quote,
“Mr. O'Brien seems
to believe that lying
“to a federal psychologist
is justified
“so long as the job is done.
“However,
his deeper motivation
“stems not, as he states,
“from a desire
to complete his mission,
“but from empathy
for his team members.
“He has created for himself
“a purpose,
“and for each of them,
“a family.
“A safe haven.
A place to reach
their potential”"
Doesn't sound like you.
That hurts.
I doubt that.
But it got me thinking
about some things
that didn't make sense.
Like when you
hacked Paulson's car
and it didn't exactly
work as planned.
Well, technology's
not always reliable.
It is when you
guys do it.
So then I went down
to the evidence locker
to look for the fake
painting. Couldn't find it.
I don't know
how we'll build
a case against Paulson
and Labeaux without it.
This isn't the first time
they've done this.
Their records will lead you to
all of their other stolen art.
Your case will be airtight.
And if I had Forensics test
the ashes of that painting,
would it be the fake
or the original?
Forensics won't
reveal a thing about
the painting's authenticity,
'cause it was completely
destroyed in the fire.
And if I were to call
the Mueller family,
would they be
particularly happy?
Danke.
Thank you.
Let's keep this
between us.
Oh, don't hang it near
your window, Mrs. Mueller.
I'll walk you out.
No one will know about this?
Not Interpol.
Not Cabe. No one.
Before, you said
that painting
was meaningless.
Now you broke the law
to return it to its
rightful owner.
I grew to appreciate its, uh...
subtle beauty and
lyrical composition.
Fine. I still don't get it.
You know,
I saw how Duke Guillaume
looked at Countess Stephanie.
And I saw
the way you
looked at Paige.
Something made
you understand
that family's connection
to the painting.
Something.
Or someone.
Everything happened
like I said it did.
For real.
Hello? They said
we should come in here.
Come on.
Hello?
I guess you don't
hate Halloween after all.
Oh, we still hate it.
But we love Ralph.
We were hoping we could tag
along to your school party.
Hmm.
My highly tuned
facial recognition skills
tell me that is a yes.
Hmm. All right, let me guess
who's who.
Super Fun Guy.
No surprises
there.
Uh...
Sigmund Freud?
Ah, precisely.
Which means
I'm dressed as a hack.
Meow.
Every girl does that costume.
And it's still hot.
I give up.
Agent Cabe Gallo.
Okay.
We also cooked
something up for you.
You come with us, big man.
Oh.
So let me get
something straight.
Art makes you feel
nothing, yet you
lied to your superiors
and risked your job
in order for us to return
the painting to its
rightful heirs.
You also think
Halloween is nonsensical.
Mm-hmm.
And yet you
took time off work
to get dressed up
and go to Ralph's party.
For a guy who says
he has no feelings,
you sure are sweet.
Eh, it's just a costume.
Oh, my God,
that's the perfect costume.
Yeah.
I thought you'd like it.
Hey, come on, we got
a party to catch.
You know, Ralph, uh,
Halloween started off as a day
to ward off evil spirits.
Isn't that stupid?
Yeah.
But who cares?
Let's go get some candy.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net