My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
Wedding's coming up soon.
We need to give people
time to shop.
I hear what you're saying,
but I really don't
ever see us using china.
Your parents have
beautiful wedding china.
That they never use.
Well, we need to
register for something.
Okay. Well, there's this
really cool NFL chess set.
QB's the king,
cheerleader's the queen.
Never... ever...
...ever.
China it is.
That's my boy.
Ready to roll?
Yeah.
Okay.
System up and running.
Diagnostic
clear.
Good to go, Sarah.
Hooking up O2.
Go for oxygen. Okay.
12 hours
since reactive agent was added
to the phosphate compound.
Reading off weights.
Dish one: 2.2 ounces.
Dish two:
2.2 ounces.
Dish number three...
Babe,
your O2's dropping.
Correct manually?
Yeah.
How's that?
No increase.
You know what, Sarah?
I'm getting...
dizzy.
Okay. Step out.
Babe, the door
won't open.
Door won't respond.
I'm having trouble
breathing.
Sarah...
Jim,
sarin gas is leaking in from
Tox Storage through the vents.
No, no, no.
Do not remove cover!
Your lab's filled
with nerve gas!
Hold on!
This is Sarah Jacobs in Zone 1.
We have a breach
in the lab, and Jim is in there.
Somebody help us!
Come on, Ferret Bueller,
stand up.
Good boy.
Look at that--
he thinks he's people.
When are we ditching
this weasel?
You don't like pets?
I wasn't talking
about the ferret.
How long are you
gonna punish me
for sleeping through our date?
What's your lifespan?
Elia's popping in?
Good!
You're here! Hope
you don't mind me
stopping by unannounced.
Wanted to give you this.
You saved my daughter--
I can get you a little something.
Come on, open it up.
Okay.
Wow. A DC magnetic coil
for my rocket,
circa 1987.
A bit rusty.
28 bucks, retail.
But it comes with something else.
Tetanus?
This.
Excuse me?
I was eating breakfast,
and it hit me.
The work you're doing
on your rocket
isn't that much different
than the engine in the Ferrari.
Air and fuel intake results
in a propulsion of the piston heads...
That is, in theory, what I'm doing with
my propulsion chamber.
How cute-- they're finishing
each other's sentences.
Thought you should
drive it around for
a little bit, get a feel
for what you're building
on a smaller scale--
but not that much smaller.
You're giving him
a half-million-dollar car
to help him with
his science project?
It's just a loaner.
Though... truth is,
well, I got nine
of these things
and I never drive them, so...
you might want to hold on
to it for a while.
Walter, he's trying to poach you.
This is just a "thank you."
Lying billionaire says what?
Huh?
Close enough.
Guys, don't ruin this for me.
I already offered
Walt a job,
and he turned me down--
he's happy here.
My driver has arrived.
Walter,
enjoy the car.
We'll talk soon.
Guys, say hello
to the rest of the gang for me.
Hey,
give my best
to the Illuminati.
Thank you. Thank...
This car has
strings attached.
And those strings will
fly off once I'm driving
at 190...
miles an hour.
What's that?
Trouble.
Ralph.
Come check out this engineering.
Why is your kid
in the monkey suit?
Picture day. He's so cute--
he wanted to pick
the outfit himself.
There, look at that.
You don't see
what's going on there?
Mm, no.
Hey, Ralphy-boy,
could you do Uncle Toby a favor
and take off that jacket?
You don't want to get
grease on it.
You better roll up those
sleeves, too, buddy, just to be safe.
Congratulations,
you're raising Walter.
Oh, God.
Ralph! Ralph,
my action figure is here!
Be thankful--
Ralph could be emulating him.
It came in
this morning.
It's very rare.
A silicone rubber,
composite prototype
of the original
Super Fun Guy action figure
from the 1970s.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll be receiving
the rest of the gang:
the Giggler,
Sir Jokes-A-Lot,
Zany Zoey,
the entire team!
Just like us.
Cool, but...
I'm not really part of Scorpion.
Hey, hey, of course you are.
You helped us crack
that video game that
caught those bad guys.
You-you hacked that
Japanese warship.
You're a very, very
important part of the team.
And, Ralph, that's why
this one is for you.
He can't have that.
It's okay, I have, like, four.
Thank you.
Okay, off to school. I'll take that.
Ralph.
Race cars?
Collectible toys?
You guys spoil him.
Can I drive the car?
Nope.
♪ ♪
The neurotoxin research
facility right outside of L.A.
Something tells me I'm not
gonna like what's in this file.
Someone took over the
building this morning.
It's computerized to the hilt.
Whoever hacked in
has total control.
Bulletproof security doors,
labs where the nerve agents
are stored,
and a ventilation system
that could spread gas
throughout the facility,
killing everyone who's trapped inside.
How many?
23 very scared scientists.
One of whom-- Jim Stone--
has been locked in a room
that the hacker
filled with sarin.
And he's keeping Stone's O2
levels in his Hazmat suit
so low, he's
barely breathing.
So, if Stone keeps
the suit on much longer,
he runs out of air, and if
he takes it off, he's dead.
It gets better.
Our little Baghdad
bombings from '97
have come back
to bite us in the ass.
How?
Hacker wants the president
to disclose on live TV
everything about the bombings
we never released.
How we missed
our intended target
and killed 2,000 civilians,
how we covered it up.
Commander in Chief
cannot concede to threats.
We have any leads on this guy?
Homeland hasn't been able to trace
the e-mail communiqué
that's been coming in to HQ.
Bouncing off servers
all over the world.
All we know is that it came in
from a cell phone.
Time frame?
Perp wanted POTUS on the air
within 90 minutes
or we'd be sorry--
that was 40 minutes ago.
So get your team
to the site ASAP.
The media already has wind
that something's up.
Before you know it,
it'll be a circus.
After the '95 Tokyo subway
sarin gas attacks,
the United States created
an anti-neurotoxin program
that resulted in the lab
that is now under siege.
We are more than an hour
into this takeover.
Now, experts claim if any
of this neurotoxic material
were to aerosol
out of the facility,
it could possibly kill
thousands of Angelenos.
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
- Credentials?
- It's all right.
She's with me.
The five zones of the building
run east to west.
Some larger, with free access
to multiple rooms.
Other zones are mostly laboratories.
There's a vent system
linked to a server, so air flow,
including the release
of nerve gas into the vents,
could be manipulated.
We got Hazmat on
standby, and they're ready.
My God,
what a nightmare.
As this poor guy, Jim,
already learned, his O2 levels
are at the bottom rung.
We need to figure out
a way in ASAP.
I can rig a charge to blow
through that door in five minutes.
No go. All doors
are computer-controlled.
We breach 'em, the hacker
sees this on the system,
and instantly
releases the gas.
It's not just the door
that won't let us in--
whoever hacked this lab
set up some sort of block
that I've never seen before.
I can't even get
within a mile
of the network.
The hacker's
90-minute deadline
is practically up,
and, uh, we will not be able
to regain control in time.
You think or you know?
I know.
We're in the dark right now
as to how he got in
and what he's doing
to keep us out.
I'm also, um...
I'm concerned from
an efficiency standpoint
that my personal connection
to the case
might affect my ability
to solve it, so...
What's happening right now,
it's not your fault.
I designed the software
used for the bombs.
The bombs killed the civilians.
The hacker wants revenge
for those deaths.
I'm in the DNA
of this thing, Cabe.
No, you're not.
You were just a kid.
The blame lies with me.
Now, right now
we got a job to do, okay?
HQ's getting another e-mail.
"I told you what I wanted.
You've give me nothing.
Time's up."
Three sentences-- issue,
application, conclusion.
He's using the language
of someone who's
about to take action.
Something's wrong, guys.
Oh, God, Jim,
just hold on, okay? Hold on!
I'm gonna try to override
the system.
The hacker's
cut off his oxygen.
She can't override
the system. We're helpless.
Come on!
Sarah...
He can't breathe.
Turn it off.
Cabe! Turn it off!
Jim, no, hang on, okay?
It's not working! Damn it!
I have to open my mask.
I can't breathe.
No! Oh, God,
Jim, hold on!
Do not remove your helmet!
Just hold on!
He takes that off,
he's dead in seconds.
Don't take off your helmet,
okay? Hold on...
Jim!
♪ Scorpion 1x21 ♪
Cliffhanger
Original Air Date on April 13, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Tensions are high as
the unfolding hostage situation
has now become a murder scene.
With the victim's body
unrecovered
and dozens still trapped inside,
the question
everyone's asking is:
What are the authorities
going to do?
Hacker's now saying that
everyone dies in 60 minutes
if we don't give in
to his demands.
We got to get in there now!
Yelling doesn't help.
I don't even have
a digital foot in the door.
He basically made
the entire system invisible,
and I don't know how.
Structural?
Well, the third time I've been
through the blueprints--
no weaknesses.
Unless we can un-hack
those security doors,
we're not getting in.
She's breaking down.
At a base level, we're feeling
the same frustration as her--
outside looking in.
Helplessness is
a destructive emotion.
Wait, wait, wait.
Stop, stop, stop.
Outside looking in.
We need to do that.
We need to look
into the building-- right no
we're out here trying to jump
on an external network signal--
but we can't.
Maybe that's because
the problem is internal.
Like an actual physical compromise
to the building's internal server.
The hacker's been manipulating
a system
he did not design.
He could've overloaded
certain portions of it,
like burnt circuits, wiring,
and if that's so,
that's why we can't get
into the system from out here.
Fried hardware. We fix it,
we can get control of the system
and then we can retake control
of the building.
Exactly. Now, we need to search the
blueprints for the server hub.
Gallo.
Just got off
the horn with the White House.
Bodies dropping is bad press,
but POTUS still can't be
puppet-mastered by some thug.
So they found a middle ground.
An appeasement?
We're gonna release all Intel
related to the Baghdad bombing
in a massive document dump,
everything from combat
weather reports
to supply requisitions.
So it looks as if
it's a run-of-the-mill
declassification of records.
Based on what the hacker's
looking for,
is it necessary
to release all documents
from the Baghdad
operation,
particularly certain memorandum
between you and I
a few days prior to the bombing?
We're mid-standoff,
and you want me
to cherry-pick out data
so you don't hurt
your relationship
with your little pal?
O'Brien is instrumental to
Scorpion and national security.
Anything
that might disrupt that...
I am Homeland Director.
So I will worry about what
disrupts national security.
Hey.
Have O'Brien meet me around
back. It's important.
What, more demands
from the hacker?
There are things about Baghdad
that you don't know.
What things?
Son, I was honest with you
when I told you
that I had no idea
the government planned
to use your technology
for munitions
instead of aid packages.
You were just a kid.
I would never have lied to you.
I already know this.
Son, you know
how I feel about you.
Cabe, what are you trying
to tell me?
Three days
before the bombs were dropped,
Merrick told me
of the true agenda.
You knew
they were gonna drop bombs?
Not at first.
Just three days prior.
And you never told me.
I was concerned that if I did,
you would disable your software
and sabotage the mission.
That's exactly what I would have done.
And you would've gone
to prison for doing so, and I
would've been tried for treason.
Son, I had no idea that
civilians would've been killed.
The target was an Iraqi leader.
Come on, Walter. Say something.
If you're done,
I have work to do.
Right there. Cam 23,
bottom left. We got it.
Walt, where have you been? We
found the server hub in Zone 1.
Walter.
Are you okay?
Walter, you hear me?
What the hell is going on here?
Nothing. Uh, let me see...
let me see this.
Okay.
Okay, excuse me.
- Just a minute.
- Whoa.
What are you doing?
I'm calling Sarah.
She's the only scientist
in Zone 1. If we're gonna save
these people,
then we'll need her help.
Walter.
What are you doing?
She just lost her fiancé,
and you've got something
going on.
You want her to
be able to help,
then she'll need to talk
to someone human.
Hello?
Sarah,
I'm-I'm Paige Dineen.
I'm with the team trying
to help you out of the building.
I-I can't imagine
what you've been dealing with
or-or what you're going
through right now,
but if you and your coworkers
are going to get out of there,
we're gonna need your help.
We-we...
we were getting married.
We need to hurry. We need...
I know Jim
loved you,
and he'd want you to be safe and
to get out of there and-and live
the rest of your life.
But to do that,
you'll need to get
to the server hub down by
the far west entrance.
And bring your cell phone.
We'll need to see each other.
Do you know what the word
"appropriateness"
means, Ralph?
Suitable for a particular
purpose, person, or occasion.
In school,
do you think it's appropriate
to explain in detail the effects
nerve gas has on the human body?
We were doing science.
It wasn't
appropriate, Ralph. I know
everyone's in a tizzy
over what's going on
in the news,
but we have
to keep it appropriate.
Excuse me,
Principal Pastorneck.
You're needed in
Mr. Berger's class.
You stay here.
In addition to SWAT,
Homeland Security, and the FBI,
independent government
contractor, Team Scorpion,
is on the case.
Considering the stakes,
they'll need all hands on deck.
Okay, I'm here.
I'm putting you on speaker
so you can hear
from the rest of our team.
Hi, Sarah.
Um, can you open
the panel and point
your camera at it?
Great.
Nothing out
of the ordinary.
Oh, oh. Okay, um,
the large red cables
to your left,
can you move them
to the side?
Let's see behind it.
Yeah. There it is.
- Oh, boy.
- What?
I was right. It is
an internal structural problem,
but the wires weren't fried--
they were cut.
What do you mean "cut"?
Sarah, uh, what is
your system-check protocol?
I run a diagnostic every morning
at 8:15
once everyone's carded
into the building.
And today everything checked out?
Yes. No one's left since.
- Not good.
- What?
What's not good?
It was an inside job.
The person who cut the
wireless server cables,
the hacker, is inside
the building right now.
Oh, God.
Sarah,
I need you
to remain calm, all right?
We need you.
You're the only one
that we can count on.
All right, first things first,
we need to get you back
to your control room.
All the labs have monitors,
and if the hacker
sees you moving about,
checking
the server hubs,
then that's bad news.
How do you know he didn't see me
on my way down here?
He would've killed you already.
What? It's true.
What is wrong with you?
Okay, based
on hallway dimensions
and security camera
points of view,
I can calculate the blind spots
along the way back
to the control room.
Come get me out!
She's hysterical.
Whoever
killed Jim
is in the building with me.
Sarah,
this is Agent Cabe Gallo,
Homeland Security.
You're gonna have
to trust us.
If you keep calling attention
to yourself,
who's ever in there
will see you.
Now, you know
that we can't
get through those doors.
Trust is the only way
this is gonna work.
So we trust you to get
the job done. You trust us
to keep you safe.
Just shut up!
Shut up. Shut up, Cabe.
Walter.
Sylvester,
get Sarah safely back
to the control room.
And, Cabe,
you do not get to tell anybody
to trust you ever again.
Okay. Take it easy.
You slip so easily
into asking people to trust you
when you want something
from them.
Walter,
let's talk about this.
No.
I'm not gonna be tricked
into believing you.
Not a second time.
So, Director,
we'll do everything that we can
to save these people's lives,
but...
once this case is concluded,
I want Agent Gallo
off Scorpion.
I do not want to work
with him ever again.
Uh, bro,
let's take a breath.
No, let's not take a breath.
I want Gallo out, or I quit.
End of story.
What just happened?
Nothing important.
It...
seemed important.
Very important.
Not more than saving the lives
of the people in this facility.
Starting with Sarah,
who needs you to get her
out of that control room.
Sarah, hug the wall to your left
and go to the...
Can we just clarify
that you're saying Cabe
is no longer on the team?
Consider it clarified.
Okay, so we know
that the hacker is sending
e-mails via cell phone.
Let's pull up surveillance
footage of a-a minute prior
to when we received
each e-mail.
Look for, uh,
suspicious behavior.
That's gonna take a minute.
Hey.
We have a job to do.
This is my job.
If he's asking me to
leave the premises,
I will not until the job's done.
Even if he'd said it,
I-I wouldn't pass it on.
I always knew I'd have to tell
him the truth about Baghdad.
He's not the only member
of this team.
He cannot make
unilateral decisions.
It's his worst nightmare.
And mine, too.
Which is why I tried to come
clean 50 times but I didn't
have the guts.
I will do
everything I can
to help mend it. Okay?
The last time took 16 years.
This may be it.
Paige. We may have something.
If you care
to be kept apprised.
Go.
Okay, these are each
of the five zones
of the building.
The threatening e-mails
were received at
8:43, 9:39, and 11:08.
Just before each of them
were sent, this figure
ducks into a blind spot.
He goes beyond the view
of cameras.
He goes somewhere
we can't see him.
30 seconds later
we get an e-mail.
Okay, run the guy
against employee files.
Did Cabe leave?
Is he seriously gone?
He's outside.
Not going anywhere.
Okay. We are looking
at Dr. Simon Boyd.
- Neurobiologist.
- We can't go in guns blazing
on a guy just for e-mailing.
You shouldn't go in
guns blazing at all.
This guy works in Tox Storage.
From this office, he has
the ability to release sarin gas
into any test lab
in this building.
Not just the ability
but the desire.
High profile event,
unattainable demands--
this is more
of a suicide mission
than a hostage situation.
If he's that crazy,
I can guarantee
he's hooked up the Tox Storage
to the entire
ventilation system.
From the specs, it'd
be simple to do.
All right, the only way to take back
the building and open the doors
is to get inside and replace
the server cable that was cut.
No one's been able
to get inside all morning.
Yeah, that's just because we haven't
thought about it hard enough.
There's always an answer--
we just need
to find it.
All the doors are locked,
and I'm assuming this perp--
if he is our perp--
is watching the
surveillance monitors.
He is. He's got access
to all the same footage
- that we do.
- He's absolutely our guy.
Government records say
he started his career
studying the effects
of neurotoxin in Baghdad
16 years ago. He returned
from his trip to Jordan
to find his
entire neighborhood
decimated.
Among the wounded was his
fiancée, left comatose
and on life support
until 18 months ago,
when she died.
Just before he began
working here.
When he started
studying the facility,
finding its weaknesses,
planning his revenge.
Okay, uh, let's all
put our minds toward
finding a way into
the building without passing
surveillance cameras
or opening computerized
doors or sensors.
I know there are
lives at risk.
But you may be
exacerbating that risk
by sidelining
one of the team.
I can fill the gap. He's a distraction.
He's a friend.
Okay, I got it-- level nine
government research lab.
It's required to burn all
its documents because shredded
paper can always be
put back together.
In other words, we go in through
the incinerator because
there's no surveillance on it.
We'll have to go
past a flame burning
at roughly 750 degrees.
We hack the municipal gas line,
shut down the incinerator.
Uh, residual
heat will be intense,
so, uh, we'll need
heat-resistant suits
from the fire department.
How are you
climbing down?
Rope will combust,
cable or chain could
weaken and break.
Guys, what did Elia
give me this morning?
Everything short of an open-mouth kiss.
A magnet. A magnet.
The vent's made of steel
alloy. We need magnets.
Powerful ones.
Those news guys weren't too
thrilled that we dismantled
their edit bays
to get these magnets.
Yeah, well, they'll survive,
the people inside may not.
Sylvester, where are we?
I've got good news
and bad.
Which first?
Uh, the good.
Getting into the municipal system
was a cinch.
Their password is 1234.
The bad is,
this facility has its own
internal natural gas supply.
It's a fail-safe
in case heat-sensitive
experiments are left running
and the city gas goes out.
It will also restart
the incinerator.
Shut down the backup, too.
I could control
the backup if the server cable
was functioning,
but it's not.
How long before the backup
reignites the incinerator?
Three minutes
or 90 seconds,
depending on the model,
which isn't specified
in the blueprints.
Okay, we'll move
fast. Toby, suit up.
Toby, stay here.
Walter,
you're sneaking into
a facility controlled
by a madman.
If you were thinking
logically, versus
emotionally,
the person going with you
would be carrying a gun
and know how to use it. That's Cabe.
I have to
go in with someone I can trust.
Cabe is deceitful and deceptive.
Okay, we'll talk later
about the number of times
he's proved otherwise.
Right now you cannot save anyone
if you're killed the second
you enter the building.
Consider the greater good.
All right. Just say the word
when you're ready.
My own
personal invention:
a soldering pen,
or flip the switch...
and it cuts faster
than an arc torch.
You'll be able to patch
the network cable in no time.
These have a flux output of N52,
so it's gonna take all the upper
arm strength you've got.
It'll be just like
rock climbing.
On magnets. Down a...
blazing hot metal tube.
Why don't we get moving, okay?
Comm's in, everyone.
Got it.
Hey. Good luck.
Gonna need it.
Sylvester, kill the gas.
Walter.
Just keep
conversations
to the bare essentials.
How many times do we have
to save each other's lives
before you realize I'm not the
same guy that made that mistake?
I said only the bare essentials.
Grow the hell up.
People might
die here today and you're
only thinking about
yourself.
Thanks to you,
I don't sleep.
Recurring nightmares...
You think you're the only
one that has those dreams?
You guys are gonna need to fight
later, because the incinerator
just turned back on.
Evidently we're dealing with
the 90-second model. Aah!
Our suits won't protect us
long under these new conditions.
We need to climb up
and regroup.
Walter.
My magnets are slipping.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
what's happening in there?
Excessive heat
causes atoms to speed up,
decreasing
magnetic domains. This
lack of cohesion
weakens magnetic force.
Cut the science lesson. I'm
headed toward a burning furnace!
Walter, I'm losing ground here.
It's 'cause you're
heavier than me.
Guys, we got to come up
with a solution fast.
Okay, they can't go down,
we can't reach them
to pull them back up.
Through the side?
Just throwing ideas out, here.
No, no, that's
brilliant. Walt,
the soldering pen. Slide the
handle switch to torch mode
and it should slice the vent wall.
Leading to what?
If there's a concrete wall
beside the vent it doesn't help.
And that is what's
beside the vent, unless you're
17 feet down from the vent
opening facing north,
where there is a crawl space.
Okay, I put you
about 15 feet down.
And, uh, north
is toward me.
Okay. Okay.
I need a hand free
to operate the torch.
Come on, come on, come on.
Ooh, ooh. Oh.
Walter.
Walter, I'm headed
towards oblivion.
When you get to my foot,
grab hold
and I'll pull you up into
the hole when it's cut.
My weight'll pull you down.
So only grab hold of my foot
after I get a grip on the cut
inside the vent shaft.
All right, here we go.
Kid, where you going?
I'm part of the Scorpion team.
No, this is no place
for you. Come with me.
Sit in my squad car
until I can call your mom.
I got a schoolkid here.
Aah! The heat
is becoming untenable.
Oh, geez. The vent temperature
is nearing 400 degrees.
Kid, I got a few seconds, then
you're gonna be out of reach.
I need more time.
I don't think we have any.
And if that's the case, hear me out.
I have no
intention
of listening to another
apology right now,
'cause we're
getting out of here.
Aah!
Grab onto my foot.
I can't reach it.
Grab on to my foot, climb up.
I... I can't grab it.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Come on, Cabe!
Climb up now!
Come on.
Get up.
They're in.
Thank you, Walter.
Thank you.
We're not finished yet.
Sylvester, lead us
to the server hub.
Come on.
Simon's out of frame again.
I'm guessing he's about
to put our feet
to the fire.
So to speak.
Incoming e-mail.
"You have five minutes to prove
"the president will meet
my demands on live television
"or the hostages are dead.
You have five minutes
until I kill these people."
Walter and Cabe
are at the server hub.
It's up there,
it's up there.
How long?
The server cable will be
repaired in 30 seconds.
Then Sylvester can regain
control of the building. Get to
Zone 5, evacuate
the hostages, then Zone 4,
et cetera, et cetera.
Not to be the voice of doom, but
there's just over four minutes
until Simon releases the sarin.
And he's not looking
at the monitors, so,
Cabe, you need to move now.
Okay, I'll find Simon, keep
him away from the monitors,
and you evacuate the hostages.
The man's psychotic.
I handle the face-to-face.
You know the
evacuation protocols
better than I do. In two minutes
I could probably figure them out
and improve them, but it's time
that we don't have. Cabe, go.
Cabe, stay tight to the wall.
You need to hug the corner
to your left. In front of you
should be the door to the lab.
The Zone 5 hostages are in that room.
Hey, help! Get us out of here!
The server's repaired.
Sylvester, you should have
control of the facility.
I think... I've got it.
The building's ours.
One minute till he
gasses the building.
Walter, you got to hustle
to Simon
or I won't be able
to get these people out.
He's playing the role of
hostage, so you play your role.
Walter, he sees you.
Hey.
Who are you?
I'm with SWAT.
We're trying to figure out
a way to get
everyone out of here.
Simon's not facing the monitors.
Now, Cabe.
Everybody, move fast, move fast.
How did you get in?
I sawed a hole
in the wall of the
incinerator exhaust.
Alone?
One-man rescue team?
That's right.
I'm a recon scout.
Those are the mechanical
overrides, Walter.
He can still
release the sarin gas
even though we have control
of the computer system.
Sly, open the door.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
It's me you want.
I killed your fiancée.
I was responsible
for what happened in Baghdad.
You... are lying to me.
I was the programming contractor
who designed
the targeting system
for the bombs
that killed your fiancée
and everyone else.
It's me you want.
These people are innocent.
No.
No, what I want
is justice for Daliyah.
And that...
you can't give to me.
Gun.
You're not gonna shoot anyone.
You don't want there to be
any more casualties from today
from that bombing.
Now, you're distraught
over your loss.
Simon, I get it.
But you're not a bad man.
Zone 3 is evaced.
I'm all clear here.
I got to go help Walter.
You keep evacuating the others.
Who are you talking to?
Give me that
earpiece.
Now.
Now!
The world
is now gonna see
how she suffered.
Simon, listen to me.
Simon, stop!
He released the sarin.
Now I'm gonna take him outside
and kill this man on live TV!
Move!
Okay.
Uh, guys, the gas
is in Zone 5, which means
you have less than five minutes
to get out of the building.
Sarah, we have to go.
I can't leave him.
There's nothing you
can do for him.
Simon's released the gas.
If it's coming through
the ventilation system,
it kicks on zone by zone,
one at a time
so it doesn't overload.
What zone goes first?
5 down to 1.
Walter's in Zone 1.
How much time do we have?
Only about a minute
per zone. Tops!
By the time Walter and Simon
are outside,
I want sharpshooters on the
bluff across the street
and the rooftop on the other
side of the parking lot.
No way.
I'm three minutes away
from bugging everyone out
for a mile radius of here.
The incinerator's vent
has a hole that you made.
So once the gas
is released into Zone 1,
it can escape from the vents
and kill all of us.
What was that?
Is that a person?
Where?
Middle camera, moving north.
There.
Oh, my God.
That's Ralph.
Ralph is in the building!
How the hell
did he get in there?
What is he doing in there?!
Paige, you don't know
where you're going!
Happy!
He's heading north into Zone 1.
What the hell
is he thinking?
No idea, but he is crawling
into a vent shaft that leads
to the crawl space
that Walter and Cabe
took from
- the incinerator vent.
- Oh, man.
He knows that if that gas
is released in Zone 1,
it will escape through the hole
in the vent.
He's trying to save the city.
Oh, uh, Sly, Walter fixed
the server hub.
You shut down
the incinerator now!
I have spent my life
since the bombing raids
trying to atone for the deaths.
I will not rest
until I have saved
at least that number
that have died.
Please do not add any more lives
to that list.
It's already too late.
The incinerator is shut off.
But I can't see Ralph.
He's off the surveillance grid.
Once the gas is released
into Zone 1, how long before
it escapes through
the incinerator hole?
With average seepage rates,
48 seconds.
I'm calling an evac!
Kid, get off your ass, let's go.
You can go, I will not.
Come on, people, move it.
Let's go, let's go.
Sorry, Sylvester.
Ralph! Ralph!
Mom, I'm almost done!
He's melting the silicone
rubber to seal the hole.
That kid is brilliant.
Okay, without
a thermal fire suit,
even with the incinerator off,
the heat in the vent
is 128 degrees.
A kid Ralph's age
won't last long.
Ralph, you need to climb out
right now!
Right now!
I'm begging you.
Please don't let
any more blood spill
over this Baghdad tragedy.
As soon as you step outside,
you're done, you son of a bitch.
Cabe, we are running out
of time.
There's only ten seconds
until the gas reaches Zone 1.
You're so concerned
for your own life.
Could you imagine if
you cared about other people,
thousands would still be alive.
I wasn't talking about my life.
I was talking about yours.
Nice job, son.
Drop your gun!
Kick it away! I'll
figure out a way
to get you out
of there alive!
Listen to me!
I don't want you to die!
Two seconds, Cabe.
Listen to me!
Drop the gun!
I don't want you to die!
Almost, honey.
You're doing great.
Oh, God.
Sly, the incinerator!
Someone must've pulled
the server cable again
because everything reset!
Faster, Ralph! Climb faster!
Ralph, climb faster.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Whoa.
Ralph!
The magnets!
Ralph, faster, climb!
I can't!
Lower me down. Lower me down.
Whoa!
Ralph,
grab my hand.
Lower!
Okay, pull me up!
Come on, I got you.
Come on. Oh, my God.
What the
hell were you thinking?!
I had to help.
For the greater good.
I'm part of the team.
Oh, God.
Hazmat should have this
building cleaned up
and operative
in a week.
Wrap it up.
Now let's discuss this, uh,
personnel change you demanded.
Hey, Walter!
Hey.
Hey, take care of him.
We'll finish up tomorrow.
Okay.
Let me see it.
Oh, that's the way
a champion looks.
Give me that.
You did a great job.
Okay, buddy, let's go.
Nice work.
Was it?
I saw two more dead
added to the list.
Kid, what happened
when you were 16--
it's the worst thing
I ever did in my life.
I regret nothing more.
I'm not your kid.
Not anymore.
Fine.
Then I'll resign
from Scorpion
effective immediately.
Once again, the government
contractors known as Scorpion
have used
their incredible abilities
to save lives
against staggering odds.
One can only imagine the pride
and sense of accomplishment
they must be feeling right now,
and what's in store for
this unique group of geniuses.
Cabe will be coming
back for these--
government case files.
For shredding,
just like our income.
We will survive, thrive even.
Is there really no way
that he's coming back?
I mean... ever?
Trust was our only bond,
and that's been eroded
way too far.
I don't like being a pessimist.
You're always a pessimist.
But him leaving...
Walt, it's...
not good.
How's the boy?
Uh, resting
with his dad.
Walter?
Yeah.
I can tell that
you're, uh, concerned
about, uh, Cabe's, uh,
departure, but I, uh...
You know it wasn't him who
made this team coalesce.
It was you.
I don't think
I can be here anymore.
Can you repeat
that, please?
Ralph... admires you,
worships you...
Uh-huh.
...copies everything you do,
including putting himself
in mortal danger.
I-I don't think
being here is safe.
Drew was offered
a coaching job in Maine.
I'm going
to recommend he take it.
And you'd go with him?
We would move to Maine, yes.
I appreciate everything
you've done for us.
Do you see what
you're sacrificing by leaving,
by taking Ralph away from us?
I have to think of his safety.
Earlier today, you
invoked the greater good
so that I would
team up with Cabe.
But do you just throw
that term around?
My son nearly died
because he wants to be you.
Is it so awful being me?
Being around me?
I just don't want him
to become you!
What is your solution?
Keep him in a cocoon?
Have him watch you move to Maine
to follow some guy
who's already abandoned
you? That's idiotic!
That guy is his father, Walter.
You are not.
I... I have to go.
Good-bye, guys.
I don't need her.
I don't need Cabe.
Yeah!
Oh, oh!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net