WALTER:
My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
Friday's shipment
was late.
I know. Small snafu.
I'll do my best so it won't
happen again, promise.
Don't do your best, Gary,
do my best, you understand?
Yes, sir.
MAN: Get down!
Everybody down on the ground!
No one move!
Okay, friend,
we're just a safe
manufacturing company.
We don't actually store...
Anyone else want to
explain things to me?
(grunts)
(music playing over speakers)
(music stops)
WOMAN:
Thanks.
(people murmuring)
Don't shoot!
I got it.
(camera clicking)
Patel, you sneaky little creep.
You think a sniper rocket's
gonna take me out?
Once you think I'm gone,
I come back!
Like herpes.
Couldn't you play
something less violent,
like Mario Bros.?
TOBY:
Quiet, Luigi.
Get ready to feel
some pain, son!
Oh, wow, for a second there,
I thought that Cabe
was interrogating someone.
PAIGE:
Ralph doesn't even
act like this
when he plays this game.
Where is Ralph?
Did you drop him off at school?
No. Slept at his
dad's last night.
Oh, that's, um...
good they're, um...
getting on well together;
it's positive.
It is. They're connecting.
It's... it's really good
for Ralph. And Drew.
Speak of the devil.
Oh, hey, guys.
Hey.
Dad got me an erector set.
What?
That is super cool.
Looks like you guys
had a great night.
Box looks old.
Well, it's a
collectible.
It's one of the first
ones Gilbert made.
I had one when
I was a kid.
That was nice.
Yeah, he likes telescopes.
But it is, um...
it's cool though.
You want to go
play with that?
Could I, um, talk
to you for a second?
Mm-hmm.
(phone ringing)
Cabe.
(quietly): Um, I just wanted
to ask you something.
Oh, I've seen
these guys build
a parabolic mic
out of an umbrella.
If they're gonna listen,
they're gonna listen.
Uh... I just wanted to know
if you wanted to have dinner
with me tonight.
Oh.
I... I don't know.
I'm not proposing;
it's just dinner.
Since I got back into town,
we haven't had two minutes
just... us.
But you and I both know
it's... it's not that simple.
So let me think about it.
Absolutely.
Okay.
Yeah.
PAIGE:
Hey.
Sylvester?
Yeah?
Any reason you're not
making eye contact with me?
Yes. I'm uncomfortable
because we eavesdropped.
Way to stay strong, Sly.
It was Toby's idea.
You guys fold like a card table.
It's really not a big deal.
His seed blossomed
in your fertile soil.
The emotional bond
between the two of you
is ever present--
it's a huge deal.
What's a huge deal?
Drew asked Paige out.
Oh.
I didn't say yes... yet,
and it's really not a topic
for public consumption.
WALTER:
Yeah, you're right.
Besides, we got to focus
on work.
Cabe just called
with a new case.
We can drop Ralph off
at school on the way.
Sylvester, stop letting
Toby corrupt you.
(siren wails)
SIMONE:
Gallo.
Well, you look the same as
you did seven years ago.
Not a compliment.
Nothing worse than getting
an insult from a lady.
Thank God
it's coming from you.
(laughs)
TOBY: That's nice-- witty banter.
My favorite kind of banter.
Gang, this is
Agent Simone Taylor
from Interpol;
we worked
an international task
force seven years ago.
Thanks for coming.
You really think
we're dealing with The Ghosts?
Who are The Ghosts?
They're an international,
incredibly effective,
incredibly brutal
gang of thieves.
Jewels, cash, artwork.
If you pay them enough,
they'll steal anything.
And they don't care
who they kill doing it.
Case in point.
They're headed up
by Javier Acosta,
out of Barcelona.
He handpicked his team.
Sounds like a job
for law enforcement.
Or Superman.
Law enforcement's been on
this for over a decade
and have gotten nowhere.
Your team is starting
to get a reputation.
A good one?
Yes.
Let me show you
the crime scene.
PAIGE:
They make safes here?
Complex security systems.
High-end, top of the line,
very expensive.
The Ghosts stole a safe?
No, they just
broke into one.
The system
they breached,
TD-9000--
brand-new technology,
can be used on
any size vault.
More than a dozen interlocking
composite-steel bolts,
reinforced receiving cups,
ten-gear release mechanism.
This could withstand a 9.0 quake
or an industrial thermal lance.
Yes, but our
witnesses said
they got in with
a glass of water.
Th-They did what?
This... just, um...
this could be a...
a theoretical long shot,
but the lock you just described
is as tight as a drum,
which has its strengths
and weaknesses.
Now, water,
put in a confined space,
dips a little bit in the
center-- it's called a meniscus.
So the glass goes
on top of the wheel
casing, and then...
And when the notches align,
there's a slight release
in the tension of the gears
that are wound
so tightly
on this bad boy that release
makes the meniscus move,
the water ripples,
which means
you've hit
a combination number.
CABE:
Some of these systems
can only be purchased by
licensed banking institutions.
Correct.
Since they couldn't test
their water hypothesis at home,
they came to the source.
They saw they were right,
and then they left.
Not without killing
innocent people.
Now they're planning
on hitting up
the banks that have
this system in place.
That's the theory
we're working on.
Do you mind if we look
around a little bit?
No, go ahead.
Okay.
Same as last time--
shrapnel everywhere,
but nothing in the
vault that can help.
Run what you found for DNA.
Even though we both know
what the results will be.
Thank you.
Fill me in.
They leave small
metal boxes behind
in the vault-- IEDs filled
with perchloric acid and oil.
A timer pops, the top opens,
setting off an explosion.
The acid kills any DNA that
might have been left behind,
and the oil
compromises all prints.
Exactly. They're smart.
Maybe.
But they ain't smarter
than my guys.
WALTER: So, they
came to the source
to run a test.
Scientific... method.
You have to respect
their process.
Except for the murder part.
Walter,
I think that going after
these types of people
is not what
we are best suited for.
And it's not just
my fear talking.
It's a question of skill sets.
Duly noted.
(exhales)
Don't touch that!
♪ Scorpion 1x11 ♪
Revenge
Original Air Date on December 8, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Mr. Dodd is alive,
but he's in critical condition.
We've moved Mr. Dodd
into surgery...
Sylvester.
You can call him Sylvester.
Sylvester has shrapnel
in his chest and abdomen.
The heat from the explosion
combined with the acid
burned through his clothes
and scalded his skin.
The blunt force trauma from
striking his head on the floor
has caused swelling
about the brain
but no focal injury.
H-His brain will recover though?
We won't know the extent
of the damage until he's awake.
Do you think he's
gonna make it?
I don't like to speculate.
Speculate anyway.
I don't think we're
communicating the kind
of mind you're dealing with--
this man is a supercomputer.
He's getting
the best care possible.
Excuse me.
Walter.
Hey, Megan.
She's doing her physical therapy
here in the north wing.
She will be
our eyes and our ears.
Meet me at the car.
Wh-Where are we going?
We're gonna work.
Thanks for rushing here.
Yeah. This is so awful.
How is he doing?
Well, he's in surgery.
But you will relay
all information to me?
Anything I hear.
Any decisions that need to be
made, anything on the fly,
and you can't contact me,
I need you to think like me.
How would I respond,
what would I ask.
I'll try.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay.
(sighs)
There's a reason a cop
gets taken off a case
when his partner
gets wounded.
I'm not a cop.
It infuses the investigation
with anger, emotion, revenge.
You get myopic, can't see
the forest for the trees.
See, I don't have
those feelings, so if you...
There is no purpose
to this conversation.
If you expect me
to stand down...
They put our boy
in the hospital.
There's no way any of us
are gonna stand down.
I'm just bringing it
to your attention.
Keep your focus,
or it'll cost you.
Let's find out who else uses
the TD-9000 security system.
That's gonna be
the team's next target.
Let's go.
Drexler Bank in Agoura.
Leeside Savings, Burbank.
Toby.
Toby?
(snaps fingers)
Uh, Business Bank
of Sylmar.
So the sophistication
of the team cuts out
a cash haul--
it's too easy to trace
and too hard to carry.
They're after something small--
jewels or a hard drive.
Is there any word
from your sister, Walt?
I would've told you.
Now please help me eliminate
these possibilities.
The Ghosts do not
sit on their hands.
Their primary strike
will come very soon.
Uh... okay.
So maybe start
with locations. Um...
Proximity to freeways,
airports, the escape routes.
Then we can calculate
the statistical likelihood
of one site
over another, which...
is Sylvester's forte.
I need to take one minute.
We don't have a minute, Toby.
I'm taking one anyway.
I'll be right back.
They need to process
what's happened.
No, they need to use
it. Not to be callous,
but they're the perfect
team to be working on this.
Can you think of anyone
else more invested?
(exhales)
(door opens, closes)
So what's going on, Doc?
Do you think I was
wrong in there?
With Lord Walter?
What's the... psychiatric term
for crapping on one guy
when you're upset
about something else?
Displacement.
I have known Sylvester
since he was 16 years old.
He once sold his entire
comic book collection
just to cover my rent;
and I always told him
I'll pay him back
for that one day.
And you'll get your chance.
Doctor, how is he?
He's stabilized.
But we won't know
the extent of brain function
till he wakes up.
Oh, God.
Could've been worse.
The one-inch piece of shrapnel
that was threatening his heart
lodged in his sternum.
If it hadn't,
he'd be dead.
I'll keep you posted.
Wait.
That piece of shrapnel--
my brother will want to see it.
Nowhere near freeways
or airports.
Leaves us with 38.
Can you please tell Happy
and Toby to get back in here?
They're trying
to work through the fact
their friend's life's in danger.
And so are you,
just in a different way.
Oh.
This branch
was on fire
two weeks ago.
It's being rebuilt.
Walter's doing his job,
and he's doing
it well.
When someone's really
focused like this,
it's best to give
them their space.
Sometimes it's better
to give them time.
We have none. The group
who wounded your friend,
they'll disappear into the ether
and then they will kill again.
(monitor beeping steadily)
I've never seen that
before-- the lining.
We've never recovered
a piece of shrapnel
bigger than a millimeter.
And only metal.
I'm sorry, you're gonna
have to clear this hall.
Too many people...
(slaps fire extinguisher)
Okay, we are
busy here.
It's okay, sir.
We'll be moving on
in just a moment.
It's government business.
Okay, abusing the
fire extinguisher
is another form
of displacement.
We deal with stress differently.
You reminisce, I smash things.
Happy, what do you get
from this?
The Ghosts need an industrial
plastic liner inside those IEDs
to keep the acid from eating
through the metal casing.
An explosion
would normally melt it.
Well, how'd it survive
this time?
It was in Sylvester.
When the IED exploded,
it superheated
all the metal.
The bits that went
into Sylvester cooled down
from, say, 400 degrees
to 150
very quickly because the human
body is good at absorbing heat.
How does it help us?
Polyethylene plastic is
hard as hell to affix to metal.
There are processes,
especially used in car parts.
I know a few guys
who do this quality of work.
But I'll have to
do some research.
There's no time.
These guys,
how long has each
been in the business?
Uh, one guy, 30 years,
the other two about five each.
Well, we'll scratch
the old-timer.
The other two,
either one has kids?
HAPPY:
Neither.
TOBY:
How about doing time?
Dirty John Tucker did a stretch.
The man's name is Dirty
John and he did time.
What the hell
are we playing 20 Questions for?
Good luck with him.
He won't talk.
We'll think of something.
We'll make him talk.
(panting)
(shouts)
What the hell
is going on here, man?
All right.
So, good. I...
I guess now you got the
guy who really knows.
I can go?
Shut up.
The only words coming out
of your mouth
need to be concerning this.
And what the hell is that?
It's not gonna be easy
to crack this guy.
I got nothing to say
to you, bud.
Nada.
(grunts)
(whimpering)
We've narrowed it down.
One of you two guys,
you built the box
that this shrapnel came from.
And I want you to tell me
who it is.
Oh, come on, man.
Are you for real?
I just... I just work
in a plastics factory.
I just want to get out
of here. Please.
You want to go first?
No. Please don't.
No.
(whimpering)
Tell me the truth.
I told you,
I didn't make any boxes...
(shouts)
Oh, God!
(crying):
Oh, God...
(crying)
I swear it wasn't me!
(crying continues)
Oh, God!
Oh, oh, God!
(crying continues)
Okay.
Okay, let's talk.
Was there a reason
you had a fake blood pack
and retractable knife
just lying around?
I had to teach an
old boyfriend a lesson.
Okay, guys, I admit
that I build stuff
for shady people
from time to time.
Lock picks,
smoke bombs.
Incendiary explosive devices?
Those boxes were built
to very detailed specs.
Such as?
Heavy polymer lining
used to handle
powerful non-ionized acids
as well as incineration
under high heats.
He ordered 20.
In my game,
it's best you don't know.
Can't imagine
why they call you Dirty John.
We need the name of the buyer.
He never gave a name.
Look, he's a handsome dude.
He-he spoke
with a Spanish accent, but...
That's him.
Crazy son of a bitch.
(groans) When he showed up
to pick up the package,
I told him
I needed an extra hour.
He went nuts,
shoved a gun right in my mouth.
Something's off.
Javier's cold-blooded,
but shoving guns in people's
mouths sounds emotional.
Javier never loses
his cool.
When you do that,
people remember you.
Exactly. He slipped up,
and now we have everything we
need to find their next target.
How do you figure?
Javier received
20 incendiary devices
from Dirty John, but when
The Ghosts hit the safe factory,
they only used 15.
Meaning he has five left.
The Ghosts are nothing
if not efficient.
Now, if each incendiary device
wipes out exactly
14-and-a-half feet
of evidence, then...
HAPPY:
We narrow our search
by figuring out which vault
requires exactly five devices.
Happy, we need the blueprints
for every bank on that wall.
Size of the vault
is key.
Already on it.
We need to scan
for spatial parameters.
He really is
on fire today.
Fire is exactly
what Sylvester needs.
(monitor beeping steadily)
MEGAN:
Come on, big guy.
Wake up.
We were just starting to get
to know each other. (chuckles)
Just open your eyes.
Come on.
Blink for me.
Sylvester?
(monitor beeping rapidly)
(alarm beeping)
Oh, my God. Nurse!
Get me two milligrams
of Lorazepam, stat!
Pulse is 66 and strong.
Intact.
No signs of dehiscence.
MEGAN: That's everything the
doctors have told me so far.
How bad was the seizure?
A grand mal
caused by the swelling
in his brain.
And what's his status?
They're not sure.
No way to tell yet.
I'm sorry, Walter.
Okay, thank you for the update.
We need to keep
it together.
We have to focus.
It isn't healthy to pretend
we're not hurting.
You want to talk about hurting?
Sylvester is hurting,
so take a moment if you need to,
and then get back
to scanning those blueprints.
Hey, wait.
Let him take a beat.
You have no
idea how close
we might be to
catching these guys.
And then what?
You ever think
what we'll do
the day after we catch them?
You can't be so driven
that you don't see
the next step ahead of you
or what you're doing
to other people
while you chase your goal.
For me, it's Taekwondo.
But if this Good Will Hunting
thing is how you vent...
Whatever works.
Just trying to stay sharp.
I get it.
There's a lot more answers
on that board
than there are in your friend's
hospital room.
You're pissed.
You know, I don't, uh...
I don't... get pissed.
Ah.
Well, you could
have fooled me.
Seven years ago,
my partner and I were tailing
Javier and his crew.
When we got close,
they practically cut him
in half with bullets.
I'm sorry
about your friend.
He's, uh...
He's spent every day since
in a wheelchair,
drinking meals
through a straw.
(clears throat)
What you're feeling right now,
I still feel every day.
How do you deal with it?
Focus.
For seven years, catching
these guys is the last thing
I think about when I go
to sleep at night
and my first thought
when I wake up.
I'm not saying
you can't grieve.
I'm saying
you can't grieve now.
These people can't get away.
They won't.
And when we finally
lock them up...
well, I've been fantasizing
about calling my partner
to give him the good news,
and then finally relaxing
with a stiff drink...
knowing I've done my job.
You know, after
seven years, uh,
you deserve a
stiff drink.
About earlier...
Me, too. Let's move on.
Bigger fish.
Okay, what do you got?
I just scanned
the last of institutions
with TD-9000 security.
Not a one of them
is small enough
to be completely wiped out
by five of those
acid-bath canisters.
Mm.
Maybe we're looking
at this wrong.
Maybe when they hit
the safe factory,
it wasn't a test run.
It was an announcement.
They were getting word out
that they cracked the TD-9000,
and they were planning
to hit another one.
TOBY: And if you
had something
you knew The Ghosts wanted
in the TD-9000 vault,
you got to move it quick.
And an armored car's
cubic footage can easily
be taken out
by just five of these IEDs.
Boom, now we're cooking
with salt.
HAPPY: Damn right. We start
with this company.
The biggest armored car
service in L.A. County.
Well, let's call and see
who got a truck.
MAN: I only had one
new booking today.
Safe deposit box move.
Client by the name of Huertavas.
Let me pull up the job details.
Oh, my God.
That's it.
A few years back,
a Venezuelan cartel boss named
Huertavas hired The Ghosts
to steal a fortune
from his rival.
They grabbed $100
million cash.
Deal was, Ghosts would get
a third cut.
Let me guess. Senor Huertavas
wasn't a man of his word.
He double-crossed them.
They barely got out
of Venezuela alive.
Probably right around
the time they swore revenge.
A team on a revenge mission--
sounds familiar.
SIMONE:
Rumor is,
Huertavas converted
the cash into diamonds
and hid them
somewhere in the U.S.
A hundred million in diamonds
would fit
into a safe deposit box.
I got it. Got it.
Client ordered safe deposit box
number 1840, moved out
from Santa Monica Trust & Loan.
And what time
was the pickup?
Log says it was made
five minutes ago.
Headed east on Olympic now,
turning south on Barrington.
Okay, okay, you need
to call the workers.
Tell them they're in danger.
We're on our way.
I know we want to get the guys
who hurt Sylvester, but...
let's not forget who we are.
MAN:
Vehicle 117, come in.
(tires screech)
What the hell?!
Vasquez, DeLongpre,
do you copy?
(automatic gunfire)
It's going to give!
We got to return fire!
(automatic gunfire continues)
♪ ♪
(siren wailing)
HAPPY:
There's two down.
Animals.
Homeland. You got
a 20 on the perps?
Three bikes fled west on Grand.
Highway Patrol's setting up
a roadblock
at the Sepulveda Overpass.
They're gonna ditch the bikes
before we get there.
Advantage?
Three-minute head start.
(monitor beeping steadily)
(grunts softly)
Sylvester. Hi!
Oh, thank God you're awake.
Where...
where's Walter?
Right now I think
he's got his hands full.
We got to get them now.
Once they hit the freeway
or the hills,
they're too maneuverable
on those bikes.
So we cut them off.
(horns blaring)
Head down to 22nd.
Everybody hang on.
(tires screeching)
They're headed right for you.
I see them.
(tires screeching)
Walter, be careful!
You all right?
I wedged my phone
in his backpack.
Nicely done.
WALTER:
Okay, they're going down Tenth.
We can cut them off on Sixth.
All right, this is Homeland
Security Agent Cabe Gallo.
The perps are headed
toward Sixth and Tenth.
We're on our way.
(sirens wailing)
OFFICER: This is LAPD.
We have no sighting
at Sixth and Tenth Street
location.
Wait. That's impossible.
The signal says they're passing
through right now.
They should see
three motorcycles.
I'm not wrong.
We're half a mile
from the L.A. Aqueduct.
They're in the sewers.
They're underground.
They're heading down Pico
towards Santa Fe.
According to
the county DWP match,
there's an outlet hatch
by the Sixth Street tunnel.
JAVIER: We ditch the bikes,
and we're gone.
How the hell did he find us?
Surprise, jackass!
Okay, you know what to do.
CABE: You take Javier,
we'll take the other two.
Can't keep up
with these motorcycles.
Let me out.
What?
That's Broadway up ahead.
What the hell are you gonna do?
HAPPY:
I'll think of something.
Flushing them back down
toward me.
Oh, come on, come on.
(tires screeching)
Look out! Look out!
(automatic gunfire)
He dropped the gun.
(engine revving)
Okay. Uh...
87 miles per hour, 150 yards.
Three, two,
one.
You move, I shoot!
Oh, yeah.
Sometimes you got
to smash stuff.
I'm gonna follow him.
You head to the north side
and head him off.
(tires screech)
Hey! Hey!
(sirens wailing in distance)
(tires screeching in distance)
Help me.
Please, pull me up.
Help me!
Help me.
(screams)
(gasps)
(indistinct
police radio chatter)
You all right?
Yeah, yeah, I made a...
made a move to save
him, and I couldn't.
Right.
Pushed him hard today.
We were all trying
to do the right thing.
CABE: Case like this,
if you don't close it,
it becomes a sore--
won't heal.
I didn't want
him to have that.
What happened
on the roof...
I don't feel bad
about what happened.
You know me, I don't... I don't
have those kind of feelings.
I got to go see Sylvester.
Oh, there he is.
Man, you'd just do anything
to get out of work, huh?
Hey, pal.
How you doing, kid?
Good. I'm on morphine.
(laughs)
We missed you today.
Could have used
you on the case.
What's in the box?
Oh, something I have
owed you for six years.
Super Fun Guy comics.
First 50 issues.
Silver Age classics.
Toby, that's
your whole paycheck.
I know, and
it's making me sick.
I'm gonna go now,
'cause I'm a doctor,
and I know
you need your rest.
Otherwise, I'd be staying
here all night, pal.
The rest of you clowns,
let this guy sleep.
Okay.
See you tomorrow,
Sylvester.
I'm not gonna kiss you.
(chuckles)
Take care, kid.
Thanks.
So my sister's taking
good care of you?
The best.
Yeah, I thought
she would.
Uh, one question before I go.
Um, quick brain teaser,
see how the
cranium's feeling.
Walter, the doctor
said he's fine.
Fire away.
Okay, so if a man weighing
160 pounds, with an arm span
of 69 inches and a height
of 72 inches reaches
down at a 90-degree
angle to, uh, pick up a man
weighing 200 pounds,
could he lift him?
That's not a brain teaser.
Megan told me what happened
on the roof.
That weight,
that angle,
he would have pulled you over.
Right, but I didn't
know that when I, uh...
hesitated.
Bye, Megan.
I'll see you
at work, Sylvester.
Okay, so...
do you like to fall asleep
with the TV on?
Fluff your pillows?
(panting)
Um...
I never felt safe anywhere
on Earth except for Scorpion.
And now not even there.
How can I go back to work?
You can't tell Walter.
Okay.
I'll help you get through this.
We'll get through this
together.
Hey. What are you doing here?
Checking on your friend.
The nurse said
he'll make a full recovery.
Yeah.
Walter, I've been
waiting seven long years
for that drink I told you about.
Would you have it with me?
I'd like that. Yeah.
♪ ♪
Hey, you remember this?
(humming tune)
(laughs)
Not since
I was pregnant.
“Drew, I need salty-sweet.
I need salty-sweet.”
(laughs)
I had no idea what
you were talking about.
I had the
weirdest cravings.
Ralph built
an incredibly realistic
suspension bridge with
that erector set I got him.
Gave me detailed instructions
on how I could help.
Hmm. Maybe he'll
be an engineer.
As long as he's happy.
You know, I think, um...
a lot about
what it would have
been like if I hadn't left.
Paige.
I know you.
Your mind is
somewhere else tonight.
I'm just
thinking about...
today.
Walter?
The whole team.
Rain check?
I'd really like one.
♪ ♪
I called
my old partner's wife.
She relayed the good news.
Said she thought
she saw a smile.
(chuckles softly)
I think your friend Paige
might be right
about waking up tomorrow
and not knowing
what to do with myself.
Well, I'm confident
that you'll find
a new quest for,
uh, justice.
Thank you.
Couldn't have
done it without you.
Anytime.
You know where
to find me now.
My plane doesn't leave
till the morning.
We could take this celebration
back to my hotel.
(sighs)
Simone, you're...
you are smart,
you're impressive,
you're, uh...
you're beautiful.
I'm flattered.
But, um...
...there's somewhere else I-I
feel I need to be tonight.
Okay.
Hi.
Uh, I'm here
to visit Sylvester Dodd.
Okay, uh, friend or family?
Family.
(monitor beeping steadily)
Hi.
You guys are here, too?
Submit your sitter's bill.
I'll call it research.
We'll get Homeland cover it.
There's the one where Super
Fun Guy meets Dr. Power Pants.
We saved this
one for you.
Thanks.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net