My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
Think we should go east.
That's west.
Well, still should go that way.
Yeah?
Based on what?
This is your fault!
You had to take us
off the trail.
You had to see
that damn waterfall!
I thought I knew
where I was going.
Oh, well, a lot of good
that does us now, huh?
Day and a half with no water,
food or cell reception.
And the kids are terrified.
And you two
aren't helping.
Let's just keep moving
and try to get
back to a road.
We'll get you out of here.
I promise.
Whoa!
Winds of Santa Ana.
She's a-blowin' a-leeward
and a-windward.
That is sailor talk.
Actually, those terms
just relate
to one's position
to the wind.
It's not exclusive
to sailing.
In fact,
I'm about to show you
how it applies
to aeronautics.
State the wager.
Down the telephone wires,
straighten at ground level,
then across the street
and through that window.
You're on.
If I win, dinner date.
If you win, I do your laundry
for a month.
You'd probably like that
more than the dinner, perv.
I'm feeling Greek,
maybe Tex-Mex.
The bet is null and void
on account of that truck.
You said you'd get
it in the window,
and it ain't
in the window.
I'm the gambling expert.
We be datin'.
Ooh, great.
Coffee's ready.
Oh.
Yes.
Mmm. Perfect.
Thanks, Walter.
Walter, a minute of your time.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Mmm.
Oh. What is this?
This is outreach.
Now, as you know, Drew comes
back from Portland soon.
He's gonna come back full
of confidence and swagger.
And what did those alpha-jocks
all want?
The cheerleader.
AKA Paige Dineen.
Why is Paige's personal life
my concern?
Right here is why.
I've been collecting data
on your shifting
behavior patterns
the past few months,
and the result is
an iron-clad theorem that proves
you have feelings for Paige.
That's preposterous.
Said the climate-change denier
in the face of
scientific evidence.
While you're at it, how 'bout
you get no vaccines today?
You want to take
this for a spin?
Remember the reservation
you made for
a Valentine's Day
“work dinner”?
We never ended up
having the meal.
Okay.
How about the new
lavender diffuser
in your office?
That is to mask the smell
of experiment-generated
mouse urine.
That's disgusting.
But also a lie.
Paige loves lavender.
That hand cream of hers
is always stinking up the van.
Finally...
...Coffea arabica.
Why do you think I've
been getting my Joe
at Kovelski's?
Because you put cinnamon
in our pot here.
It has antioxidants
and improves brain function.
Cinnamon's for elves.
You put cinnamon
in the coffee
because she likes it.
You're giving her
special treatment,
which can only mean...
And how old are you?
13 months older than you,
so show your elders respect.
What is...
What is with
the almost constantly commenting
on me and Paige lately?
It's borderline obsessive.
As a student of human behavior,
I find emotional dishonesty
offensive.
And also, you're
my friend.
Also, I don't like Drew.
You're not saved
by the bell.
Yeah, Cabe.
Got a case, urgent.
We got six hikers
from a church group
lost in Los Angeles
National Forest.
Been missing for 36 hours.
Santa Ana winds are kicking up
the forest floor,
killing visibility.
Search and rescue
is damn near impossible.
LAFD and the Forest Service
need an assist.
I was thinking
your tracking software
from the Baghdad operation
years back--
maybe dusting that off.
Winds have gotten
worse since we spoke.
We don't have
any time to waste.
Must be the hikers' families.
Alongside members
of their church.
My system uses a camera
and laser scanners
to conduct advanced
ground imaging
that can penetrate
tree cover
and recognize ground patterns
at high altitudes.
Basically, our
stuff sees good.
You built this for fun?
Well, let's just say I, uh...
I modified an old system
from way back.
My guys will
locate the hikers,
radio in the coordinates;
the rescue team can do its job.
We need
to see whatever
your people have done so far.
It's an interesting use
of my Baghdad software.
How did you think to apply it
to this situation?
The truth is,
I think about what happened
in Baghdad a lot.
What happened
between us.
Maybe your tech--
some good can come from it now.
Walter, you got to see this.
One of the kids
tweeted a picture
right before they went
on the hike.
They've been out of cell range
ever since.
Well, that's all we need
to find the hikers.
How?
You've been looking
for where the hikers are.
That's one specific place
in a specific moment in time,
and it's constantly moving.
The footprints, however,
they can last for hours,
even in this wind,
and they could be
a road map right to them.
Breakdown?
Okay, so these treads
are the kids' sneakers.
Two are piece-wise lines,
other is
a cross-hatch pattern.
Approximate sizes:
two boys' size nine
and a girls' six.
The adults are
wearing hiking boots
with standard waffle patterns,
and the woman's got
an outside heel break.
Scan the images.
One of the men will be in
front, one of them in back.
It's standard defense formation,
wired into animal DNA--
they don't even know
they're doing it.
That woman will
most likely be
with the youngest girl-- a
mothering instinct to protect.
If you look at the,
uh, body language
of these two youngsters here,
they're in love.
They're side by side.
You can tell they're in love
just from the photo?
Oh, I can tell
lots of ways.
The others will
follow standard
pack formation and fall in
here and here.
We'll be looking
for a shape like this
filled with tread patterns
that we can distinguish from
mountain lion drag marks,
windswept debris.
That'll let us
find our folks.
Uh, where's our workstation?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
Walter, I am not
going up in that thing.
Helicopters have
zero aerodynamics
and no glide ability
in case of engine failure.
That's our
only choice.
It's a box
held up in the sky
by a lawnmower blade. Pass.
Hope you're up for a
little handholding today.
Sly, we need you.
No one can run
the analytics
as fast as you can.
Walter, I want to help,
but I can't willingly
board a death trap
designed by
Leonardo da Vinci
500 years ago.
Then stay here!
'Cause I got a strict
no-crybabies policy.
Meet your pilot,
Marcus Bronson.
Look, you
don't want to come,
don't come,
but once you get on board,
you need keep it together,
you understand?
It's serious
business up there.
I can't have anyone
freaking out in my bird.
Hey, what'd you mean,
our pilot? You're not coming?
There's no room in the cabin.
So I'll stay back and
gear up with the rescue team.
Once you send in
the hikers' locations, we go in.
This is a sat phone.
Works where the
cell phones don't.
Keep it close to you.
It's your lifeline.
Hey!
You scratch it, you buy it.
He's fun.
Are you good?
Sure.
Okay. Let's go.
Okay.
We know you have
a lot of choices when you fly,
so we want to thank you
for flying with Air Scorpion.
Please, no
unnecessary words.
Big guy barfs, you guys
are cleaning it up.
Everything's going to be fine.
Just look at your laptop and
avoid peripheral vision, okay?
Now, our predictive model
says they headed downhill
west-southwest,
with a statistical
likelihood of 94%,
so bank west here.
I got a hit.
Happy, you seeing this?
Yup.
The treads match our hikers.
The formation they're walking in
is spot on with my prediction.
Okay, pilot,
stay the current course
while we close in on them.
Ooh.
Everything okay?
Wind's up to 50 knots.
It's gonna get bumpy.
Hold on.
Cabe, do you copy?
Copy, Walter.
It's good news.
We found the hikers' trail.
Within minutes, we find them.
That's great work.
What's your location?
Hey, Captain Charisma,
where are we?
Damn it!
Wind shear! Hold on!
Base, this is Eagle!
Do you copy?
Copy. Copy. We copy.
Do you read?
We have equipment fail...
Wind's wreaking havoc
on the comms.
Walter! Walter, do you copy?!
We're gonna die!
No one's gonna die.
Mayday!
Base, this is Eagle!
We are in distress!
Repeat-- we are in distress!
We're heading right
for those trees!
No, no, no, no, no!
You steer away from the pines!
Aim for that! The Sheoak!
It's softer!
We'll have a much better
chance of survival!
Walter, 500 feet! 400 feet!
You got to trust me!
Do it now! Do it now!
- Oh, my God! Oh!
- Oh, my God.
What the hell
are you doing?!
Heads down! Heads down now!
Everybody, hold on!
We're going in!
♪ Scorpion 1x19 ♪
Young Hearts Spark Fire
Original Air Date on March 23, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oh.
My duodenum.
- Everyone all right?
- I'm okay.
Check.
Terrified,
but breathing.
Okay.
Watch our weight
distribution
or the bow breaks
and this cradle falls.
You okay, boss?
I've been better.
How bad?
Uh, bright blood,
outer left side of the thigh.
Looks like he nicked
the femoral artery,
but it's clotted off,
stabilized.
How would you
know that?
If it hadn't,
you'd be dead.
But that cut could expand.
We need to leave the metal in.
You do a tourniquet,
and I'll clean it up
when we get on the ground.
We need to get you
to a hospital ASAP.
Great in theory, but we are
40-feet high in a tree.
And our comms are dead.
I doubt they got
a location on
our crash site.
I can take care of that,
but I'm gonna need everyone
to cut off their seatbelts.
Sly, I need you to do
some math for me.
Okay, based on
the angle of the tree
and the weight
distribution, uh,
estimated by the
barycenter balancing point,
as well as the relatively
weak tensile strength of
the River Sheoak, which is
really no more than a weed...
Focus.
Okay.
Bottom line is we need to remove
the weight strategically, or
we're all going to topple over--
like Don't Tip the Waiter.
So, best guess is Happy,
then me, then Toby,
then Marcus needs to take
some weight off the nose,
then Walter,
and then lastly Paige,
because the weight displacement
in the cabin is less.
Happy,
make it happen.
Whoa!
We're fine!
Everything's fine.
When I go down,
this thing is gonna shake.
Just keep
your heads straight.
We should be good.
“Should.” Fantastic.
Made it!
You're up, Sylvester!
You know what?
I think my calculations
were off, Happy!
I should go last!
No, your calculations
were perfect,
and this thing's not gonna
hold much longer, okay?
So you go now.
You're gonna be fine, Sly.
Okay.
Think happy thoughts.
Geez.
Oh, my God.
Come on! You can do it!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
I can't go any further!
I can't... I can't go
any further!
Just straighten your legs.
Hurry, guys!
All this movement
is cracking
the support branches!
Okay, you're up.
Sylvester said I go last.
You're going. Now.
No.
No, we should do...
we should do
what Sylvester said.
No, you go.
Now. Go.
Go!
Oh, my God.
Okay.
That's the wrong order!
That is the wrong order!
Hey, Walt, you better hustle!
Walter, you've got seconds until
that helicopter is in free fall!
The support branches
are breaking!
- Walter!
- Walter! Walter!
Uh...
looks as if things haven't
gone according to plan.
We call in our location
on the SAT phone,
Cabe gets us, we regroup.
We might not get the reception
we're looking for on this model.
I have to tighten the tourniquet
almost on top of the wound;
it's gonna hurt.
I think you and I have
different definitions of pain.
Okay. So we're here.
And with the tree cover,
there's no way a chopper
can land or airlift us out.
Only suitable
evac point is here.
It's Fiddler's Basin;
it's due east.
It's that way.
How do you know that?
I point the hour hand
at the sun, I bisect the angle
between the hand
and the 12 to find south.
I know south,
I know every other direction.
Okay, so...
we can't contact Cabe,
but we have to assume
that he's
thinking like us
and he knows that Fiddler's
Basin is our only shot.
So, we follow the
hikers' footprints.
We find them, and then we send
an overground rescue team back
for Sylvester
and the pilot.
Oh, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!
You're leaving me here with him?
No way.
You can't walk.
Toby has to come with us
just in case there are
any injured hikers.
I do not like this plan.
We're in desolate woods--
no food, limited water
and no comms.
Right.
Then you two can work on
getting a radio sorted
while we're gone.
Well, we're well aware
things would be easier
if we still had that SAT phone,
but that is not the case.
What was with
the swipe at me?
Well, if you had been
holding on
to the SAT phone
instead of me,
we would never be
in this mess right now.
I was protecting you.
It was instinctive.
It was stupid.
You were an unbuckled,
150-pound projectile.
154-- I've been
working out.
Let's get moving!
Sun sets in
47 minutes.
Okay, so... I'll just stay here
in the middle of the woods
with the grumpy guy.
Hey, stop your bellyaching,
go fix that radio.
Go on!
Sir, we spotted
the chopper's tail
through a break
in the tree canopy.
Cover's too thick.
Can't make out any survivors.
Show me a topo map!
Yes, sir.
If they survive,
you think they'll try
to keep with the mission?
There's no “if.”
My guys survived.
Here, Fiddler's Basin.
Only viable evac point.
Three miles from the crash site.
That's where we land.
Not in this wind.
At 55 knots,
everything is grounded.
Transport helo
can handle it.
County doesn't
have one.
Then I'm reaching out
to Pendleton.
There's no way I'm leaving
my guys down there!
Hikers, we're here
to rescue you!
Whoa, whoa.
So, based on the prints,
one of them
is favoring the right foot,
partly dragging the other;
they're probably injured.
Yeah, that's a
size six shoe
with a shallow depression.
That's Caitlin, the lightest.
If she's hurt, they can't
be traveling that fast.
We will find them.
Oh, by the way,
uh, they really
stuck to that
cluster pattern you predicted.
You were right on the money.
Most of my behavioral
predictions turn out to be true.
For instance, what you did for
Paige up in the copter. Huh?
Letting her go first, putting
yourself at risk for her.
I was not giving Paige
special treatment.
I watched you almost get
pancaked by a falling aircraft.
You ignored Sylvester's
calculations--
math and science-- so that
she could descend first.
Can we focus
on finding the hikers?
Of course.
Okay.
May I have some of water?
Oh, yeah.
The... agreed-upon ration.
Same as
everyone else gets.
We're all equal.
Thank you.
Wow, you really
learned me there, boss.
You clearly
don't like her.
Guys, we got a problem!
The trail ends here.
The hikers crossed this field.
They could've entered
up those woods at any point,
headed in any direction.
We have no way
of finding them now.
Wait, shh, shh, shh.
Over there.
How do you know?
It's very scientific.
I heard them.
These kids
can't go much further.
Maybe we split--
increase the odds
of some of us getting rescued.
Yeah, maybe.
I don't know.
I don't know
what to do.
Hey.
Heard you guys are lost.
Oh, thank God.
Thank you!
Okay. Okay.
How come he always gets the hug?
I'm standing right next to him.
Are you guys with
the Forestry Service?
No, no.
We're here with the government;
we're here to bring you home.
How?
Well, we're gonna take you
to a nearby clearing;
there are people
who will meet us there.
Okay, let's go.
Toby, can you check
on the girl
with the hurt leg?
Let me get them some water.
Okay, let's go, kid.
What is this?
I collect rocks.
These have
boracite in them.
I'm bringing them
home with me.
Not anymore you're not.
We're hiking for miles--
no extra weight.
Okay, one rock.
Okay, are we ready?
Yeah?
Okay, let's go.
Toby?
Okay, you need to strip
those input wires.
I don't have any wire strippers.
Just use your teeth
and your fingernails.
This is incredibly unsanitary.
Unsanitary? Really?
I ate grubs and worms
for five days
on a military exercise
when I was your age.
Good for you.
No, great for me,
because I learned to do
what needs to be done.
Copy. Come in.
Oh, my God.
Hello?
Oh, my God,
you hear that?!
Don't talk to me,
talk to them! Talk to them!
Hello, do you
copy? Hello?
Come in, please.
Hello? Come
in, please.
Come on, come
on, come on.
I'm sorry.
What?
You're not gonna
say anything?
I already said
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I get it. I get it.
Maybe if I rewired
the entire radio
with my mouth
full of beetle larvae,
maybe then I would have
done a better job for you.
Kid, kid, look, look.
Oh, no.
You smell smoke?
There must be
a fire somewhere.
Is that an ember?
Whoa.
Ah, that was close.
Um, Walter.
Yeah?
Oh, boy.
You need to hurry up kid!
I'm well aware that a
forest fire can spread
at 22 feet per second.
Fire's circling
around us.
That loop closes,
then we're cooked, literally.
Okay, I just need to
secure one more seat belt.
All right.
And you're okay to lay
on this on your back?
Of course I am.
Great.
Hey, take my arm,
take my arm, okay?
Your leg has a lot
more blood on it.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Just get me on there.
Easy, easy.
Strap yourself
in there.
You sure this is gonna hold?
It only needs to hold us
for three miles
until Fiddler's Basin.
Your friends took the map.
You remember where it is?
I have a photographic memory.
Of course you do. Let's go!
Let's go!
My eyes are burning.
It's getting
hard to breathe.
Okay, hold on.
Will you grab that out?
Grab that.
Okay, now hold that up
to your nose and mouth.
Here you go.
Whoa, what the hell
are you doing?
I'm helping you, like I was
trying to on the helicopter.
That's all, just help.
I do not need someone
to take care of me.
Hey.
You kissed me.
And now that
I'm responding to that,
you're scared
and shutting down.
I am surrounded by fire.
We have kids to save,
not to mention ourselves.
Not the time.
What's up?
See for yourself.
What now?
There's got to
be a way around.
We'd be moving laterally as
the fire proceeds in this way.
If we pick the wrong
direction, then...
We're dead.
How long would
you say we have?
We've got
about ten minutes.
to get across.
Start looking for long branches
strong enough to hold us.
Maybe we, uh,
we bind them together,
then we reach across.
Oh, bro, that sounds
like suicide.
Staying here is suicide.
Come on,
start looking.
Walter, I'm sorry,
this is all my fault.
You didn't start the wildfire.
I took everyone off the
trail, got everyone lost,
all because I wanted to
find the perfect spot
for Jenna, to
propose to her.
And now she's gonna
die, everyone,
because of me.
You want to undo that?
Help us get over that ravine.
All right?
What's she doing?
Any of you guys ever rope-swing?
I-I got to catch my breath.
It's on account
of the smoke.
You got to push
through it, kid,
'cause I'm looking at a blaze
coming over that hill
right toward us.
It's faster than I am.
I can't outrun it.
Like hell you can't!
Now get your ass
in gear now! Move!
Don't yell at me.
I'm about to burn to death!
Now grow a pair, son,
and Oscar Mike now!
Stop.
Military talk and berating
won't work with me.
It never has.
I have done the calculations!
My fastest rate of speed,
the decline angle of this hill,
the pace of the fire,
the dryness of the underbrush--
a gazelle would be
taken in minutes.
You and I have seconds!
Son, doing nothing isn't
an option for either of us.
Listen to me.
We got to figure a way
to move faster than this fire,
or we're both dead.
Do you understand?
We can't,
but we may not need to.
Okay, at least the
hold is secure.
Can't help but notice
you haven't swung out yet.
Yeah, about that--
this tree could totally
be rotted out inside.
A person's weight
could snap it in half.
Yeah, and fall 50 feet to their death.
Yup.
We've got to do something;
the fire's getting closer.
Well, unless we got
a human guinea pig
who wants to test
this thing out...
Whoa.
Yeah.
It'll hold.
It's getting closer.
We got to move faster.
I know, I know.
Let's go!
Okay. Here.
Are you sure
about this?
Yes. Back in here.
Watch your head.
Thanks.
Oh. Okay, okay.
We're gonna be baked alive in here.
No.
The door's made of titanium;
it's a low conductor of heat.
You better be
right, kid.
Oh, my God!
Get down!
Get down! Cover!
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Careful with your leg.
Okay.
You okay?
Breathing.
Barely.
Oh, man, your leg's
losing a lot of blood.
I have to tighten
your tourniquet.
Do your worst.
That should hold
it for a bit.
Thanks.
I got to hand it to you,
that was quick thinking
with the pipe.
We got to move.
This door has been
warped by the heat.
I think I can fix it.
Hey, hey.
Use this.
Thank you.
So I take it your dad
was military?
Very.
You guys didn't
get along too well?
Well, my father comes from a
world where a man is measured by
how many tackles
he made in high school
or how many beer cans
he can crush against his skull.
Same world that you come from.
Okay, guys, about a
quarter mile, we dogleg right,
then it's a straight
shot from there.
About, uh, 500 feet,
five percent grade.
Okay, Toby?
Follow. Great.
Come on, guys, got to
make it to the clearing.
Let's start rationing out the
water-- give us a little lift.
You can take my share
if you want.
No. You need
as much as anyone.
Thank you though.
Walter, get down here! The
basin's just around that bend.
This is the only way through.
This gully is
creating a funnel effect
that's pulling
the fires together.
We got to run.
Okay, okay.
Come on. Come on, guys.
You heard her.
Come on!
Hurry, the wall's closing!
You're okay.
Walter!
Jimmy, you're okay!
I'm fine, I'm fine.
You got to be careful.
You don't want
to burn out.
Too soon?
Guys, the fire's gonna fill up
the clearing before we know it.
We got to move.
Over there, come on!
Hold up! Wait.
We're stuck.
All right.
Stop, stop, stop.
This contraption of yours
isn't going anywhere.
Okay.
Give me a second.
Let me see if I can fix it.
No, no.
Stop. Just stop.
Look, I'm dead weight.
You're dead on your feet.
We're out of water.
You're cramping up.
At this rate,
we're not gonna go
another ten inches,
let alone another mile.
I'm not going to abandon you.
It's not your call.
This gully is filling up
with smoke.
There will not be
enough oxygen left.
If I leave you, you will die.
We both die if you stay.
What are you doing?
I'm saving your life, son. Go!
Go.
We're coming up
on the crash site.
Light it up!
I'm sorry, Agent.
Staying ahead of this fire,
even for smoke jumpers,
would be damn near impossible.
Take us to Fiddler's Basin.
We'll be flying right
into the fire front.
Visibility will be low to nil.
I don't see any bodies
by the chopper.
Now, my guys are survivors.
Don't make me ask again.
Let's head to the basin.
We can't make it to the basin.
We can't go back.
Oh, my God.
We're trapped.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Shh, shh.
Listen. Listen.
A helicopter.
It's Cabe.
Hey!
They're never gonna see us
through the smoke.
Flashlights. Flashlights!
Hey!
I don't see anybody.
You?
Not yet.
That fire line
to the west
is cutting off any
route into that basin.
Wherever they are,
they are not making
it to the clearing.
Sir, soot can
choke our engine.
Respectfully,
there is no point
in all of us dying.
We need to go, sir.
Hey!
Come on!
Pete, Pete, Pete.
Her hand.
Give me the ring that you
were gonna put on that hand.
The engagement ring.
I need that diamond.
Give me the diamond.
Congratulations.
Toby.
What are you thinking?
We need to create
a signal flare.
And what is
the one element
that we have
in spades around here?
That would be fire.
Exactly.
And thanks to Jimmy,
we have boron.
Now, fires out there
are burning upwards
of 4,000 degrees.
Boron melts at 3,700.
You insured that, right?
Boron also has
a deoxidizing effect...
...on white gold,
all of which
combine to form
a green plume of smoke!
Come on. Come on.
There!
Right there! A signal!
Where?
Right there! Green smoke!
They're still alive!
Turn it around!
Turn around!
Douse those in water
and hold over your faces.
This one's empty.
So is my canteen.
Oh, we're losing the signal.
Oh, God, this is it.
Happy, I'm not
gonna apologize
for what I did earlier,
'cause I wanted to protect you.
By now, I figured
you'd know why,
but in case you don't know,
I want my last words
to have some meaning.
So, Happy Quinn, I am in love...
Perfect timing.
Let's go! Let's go!
Got our chopper 20 yards south!
Where's Sylvester?
I thought he was with you.
No, we left him
at the crash site.
Crash site got burned over,
Walter. Let's go.
Come on. Let's go, son!
We got to evac now!
We have to wait
for Sylvester.
Fire's too close.
We got to go!
Not without our man!
I know Sylvester.
He thinks like us.
He will make it here.
And I'm not gonna leave
without him.
We can look
for him when we're back
up top again.
We need to go now, sir.
Negative! Not an option!
There! There! There! There!
Walter!
Put him down. Put him down.
It's okay, buddy.
Toby, he's lost
a lot of blood.
All right,
let's move out!
Sounds like they're getting
a handle on the fire.
Should have it contained
by nightfall.
Look, I know we've had some
close calls together, but...
today was extra dicey.
Aw.
You were worried about us.
In so many words, yes.
I'm glad you're all okay.
Guys, we're
growing on him.
Softy.
Hey. Hey.
Excuse me.
Please be careful with him.
Sylvester.
You're gonna be okay.
You're one tough
son of a bitch.
I'd be proud as hell
to call you my kid.
Lift.
Uh, it's just costume jewelry,
but it should do the job.
♪ ♪
Hey.
Got pretty intense out there.
Yeah. Big fire.
I wasn't talking
about the fire.
People say stupid things
in the heat of battle.
Oh...
No, I meant it.
I chose in the moment
to live honestly,
and if you don't feel
the same way yet,
I'm okay with it.
You're confident.
On this I am.
I'm confident enough
to make another wager.
What are the stakes?
If I win, you take
me to dinner.
And if I win?
I take you.
♪ ♪
What is all that?
It's something
that Toby's been working on.
I got to give the kid more work
if he's got time
to draw cartoons.
Hell of a day.
Ridiculous
if you think about it.
One man's belief
in romantic love
destroys a helicopter,
400 acres of forest,
nearly kills a dozen people.
Heart wants
what the heart wants.
Heart is a circulatory muscle.
Nothing more.
Spoken like someone
who's never been in love.
Hope that changes
for you one day, pal.
Take care, Walter.
Ugh, it's cinnamon.
It's awful.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net