My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
♪ ♪
I want Gallo out.
Then I'll resign.
Effective immediately.
I just don't want him
to become you.
I don't think
I can be here anymore.
Calling to order Scorpion 2.0.
Toby Curtis?
Check.
Sylvester Dodd?
And... Happy Quinn?
Whatever you're doing,
stop it immediately.
I'm maintaining a sense
of order in our chaos,
filling a leadership vacuum.
You're highly unqualified.
Spend your time wisely.
Look for a new gig,
like me.
Now, Walter did not say that
this was the end of Scorpion.
He only said that
he didn't need Cabe or Paige.
However implausible that is,
maybe Scorpion will...
- persevere.
- Run the numbers on that.
We lost a third of our personnel
in one night.
We're back to where
we were a year ago.
Broke, aimless, losers.
I was not
"aimless""
I'm calling Walter again.
You've called him ten times.
He's not
going to answer.
Paige, then.
She bailed on us.
Who needs her?
Then I'm calling Cabe.
Walter threw Cabe off the team.
No Cabe, no Paige--
the Scorpion you're thinking of
does not
exist anymore.
Accept it and pull the rip cord.
We're not going down
without a fight.
Isn't this worth it?
Call Cabe.
What do I care?
So, I got your
new assignment.
Pomona airport?
You're on a desk,
but you're in charge
of all TSA.
If you get bored, you could
strap on a blue uniform
and work the
luggage scanner.
Why do I get the sense
you're enjoying this?
Scorpion's flameout freed up
funding for certain pet projects,
but this is all
you're doing, Gallo.
You were always
intimidated by them
because they're smarter
than you by a millionfold,
save countless lives, and help countless
more than you ever could.
Maybe Pomona's too good for you.
I'll never know.
You can take this
assignment and shove it.
How the hell am I supposed
to fix this team
if no one's gonna pick up?
That was Megan.
Walter missed her weekly
doctor's assessment.
He didn't even call.
She can't get ahold of him.
That's not great.
He's never missed
an appointment before.
Megan thinks something could
be very wrong, and so do I.
Or he's holed up
in a bar somewhere
throwing back tequila bombs rewriting
the relativity theorem.
Walter doesn't drink.
Then he's throwing back
milkshakes rewriting
the relativity theorem.
Can I please have
a little emotional escapism
while we trace his phone?
On it.
Hi. This is Paige Dineen.
I can't come to the phone,
but leave a detailed...
Are you calling Walter again?
Hi, Walter.
It's me again.
Can you call me back, please?
I promise my call
will be efficient.
I just want to
say good-bye.
Why won't he pick up?
Ralph,
you've already left
three messages.
Now pack.
We're leaving soon.
I don't want to go.
It's two days.
And then it'll be forever.
Go.
This is Walter O'Brien.
Please leave a brief message.
Yeah, it's me this time.
I can't believe...
you're not returning
Ralph's calls.
I always knew you had issues,
Walter, but this is...
way beneath you.
You are selfish,
and you are being a jerk.
Glad you finally grew a pair.
Uh, it's Happy Quinn.
From the team
you were formerly a part of.
Oh. Happy, I'm-I'm-I'm sorry,
I thought it was...
I'm looking for Walter.
No.
You know where he is?
Ralph has been trying
to call him all morning.
Okay. Bye.
Happy. Come on.
Okay, I'm
ready to go.
No, no. That will not fit
in the bag-- it's not going.
Going where?
A little trip.
You're moving this quick?
No flies on you, girl.
Drew invited us to Portland
for the weekend
just to get a feel
for the place, but we wouldn't
move there till the end
of the school year.
Great.
Bring a raincoat
and a mosquito net.
Okay, you're obviously
upset with me.
You come onto our team,
mess up with Walt's head,
and get us used
to having that kid around,
and then you up and leave.
We were all good
before you came along.
I am doing it
for the sake of my son.
And for the record,
before I came along,
you guys were a disaster.
You've wormed your way
into Walt's head,
and that is a big reason
why he's MIA right now.
I don't need to listen to this.
Then don't!
His phone is cloaked,
and his GPS is disabled.
Walter, you clever bastard.
You're killing us here.
You'll never find him that way.
Well, what do you care?
You're already looking
for a new job.
We can track
the car's onboard computer.
All we need is the VIN.
Elia...
would have that.
Well, look who wants
to help now.
Would you just admit
that you're on board
with trying to save Scorpion,
the greatest thing
that ever happened to any of us.
Guys... Elia's
Playa Vista headquarters.
Mm.
Ma'am, I know there's a policy.
Outside of family,
Mr. Elia cannot be interrupted
during a meeting.
But by saving his daughter,
we became de facto family.
The notion is outlined
in a Chinese proverb
I doubt you're familiar with.
What I am familiar with
is the number for security.
Okay.
We'll be sitting down now.
You think Walter isn't calling us back
because he's preparing his exit strategy
to come work here?
I mean...
look at this place--
we can't compete.
It's not so great.
It is.
Multiple dedicated T-1 lines,
state-of-the-art engineering,
unlimited resources.
You know what this place
doesn't have? Us.
Tobes and
the Sly dog.
And that's
what's gonna keep Walter
at Scorpion where he belongs.
That guy is going down the hall
on a hoverboard!
Hey.
Don't look. Don't be seduced.
Happy should be
in position by now.
What the hell?
I need that VIN number
of the bribe on wheels
you gave Walter O'Brien.
I'm in the middle
of a meeting.
And I'm in the middle
of your conference table.
You stuck your nose
where it didn't belong,
looking to break apart
the only family
some of us have ever known.
I was being friendly.
You were poaching our boss.
Now he's missing,
and I'm not leaving
without that VIN.
Onboard computer's pinging
right here.
Do you see a car?
I see no car.
Did Elia
mislead us?
Maybe he doesn't
want us to find him.
- Rat.
- I'll call Walter again.
It's ringing.
You hear that?
Hey, guys...
Aw, geez.
Okay, count of three,
we yell his name.
On three,
or two, three, then go?
Which is
essentially four.
On three.
Okay, one, two...
Walter!
Hello?
Oh! Walter?
You're balanced
on a cliff's edge.
One wrong move,
and the car falls 300 feet.
Stay very, very still.
♪ Scorpion 1x22 ♪
Cliffhanger
Original Air Date on April 20, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Police and rescue are on their
way. How you holding up, Walter?
He doesn't sound good.
Tell the doctor where it hurts.
My left side.
What's it look like?
Is it bruised or bleeding?
I can't move to see.
I'm pinned to the seat.
Pinned how?
Something leaning on you, or...?
Or what?
Stay cool, Walt.
We'll have a visual
on you in 30 seconds.
Birdroni lives.
It was gonna be your birthday
present, but I wasn't
done yet. I was gonna
mount a camera...
We'll need one,
but I have a solution.
Any duct tape in your truck?
You really did a number
on that car, O'Brien.
Yeah, well, I was doing fine
until an untimely interface
with Mother Nature.
This's what I was afraid of.
So, it's, um, good news?
Walter, you're impaled
on what looks like
a piece of metal
from the guardrail.
So, it's excellent news then.
From the color of the blood
and the position of the metal,
your body has been able
to clot off.
Best scenario,
we keep it that way
until we can get you
to a hospital,
but that means
no movement, nada.
The wound is dangerous
close to his spleen.
I thought
we don't need the spleen.
We don't, but it's basically
a giant sack of blood.
Never good to lose a giant sack
of blood.
Walter, I know
it hurts like hell.
You got to stay with me here.
No, I was just...
I'm just running some numbers.
Okay, so, I-I'm perched on...
...about a 71% grade?
Give or take.
I don't have my protractor.
I do-- 71.8.
All right, okay,
so, given my precarious hold
on the Cliffside,
the extent of my injuries,
the time needed
for successful rescue...
Sylvester, would you put this
at about a 97% chance of death?
You know, Walter, I've never
put much faith in numbers.
That's the police.
I'll coordinate.
They need to know
who they're dealing with here.
You don't handle
authority well!
This is Paige's job.
Yeah, we don't need her.
Paige. Where's Paige?
Taking a little R&R.
She's taking Ralph
to Portland to see Drew.
I told her
it was a stupid idea.
What the hell is this?! I said
fire department and
ambulance. Do you have
any idea who's
stuck down there?
All right, buddy, we're gonna
need you to take a step back.
Whoa. I'm not your buddy,
and if anybody's gonna
be condescended to,
it'll be you by me.
One of the great minds of
this or any other lifetime--
and also my friend--
is clinging to life by a thread.
We are formulating
a plan of rescue,
and are gonna need
every resource at our disposal.
The resources belong to trained
rescue personnel that...
That don't have the brain
power of me with a hangover
and this guy when
he's sleeping.
So, first thing
we'll need,
Officer, is a soil integrity
report on that Cliffside
so we can start working
toward a solution.
Excuse me. Do you know
what this badge means?
That you got "D"s
in high school?
Actually,
I have a better solution.
Don't get in the car.
Sly!
Call Cabe!
Quiet down. Come on.
Track him down!
I'll admit, Paige would
have handled this better.
Cabe.
Cabe, they're talking
about sending a team down
with grappling hooks.
Happy says this is going to
disrupt the soil beneath the car
and drop it like a hot potato.
They've shoved us aside.
They won't listen to us.
They're gonna kill him.
All right.
Who the hell's in charge
of this operation?!
I am.
Wrong! I am. Cabe
Gallo, Homeland.
Now, get my behaviorist and
engineer out of that squad car
and give my team some room.
That man down there
is a government asset.
Move!
You heard the man. Move it!
Did you just flash
your scuba certification?
Yeah. I don't work
for Homeland anymore.
Oh, my God.
Cabe?
Yes. We thought it
would be best to bring him in.
Yeah, I'm here,
and you don't like it,
you can yell at me later.
Consider it a date.
Our soil expert just confirmed
what Ms. Quinn was saying.
Thank you very much.
Which kills us sending guys down
to hook the chassis
and winch the car.
A chopper extraction
might be faster.
No, the rotor wash could upset
the car's balance.
Call that a no go.
So, we're gonna send a team up
from the canyon floor.
They'll approach
from underneath,
secure the vehicle from there
without going near
the support topsoil.
But nothing's guaranteed,
and we're talking
a half hour climb at least.
If I hold out that long.
I don't like that look.
Do I need to throw down a copy
of The Power
of Positive Thinking?
I want to see the equipment
your team will be using,
see if I can cut down
the amount of time
it'll take them
to get to Walter.
Okay, Walt. Happy's on it.
We're gonna have a rescue team
up to you very soon.
Yeah, really?
Because from what I heard,
it won't be that soon...
or at all.
Guys, do you think, uh,
you could reach out to...
to Paige for me, um,
get her and Ralph over here?
I've actually already
reached out to them.
Her phone is powered off.
The last tower ping
was near her apartment.
Look, there's gonna be plenty
of time to talk to her
once we get you back
up here with us.
I'd really like to talk to her
as soon as possible.
I'm getting a black and white
sent to her home right now.
Thank you.
Go find this woman.
Cabe, uh...
Cabe, when I was 16 years old...
What I did with
Baghdad was wrong.
You have every right
to be mad at me.
No, I was
hurt and, uh... I overreacted.
I was, uh... emotional,
and, uh, ineffective, and
if I'd been logical,
then I'd, uh...
I'd have realized the man
who knew me when I was younger
would never hurt me on purpose.
Thank you, Walter.
Cabe, you told me that
when your daughter passed away,
you'd visit her grave
every Sunday?
Yes.
Without fail.
The grass at her plot-- it was
always, uh, green, healthy?
And the others were brown?
I hacked the sprinkler system.
I, uh, watered it
twice a day.
The others were...
once, uh, a week.
I always thought that
was the groundskeeper
taking pity on me,
'cause I was there alone.
No, it was me.
15 years ago, you were so
mad at me about Baghdad.
Why would you do that for me?
That's not the point.
The point is
that I don't want there
to be any more secrets
between us.
Guys, we got a problem!
The engine.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yup, this is a problem.
Spin the drone around!
Smoke!
Uh, it's from the oil pan.
It must have been
an electrical short
caused by the accident.
If the flame gets to the gas
tank, the whole car goes up.
Water cannon will blow the car
right off that perch.
A fire retardant
might be better.
No, you-you... you can't.
You can't control the
weight distribution even with
foam or gel.
Well, if we can't douse it,
maybe we can prevent it
from spreading
to the gas tank.
How?
I have no idea.
It was just a conceptual notion.
Fire can't burn without fuel.
Guys, we need to drain the oil.
We can't go down there
and put you up on blocks.
You don't need blocks.
You have an ambulance
and a fire truck.
Ralph, come on.
Clock's ticking.
What's going on?
I'm not pleased
with this plan.
Think of all the firsts.
Ride in a plane,
see the Atlantic Ocean.
There's something
wrong with Walter.
Why didn't he pick up?
Walter is...
going through a lot right now,
and it's best
we leave him alone.
Just follow our own path,
just for today.
Okay?
Okay.
Guys, not to pressure anyone,
but a, uh, a status update
on my, uh, proposed solution
would certainly be comforting.
We're working on it.
Okay, aim it at the car.
I thought we said
that that would
knock the car off the hill.
Okay, just do it, and
then, get me the jacket and
the duct tape I need. Now!
I'm calculating
we have seconds at best
before this entire car
is engulfed.
I got the dart!
Ten steel syringe needles--
best I could do.
- Sylvester!
- Okay. You have a target
surface area of eight square
inches. You need to hit the pan
low enough to ensure full
drainage away from the car,
or else, kaboom.
Guys, the heat
is getting up to about
130 degrees, give or take.
We're gonna have enough
force to penetrate the pan?
Standard PSI is 55,000,
comparable to an M40A1
sniper rifle.
Your margin of error
is 2.2 inches
to the left, and
two to the right.
A syringe dart shot
out of a water hose, guys.
I just don't know.
Chief, I just don't care.
Fire in the hole,
so to speak.
How we doing?
Ever hear of adding fuel
to the fire?
We just did the opposite.
Nothing left to burn--
it'll be out in seconds.
The car's shifting.
It's the weight loss
from the drained oil.
Uh, Walter,
compensate for the weight.
Lean the seat back
as far as you can.
Okay. Okay.
Yeah, that wasn't a scream
of fear, that was pain.
What's going on
down there?
Well, the good news is...
with the shift in
the car, I'm no longer impaled.
The bad news is
there's a-a great degree
of bright red blood just
spewing out... my wound.
That sounds like an
arterial bleeder.
That shard of guardrail must
have been in the spleen.
The blood coagulated around it;
now it's been ripped out.
How long does he have?
If he's really bleeding
out, four minutes.
Walter, you got to get pressure
against that wound to stem
- the bleeding.
- I am. It's not...
it's not working.
He doesn't sound good.
Hey, Walter!
Walter, listen to me!
You have to fight the urge
to close your eyes.
Do not close your eyes.
Find Paige.
We're losing him.
You're the doctor.
Do something!
Can't exactly cauterize
the wound from here,
Sylvester.
Or can I?
Holy crap, am I smart.
Walter, I got an idea
to fix your bleeding,
but it won't work if you die
before I can implement it.
So you have to stay conscious.
Wal-Walter, Walter, hey, hey,
you have to stay awake
so I can get
a good look at your wound.
You okay in there, son?
Just trying to stay awake.
Okay, hey,
Walter, I can see the wound.
It is bad. You're
gonna have to cauterize it,
'cause my arms
are not nearly long enough.
Listen carefully.
Find a thin piece of metal.
I see a pen.
Okay. Reach for it slowly.
Oh, boy.
It's silver.
Oh, yeah, of course Elia
would have a silver pen,
rich jerk, but that's good.
'Cause silver
conducts heat fast.
Now, press in
the cigarette lighter.
You okay back there?
Huh? You want me to put
that science CD in you like?
Sweetheart,
I know you're upset...
It's not finished.
What isn't, sweetheart?
The rocket.
Walter and I need to finish it,
but you won't let us.
I'm gonna miss him.
I know.
Me, too.
Don't leave it there too long.
We need it to be hot,
not glowing.
Yeah? All right.
Fantastic.
That's perfect.
Walter, Walter, hey!
Keep those peepers
popped, buddy.
Okay, now here's
the rough par.
I can't watch this.
Okay, Walter, you need
to press the pen
into the wound
past the rib cage.
When you feel the spleen...
How do I know it's the spleen?
the pen will stop moving
and you'll feel the pulses
of the artery transmitted
through the pen.
Oh, man.
When you feel the spleen
touch the hot metal
against the organ
in short little bursts,
it'll stop the bleeding, but
it'll preserve the tissue.
You can do this, son.
Walter,
no matter how bad it hurts,
you got to stay still,
or that car's gonna fall.
Toby...
do you remember the '07...
World Series of Poker when, uh,
when... you made me go
to Vegas with you?
How could I forget?
And you m-made me s-stay
in that...
that crappy hotel room...
off the Strip?
God, this hurts.
El Ranchorito.
Wasn't that bad.
And you won that...
gangster's bankroll in that...
back-alley crap game?
He and his friends...
chased after us with,
: uh... with crowbars
for nine blocks?
We had to hitchhike...
back to L.A.?
I remember every
minute of it, Walt.
It was one of the best weekends
of my life.
I need to take a look.
How much longer?
Can you move your hand away?
Okay.
Yeah, the bleeding
has stopped substantially.
Great work, pal,
great work. Now...
take a beat
and catch your breath.
Nice work, Doc.
The way he's telling the stories
from back in the day,
it's like he's
almost at his own wake.
We got to get him
out of there.
He might be giving up.
Okay. This is our gate.
Now we need to get you
some yogurt and fruit,
because I assume you'll find airplane
food lacking in nutritional content.
What do you want from the newsstand,
Discover or Smithsonian?
Ralph.
Which magazine do you want?
The Cliffside rescue attempt on
Mulholland Drive is underway
to save Walter O'Brien, head of
the genius problem-solving team
known as Scorpion.
Oh, my God!
Come on!
I can't find anything
on the news!
Mom?
What?!
I'm sorry.
Is Walter gonna be okay?
Yes. Of course he will be.
I just need
to call the guys.
Damn it, I left my bag
at the airport!
Hold on, Ralph.
Copy that.
Relaying the data now.
Those were my climbers.
Recent changes in the position
of the car are forcing them
to change their course.
They can't just go straight up.
They have to try to up and around.
How long?
22 minutes minimum.
Walter might not
have that long.
Thanks to him
shifting around in there,
the ground's moved
under the car in a way
that even the slightest change
in weight distribution
can upset the balance
and he's a goner.
Well, that's good to know.
I'm sorry, pal--
I thought the phone was off.
That's okay.
Any luck finding Paige?
Uh, still nothing, buddy.
I called again--
not answering her phone.
Too bad we don't have
a Southernell
two-slot pay phone circa 1991.
Stop it!
I know what you're doing--
you're talking
about that pay phone
I rigged for free calls
when we first opened the garage
'cause we
couldn't afford a phone.
Well, you sure fixed that
for us, didn't you?
Okay, I'm not having it!
Okay? I will not let you
eulogize a memory of you and me.
You have three geniuses up here
putting their heads together.
We will figure this out,
you will not die--
the situation is under control!
Sylvester,
you're into bird-watching--
how much does a crow weigh?
Decent size:
1.2 pounds.
Why?
One just landed on my hood.
A pound of pressure on the lever
at the greatest distance
from the fulcrum
can create enough force
to start the beginning
of a slide which results
in gravitational pull.
Which results
in car overboard.
If that bird flies off...
Walter dies.
Guys, the car's starting
to tilt...
ever so downward.
Copy that.
We're aware of the situation,
and handling it.
How are we
handling this?
Uh, the fire department's
got a hook and ladder
parked up around that bend.
It would never extend out
far enough.
I know, but I saw construction work
down the road from here.
I have an idea, and it works on
the same principle!
Hey,
if you fly off, the reverse
torque from weight distribution
will cause my death.
You don't really care
about that, do you?
He's talking
to the bird.
Not the best sign.
Rescue crews are at a loss
of how to extract the man
identified as one Walter O'Brien
from the car
before it completes its fall
down the cliff.
With me is Tomas Kolbrenner,
USC professor
of structural engineering,
who has studied photographs
and video of the scene.
Mr. Kolbrenner, given the situation,
what's the likelihood Come on, go faster!
of a successful rescue?
Well, I hate to morbid, Jackie,
but I don't see a scenario
where Mr. O'Brien
makes it out alive.
Don't listen to them--
they don't know what Scorpion's
capable of.
Baby...
He's my friend.
How's Tweety doing?
Staying put?
For now. We have a plan?
Uh, yeah, Happy left here
like a bat out of hell,
and you know her--
she says she's got an idea,
she's got an idea.
What is that?
Her idea.
You borrowed a crane
from a construction site?
Not exactly.
You stole a crane
from a construction site?
Exactly.
Uh, Walt,
here's the plan.
I am going to hook Cabe up
to the end of a crane,
like a wrecking ball,
and swing him out
over the canyon
to your car.
He'll connect you
via safety line,
and we'll pull you both back in.
Amazingly, not the craziest
thing that we've ever done.
It's been a busy year.
Okay, Walter,
you're gonna need
to unlock the passenger-side
door so Cabe can get to you.
But move with extreme caution
as to, you know,
not get killed.
Ugh, that is gonna hurt.
More than falling down
the side of a cliff?
All right. Point taken.
Okay.
Now I got to fashion a harness
for you to wear.
I'll get some Tech 12 cable
from Search and Rescue.
Uh, Cabe.
The car falls
when you're hooked to Walter
and his body gets caught inside?
The hoist line snaps
and you will go down with him.
Just get the harness ready.
Don't move, crow.
What was that sound?
His collarbone.
Oh.
Oh, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
You got to turn this around.
My-my friend is on that cliff!
Ma'am,
there are no cars allowed
past this point. I need you
to turn it back around.
All right. Okay.
Okay, Ralph. Let's go.
Come on.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, Ralph.
Okay, when we tell you to,
open the car door.
The weight shift will cause
the car to instantly fall.
But that won't matter because
Cabe will have already hooked
your safety line to him.
The car falls
while you hang safely in the air
with SuperGallo.
Okay. Yeah.
I'm not going anywhere
until I talk to Paige.
Ground underneath that car is
getting more and more unstable.
That bird can amscray
at any moment.
We have got
to get this party started
as soon as Happy is done rigging
that harness.
Toby,
there is a strong possibility
that this thing does not work!
If so, then I need to talk
to Paige and Ralph.
He's not gonna open that door
until they get here.
No matter what.
How do you know?
'Cause the last thing
Walter O'Brien
wants to do before he dies
is state facts, and the fact
he's tried
to tell us,
in his own way,
is that he loves us.
So why do you think
he wants Paige here so badly?
So I'm gonna feed the line
through the window
and you're gonna hook
it around your waist.
Cabe, if this thing doesn't
work, then you need to tell her.
Tell Paige what, son?
Tell her that I...
Oh, no!
Bird's on the move! Move!
He flies off, it's all over.
Happy,
how much longer?
I'm not ready!
Well, get ready.
Happy, we got
to get going.
I only have one line.
You need two.
Not an option.
Get me out there now.
Is this it, pal?
You're gonna fly off?
Well, you do what you
got to do, but...
if you could just stay put
for a little bit longer,
I'd-I'd really
appreciate it.
The proximal half
of the bird's wings are flexing.
It's preparing to fly.
And if I've picked up on that,
so has Walter.
Come on!
Walter!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Walter.
Paige,
I just want you to know...
No!
Open the damn door!
Walter!
No!
I won't let go if you won't.
Deal.
I don't feel so well.
Radiology, 135. Radiology, 135.
Hey. He awake yet?
Not yet.
You brought
balloons.
Everybody
likes balloons.
What's he gonna do?
Knock 'em around the room
with his broken ribs
and punctured spleen?
Hey, everybody.
If you're here about your car,
it's wrecked.
Don't care
about the car.
Just checking on Walter.
I'm sorry. This is family only.
Understood.
Will you at least let him know
that I stopped by?
And if there's anything
that he needs...
You'll be right there to
try and steal him away again?
After what I saw unfold
on TV today,
breaking up a
family like this,
that would
be criminal.
Please just keep me posted
as to how he's doing.
But if you would all like
to come
work with me, I'd be crazy
not to have a group like you
working for
my think tank.
Food for thought?
Nope.
Uh-uh.
No way.
Scorpion appreciates the offer,
but, um,
we're not corporate material.
We're a team.
We work out of a garage,
not a tank.
And we work alone.
Fair enough.
Um, what's this
"we" stuff, pilgrim?
Yeah. What about Maine?
Uh, I don't know, Ralphy.
What about Maine?
It's cold and wet.
Is this the
O'Brien party?
What gave it away?
Was it the balloons?
Hi. How's he doing?
He's weak and tired but stable.
He's gonna be okay.
Can we see him?
It's way past visitation,
so it'll have to be quick.
Follow me.
Hey, guys.
Hey yourself,
Mario Andretti.
The sawbones patch you up okay?
Yeah, I've felt better.
But... never better.
If that makes sense.
Doesn't.
But you've had a head injury.
Eh.
Hey, you brought balloons.
Thank you.
See?
Sly, do you remember
that time that...
we filled that balloon
with tapioca
and then we took
that catapult...
Walter, you don't need
to take me down memory lane.
But thanks.
I love you, too.
Hey. Hey, pal.
It's good to see you.
It's good to see you, too.
Okay.
It's morphine
time, which means
he's gonna be out like a light
in about a minute.
It's time for good-byes.
All right.
We will see you back at work
when you're all better, okay?
Back to work?
Yeah. Back at work.
That put a smile on his face.
That and the drugs.
Bye.
Okay. I'm gonna
go see Megan.
She's worried sick
about her brother.
I'm gonna hit
the Epsom salts.
Swinging off a crane does
a number on your back.
I... I think might
hang back for a bit
in case Walter needs anything.
He's doped-up
like a Tijuana drug mule.
Just in case.
Happy, would you mind keeping
an eye on Ralph
for a few hours?
Not if he
doesn't mind
getting his butt kicked
in Constructo-Battle.
You want to babysit with me?
Of course I would.
Hey, be good. They've
had a long day, okay?
Thanks for not
making me leave them.
Uh, is it all right
if I stay for a while?
Sure. But he's
down for the count.
He won't be awake for hours.
Okay.
Thought for a moment today
I'd seen you for the last time.
It really bothered me
that if that had happened,
our final memory together
would've been... a fight.
I'm really glad
that wasn't the case.
Because...
Because I really care about you,
Walter.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net