My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11,
the FBI arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
Of the six three-digit integers
on the board,
which are divisible by four?
O'Brien! All of them.
Not even in the outer reaches of Pluto,
where you generally reside,
is 703 divisible by four.
703 divided by four is 175.75.
They can all be divided by four,
just with the remainders.
You didn't define your terms.
O'Brien!
Stay.
You show a growing disdain for authority.
It's concerning.
Hands on the desk.
There's no drill scheduled.
Move out, O'Brien.
Walter. Let's go.
You could get arrested for
pulling the fire alarm.
He should get arrested
for daring to strike you.
He'll just call Dad.
I'll take care of that, too.
Megan, someday I'll pay you back.
I'll take a Lamborghini,
bright yellow.
Race ya!
Sorry I'm late.
Uh, Ralph's sick again.
That's two days in a row, huh, pal?
Yeah, his fever won't break.
I'm gonna take him to the doctor at 10:00
and then my neighbor can watch him.
- If that's okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Are you okay? You don't look so...
Never been healthier.
So... mail arrived.
Menus and... paychecks.
Mo' money. Mo' problems.
Or so I've heard in the rapper song.
Well, rappers may have 99 or so problems
but misplacing paychecks is not one of them.
LAX cleared our debt.
This is our first fresh cash.
Toby, are you gonna be okay with this?
I'm way ahead of you.
High stress levels triggers
my gambling addictions.
If my levels go up...
See, it reminds me I'm being a jackass.
Hell, I could do that for you.
I'll be upstairs.
Hey, seriously, what's wrong?
I'm fine.
Clearly.
So is Ralph by the way.
Yep.
He hacked the thermometer.
Recalibrated the digital display.
He did what? Ralph?
He hates school.
We all did.
Especially those of us
with math proficiency.
You know, to get through the day,
I would look at the clock
and I'd create formulas
expressing trigonomic functions
based on the clock hands.
My sister suggested that
to me a long time ago.
Oh, I didn't know you had a sister.
Is she...
enabled, too?
Not like us.
But in her own way.
Ralph... backpack.
What's his story today?
Don't know. But that is only
the second time he's ever
mentioned his sister.
Still stalking your ex-wife?
Ex-fiancée.
And I am not "stalking."
I'm keeping current.
- Uh-huh.
- Cabe called.
We're all going to meet
the governor of California.
My back-tax status
with the state isn't exactly
what you'd call good.
What's this about?
He said hurry, all right? So let's hurry.
Paige, Ralph's school is on the way,
so we'll drop him off.
Come on, guys!
The new car rides nice.
Steady paycheck equals safe car for my kid.
Heavy security.
Way more than you'd expect
for the governor.
Walter, why is there a van
from the Center for Disease Control here?
I don't know.
We'll find out pretty soon.
Uh, they handle diseases that
wipe out civilizations.
Diseases that have no cure.
And they're, they're here.
It's gonna be fine, come on.
Good, you're here. Follow me.
Wait, why are you wearing a
surgical mask around your neck?
What exactly are you
protecting yourself from?
Relax.
They put up a quarantine tent.
A quarantine tent?
I will be in the car.
Uh, Mr. Gallo, sir?
Is there a very terrible,
possibly communicable disease in this home?
Sorry.
Stress levels are a tad elevated right now.
Weird, phone's off but
I still hear a donkey.
Today's not the
day to be screwing off.
You two go wait with Sylvester.
There's a computer I need you to look at.
That poor little girl.
Who's that kid?
That's a need-to-know.
You know, what I need to know
is exactly what's going on.
Otherwise, I can't help.
Guys, this is Governor Lane.
This is the man who can help my daughter?
I'm gonna need to know
everything that's happening here.
So governmental habits
of proprietary knowledge and
"need to know..."
Jettison that nonsense
or my efforts to help your child
will be hampered.
You have to forgive Mr. O'Brien.
He's brilliant but impolitic.
Don't care what he is,
long as he helps.
In here...
We're really not trying to hamper anyone,
but if the public hears "unknown virus,"
it could cause panic.
Especially if there's
a political motivation.
What kind of virus?
She tested negative for Hanta,
Rift Valley, Ebola...
- Eastern equine encephalitis?
- Also negative.
She's only positive for the common cold.
The CDC has a database
of the rarest infective agents in the world.
They're searching.
Yeah, but while they search,
Helena's kidneys, liver,
all shutting down.
Her fever's cli...
How long?
Doctors said she has
- less than 24 hours.
- This is a medical problem.
- Why am I here?
- First of all,
Governor, we're so sorry
this is happening to you.
I have a child, too,
and I can't imagine how you feel.
All we want to do is help.
Thank you.
Come with me.
We found this virus
on Helena's laptop a few hours ago.
Based on this, we're working
on the assumption
that someone made Helena sick intentionally.
Targeting you, no doubt.
Any idea why?
Immigration reform? Three strikes?
Those are my hot-button issues,
but would they prompt this kind
of hostility against my kid?
We're compiling all threats,
past and present.
The FBI, NSA,
Homeland, all the top computer guys
been trying to trace the sender.
The source bounced around to 15 countries.
We hit a wall.
Agent Gallo said that you
and your team were brilliant.
That you could find out who sent it.
All right.
All of your devices are
on the same home network?
Yeah.
Any other computer
have this virus?
No.
Okay, so he directed the virus
to just Helena's computer.
Anybody else in the house sick?
- No.
- So...
you, your wife and your staff...
they've all been in her proximity?
Yes. What are you getting at?
Well, he could have taken out
the whole home network,
but he directed the computer
virus at just your child.
I don't think it's a coincidence
that no one else but Helena is ill.
Wait, wait. What does this mean?
Give the girl some cool air.
She's hot enough.
What are you doing?
No!
You can't catch it.
None of us can.
The virus he placed on the computer
is custom-built.
He did the same with your daughter,
- or why is no one else ill?
- You're saying
he custom-built a virus
that would make just this child sick?
Yeah. There's computer hacking,
and more recently, there's biohacking.
Now, whoever infected
the computer also infected your daughter.
Until we find that person
and know exactly what
biological agent he used,
there's not gonna be any hope for a cure.
Wait, wait, wait. Where are you going?
You can't just drop a
theory like that and leave.
Governor, the helplessness you feel
will incline you to irrational behavior.
So please,
resist the temptation to do anything stupid,
like standing in my way.
Let me do my job.
sync and corrections by dreaMaker7
www.addic7ed.com
I checked the AVG scanner,
came up with nothing.
If we can find a signature
in the viral code,
it'll tell us who sent it.
Meaning we have nothing.
So far, Walt.
Keep your shorts on.
Governor's had
ten distinct threats
since he took the office.
Four of the perps are locked up,
- thus leaving six.
- Guillermo Flacos?
This is way too subtle
for a Mexican drug lord.
Oh, announcing your intent via e-mail?
That's too subtle?
Personally, I would keep digging.
Any on the list
have computer proficiency
and a knowledge of biophysics?
Well, that'll probably
narrow our list down to zero,
but we'll keep digging.
What I want to understand is
how you hack into a human being.
I get your DNA from anywhere...
a coffee cup,
a piece of gum...
and then I study your genetics
for a deficiency... say, uh, lung disease...
and then I harness that genetic sequence
onto a cold virus and
I blow it in your face.
Or into the air around you.
Toby, anything?
I traced the computer virus' code...
Russia, China, Serbia.
It's no wonder the
government couldn't crack it.
It uses none of the known building blocks.
That's where you leave it, huh?
With a young girl dying.
All right, trace the IP header.
Study it for patterns.
Maybe that'll get us somewhere.
Don't say "I'm fine."
I was gonna say "I'll live."
What's eating you?
You're acting... I'm...
I'm tempted to use the word "emotional."
Particularly challenging problems create...
impatience.
But you were already off this
morning when you came in.
You only became "impatient"
when you saw that little girl in her bed.
Yeah, she reminded me of a
problem I couldn't solve.
You realize the more evasive you are,
the more I'll press.
All right.
As a child my, uh, sister got sick.
She survived.
She's fine.
Like you, all day.
All right, you know what?
I couldn't help her.
It felt like she was being beaten,
and I was handcuffed.
I couldn't solve her problem.
And that's how you felt,
seeing that girl today?
Walter!
- We've got something!
- Thank you for the bandage.
All right, hide the mugs,
I'm coming down!
Okay, so we've successfully
mirrored the infected laptop.
The good news is... we traced the e-mail.
The bad news... it doesn't justoue off
a few servers around the world.
It's caught in an endless loop.
That is a dirty one, it's a good one.
They're using a round-robin
on an IP address,
but it's too clever by half.
It narrows the source.
There's a pattern in the routing data.
You see that prefix?
I know the place that uses this trick
to mask their e-mail origins.
Let's go.
The sophistication
of the e-mail sent
to the governor's daughter
stamps of this place.
It's a known hacker petri dish.
One guy makes an
advancement in deception,
passes it on to another guy.
It's how Silk Road stayed
online for so long.
You know that how?
I think we both take the Fifth on that.
Hey! Kill the music!
Homeland Security!
I'm looking for the scumbag that sent
the e-mail virus to the governor's daughter.
That greaseball right there.
His wide eyes and twitching hands
go beyond the standard for
ten cans of Mountain Dew.
You. Don't move.
Since when does Walter get physical?
Um...
Never.
Got the job on Craigslist.
I never even met the client.
I think he broke some ribs.
Mm-hmm.
Refocus, or I'll break the rest of them.
How were you paid?
Cash, to my P.O. Box.
Great. Untraceable.
I didn't know about any sick kid.
I just sent a few anonymous e-mails,
and I pocketed three grand.
Three e-mails?
More than one?
I sent four total.
All the same...
"It's your fault she's sick."
So, there are more victims?
Sir, we identified the three other victims.
They're all children.
My God.
They're all as sick as your daughter.
Sons and daughters of Dwight Carrington,
Victoria Cooper, and John Tuttle.
Wait, I know them.
You were all employees of
Vlaxco Pharmaceuticals in 2008.
That's before I went into politics.
I only worked there for a
year in risk management.
There's a drug called Trexicane.
You all worked on its development.
Trexicane had promise as a cure for SMA...
it's spinal muscular atrophy.
It causes your muscles to waste away
until you can't breathe anymore.
The clinical trial was going really well
until Vlaxco pulled the plug.
Yeah, it also worked well on asthma.
It was redeveloped solely for asthma.
Way more profit, huh?
Left all the SMA sufferers out in the cold.
I spent months fielding
their angry phone calls.
I hated the job.
But how it this related to Helena?
We think that whoever attacked
Helena and these other children
must be someone who suffered from SMA.
And they're trying to make us suffer, too?
What kind of mind thinks this way?
Well, the kind that sends taunting e-mails
alongside his deadly disease.
So, someone in enough
psychological pain to not care
about how stupid that is
from a criminal standpoint.
Okay, is this headed towards ransom?
More likely,
like his experience with Trexicane,
he's saying there is a cure out there,
you just can't have it.
This person would need
high scientific aptitude
and access to cutting-edge
genetic sequencers.
I got thousands of complaints
after the trial ended.
Our best bet at finding
someone that angry enough
to infect your daughter
and three other children
is in the drug-trial records.
None of the other families
work at Vlaxco anymore.
You're the governor.
Convince Vlaxco to hand them over.
I'll beg if I have to.
Where are Cabe and Sylvester?
You haven't eaten today.
If you don't take care of yourself,
then you can't help anyone else.
Are you barking at me now?
I'm here to help you guys.
They're here.
Hey, when are we getting the Vlaxco records?
Vlaxco says they're not
gonna give them to us, yet.
They want to help,
but their lawyers are complaining
about breaking patient confidentiality
with a politician.
They say it'll take 12
hours to get us access.
Walter, I saw the governor's daughter,
she doesn't have 12 hours.
Kid's dying, and they're stonewalling.
Bastards won't budge.
What about a court order?
24 hours, at least.
How hard did you push them, Cabe?
You know me.
I tried as hard as I could.
I've been trying to hack Vlaxco's records,
but all confidential drug trials
are kept on an air-gapped system.
That means not connected to the Web.
We can't get it.
If I had another coffee cup in
my hand right now, I'd smash it.
I don't think I'd blame you.
Cabe.
Hmm. Call the governor.
Ask if Vlaxco keeps hard
copies of the study files.
Why am I asking?
We're gonna break in.
I understand that we need
to get all the patients
for the Vlaxco drug trial.
I get that that is where
we're going to find the person
who keeps making these kids sick.
But I think I would be better
suited for an advisory role.
Sylvester, if Cabe gets caught,
it's federal time. If Paige gets caught,
she loses Ralph.
Happy and Toby are the distraction.
I could be the distraction.
N-N-No, you need to memorize the files.
No one else can do that.
It's over a hundred pages long.
I'm gonna be reading the layout
and guiding you through the building, okay?
Okay.
I'm still not clear on what this has to do
with Earl's Sub Shop across the street.
Well, Vlaxco has a brutal security firewall
that would take hours to hack.
But they also have hundreds of employees.
So, statistically,
one of them is gonna
order from Earl's today.
Now, I've hacked into the sub shop's server
and I've placed a Trojan
shell on their PDF menu.
Your Trojan horse is a
two-for-one sub coupon.
That's a really good deal.
Earl knows his way around a hoagie.
Now, as soon as someone
clicks on the PDF menu
and downloads the coupon,
we're past the Vlaxco firewall.
It's lunchtime, so it shouldn't take long.
I'm in.
All right, just going through HR.
Just looking through the
employee security badges.
I'll be damned.
All right, look for someone
in middle management.
A guy driving a low-level luxury sedan,
trying to keep up with the VPs.
That's someone that can really get angry.
- Mmm.
- Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Jed Hausler.
Just copying his data.
Should have a bogus security
badge in a few seconds.
I'm heading over to Happy.
Good luck, Sly.
Governor.
We may have some good news
for you here in a while.
It's an involved operation,
I'll run it down for you later.
My thoughts and prayers are with you,
Governor.
How is she?
She's holding on as best she can.
Walter lied to me earlier about his sister.
Said she'd gotten over a childhood illness,
but I saw a letter that said
she's in a care facility battling MS.
He doesn't talk about her much.
I know, but when he's reminded of her,
he smashes things and tackles people
and does daytime robberies.
I'm just trying to give
him as much space as I can.
Third message.
Just want to reiterate,
I am making real money now.
Can start to re-pay you.
Even if you're seeing someone.
It's totally immaterial.
You can call me back anytime.
She's not getting back with you.
Look, people only let you down.
Sooner you realize that, the better.
That's a cynical worldview.
When I was two,
my dad took me to St. Luke's,
handed me to a nurse and said,
“Find her a good home. ”
Thanks to how my brain works,
I remember every moment of it.
So 25 years later, I'm not cynical...
I'm smart.
You put a quarter-inch wrench
on a quarter-inch bolt, it works.
Tools don't let you down. Only people do.
Spending your life scared
to connect to anyone
isn't any way to live.
Software just picked up Jed
Hausler's license plate.
Let's go find his car.
Here's your earpiece.
- Arpiece.
- Let's go find his car.
The laboratories have
disease samples, Walter.
Like the plague.
They have the actual plague.
Sylvester, you're not going
near the biohazard lab.
I'm gonna be talking you
through the whole way.
Okay, you guys ready?
Looking for Jed Hausler's car.
There! Punch it, sister!
Excuse me.
My wife is the world's worst driver.
Could you find out who owns this car?
You can do this.
You just walk in,
look at the files,
you walk out.
Walk in, look, walk out.
That's our guy. Sylvester...
you're on.
You need to get out of
there before he comes back
and swipes his real ID.
Okay.
Oh...
He looks angry. Perfect.
What the hell did you do to my car?
Not me. Him.
Who was driving?
You distracted me.
Oh, talking is a distraction?
Constant complaining is distraction.
Hey!
Can we please talk about
the damage to my car?
My bad.
Love the 'stache.
Um... $300, we'll call it a day?
There's thousands in damage here.
$350.
Just give me your insurance papers.
Hey, you recently divorced?
There's a tan line where
your wedding ring would be.
I only ask
'cause... I think I'm about
to pull that trigger myself.
All right.
You're looking for 2008, January to August.
Trexicane trial program.
Okay. I got the box.
Okay, get the name of
every patient in the trial.
How long is that going to take?
Accuracy is bliss.
Do you see this?
Cold as Pennsylvania steel.
Maybe if you knew how to warm me up...
That's my supervisor,
who's going to kick my ass.
Hold on. He can wait.
You're the guy just a step ahead of me:
you're back in the single scene,
trading boxers for briefs,
hitting the gym, scoring hair plugs...
Get the hell out of my way and
leave your info at the desk.
Not good.
Yeah, we couldn't hold our patsy any longer.
- He's heading back in.
- There he is.
Mr. Hausler,
it's saying you're already in here.
Well, clearly, I'm not.
I don't want you to panic,
but the guards know
you're in the building.
Oh, boy...
Okay...
Security's been alerted.
They are coming toward the file room.
Okay. All done.
Now,
you can get out through the doors
in the back. To your left.
Walter, you said no biohazard.
You have to.
Anthrax!
Last year the CDC exposed 86
of their own people to anthrax.
Walter, there could be anthrax back there.
Listen to me, you have no other way out.
Walter, there's got to be...
Walter!
We see you on the security cam.
I am in a dirty room, Walter.
Just stay calm. Head out the
east side door. Do you see it?
Yes.
Now, there's a service hall
on the other side. Head down there
to the exit, where we'll be waiting for you.
Sylvester, pick up the pace, pal.
I don't know if you can push
him too hard here, Walter.
This is my worst nightmare. Literally.
I have had this one.
Oh...
Guards are getting closer, Sylvester.
I can't touch that handle.
Logically, it's probably
one of the cleanest handles in the world.
Much better than a public bathroom.
- I don't touch those either!
- Open the damn door,
because if you think this lab's dirty,
wait until you're in a prison cell,
which is where they will take you
if you don't open the door.
No.
Come on, Sylvester.
Get the hell out of there, now.
You cannot be impatient with him.
Sylvester...
it's Paige.
What if you take off your sweater
and put it around your hand?
What kind of deterrent against a
lethal spore is a poly-cotton blend?
Think of something else.
Um... so you got a paycheck today.
What are you going to do with your money?
Get rid of it. Money makes me nervous.
Okay, then close your
eyes and get rid of it.
Okay.
You need to hand over the money...
All right. Oh...
Pull down...
and run like hell!
Come on! Come on!
Her fever's worse.
She's in decline.
Where are we, folks?
Well, based on the names Sylvester got us,
we're pulling background on the
people from the Vlaxco trial.
Now we can look for our suspect.
The last participant in the trial.
So, we have 50 names here.
One of them is our biohacker.
How do we narrow it down?
Our bad guy's gotten kids sick
and made sure the parents knew
it was done intentionally.
That's a real angry dude.
Take it from someone who has dropped
a fortune at games of chance:
nothing makes the psyche
more vindictive than loss.
It's primal;
through vengeance, humans wrongly believe
they can be made whole again.
We need to find whoever
lost the most from this
drug not being approved.
So, 20 test subjects showed
no improvement from the drugs.
So they didn't really lose anything
from being part of the trial.
They entered sick, they left sick.
- We're down to 30.
- Same with those who got the placebo...
their situation didn't change.
They might have been disappointed
they didn't get the real drug,
but that's not loss.
Five died since the trial ended.
They're all out.
Okay, here's where we get down
to the nitty-gritty.
The guys left have all suffered loss.
All would have improved
with the Trexicane drug.
Benjamin Carlisle, maybe?
32 years old,
entrepreneur making six figures.
When he started the study,
he was engaged... world on a string.
Where's he now?
Begging for charity for his treatment,
blogging pretty angrily
regarding his degenerating condition...
and no longer engaged.
If I lost a fiancée to a disease
that could have been cured,
I'd consider revenge.
That's not the guy.
This is.
Robert Richter.
Single dad.
According to this, his child
responded well to the meds
but died after the drug trial was scrapped.
He lost more than anyone.
You're basing this purely on emotion.
There's entire sections of jurisprudence
based on crimes of passion.
Emotion is as good as any of them.
Especially in a case like this.
Trust me.
Guys? There's a Robert Richter
that works at Venice College of Science.
And he is a microbiology professor.
There should be some
evidence here in Richter's office.
I'm sorry, Mr. Richter
is gone for the day.
Um, maybe I should call
campus security first?
Feel free, but my badge is bigger.
We'll take it from here.
All I have in here are exam papers.
Same here.
Oh, oh, oh. Look what I found.
He was computer modeling spray patterns.
I bet he loads
a small aerosol device with the virus;
all he's got to do is get a few feet
from the victim, presses a button
and then he infects them with a gene
that'll kill only them.
Target never even knows.
That's a pretty sophisticated murder weapon.
And scary easy to make.
He's got fast DNA sequencers,
graphene-based nanochannel hardware...
Today, genetic engineering is a hobby;
if you're smart enough,
you can be a modern Typhoid Mary.
Uh... what are you doing?
Happy was right.
Richter is a modern Typhoid Mary,
emphasis on modern.
His daughter died in 2010.
The reason he had to wait
years to retaliate is he had
to wait for technology to catch up
to his plans. But now that it has,
the same technology might
be the thing that stops him.
Here.
Saved in the memory
are the sequences for the killer genes.
And how does that help us?
We send this to CDC,
they can follow the blueprint backwards
to reverse-engineer what
Richter did in two hours.
They can save the people he infected.
They can make an antidote.
Before I send this...
I'm positive.
Great work.
Well, considering we just saved four kids,
maybe we earned a celebratory toast.
Sylvester?
Uh, you really think I'm
gonna drink something
out of a bio lab's fridge?
Well... yeah.
Don't celebrate just yet.
There's another sequence here.
There's a fifth target.
- Fifth target?
Mm-hmm.
That spam creep said he only
sent four e-mail viruses.
Well, maybe this guy didn't get an e-mail
'cause he's special to Richter.
Special how?
This sequence also appears
in a file in Richter's
laptop referring to...
It's the governor.
So, the last one is Governor Lane.
But the sequence is
different from the others.
The sequence targets a potassium channel
in the heart, killing the person instantly.
He's not at his house.
His wife said he ditched security,
went out the back.
They don't know where he went.
The only thing that can keep a
man away from his dying child
is if he thinks he can make her better.
Richter called him.
Promised him an antidote
if the governor would meet
with him and just hear him out.
He's not gonna give the
governor an antidote.
He's gonna give him the virus.
It's not just gonna make him suffer.
It's gonna stop the governor's heart
within seconds.
I put an alarm on the governor's family car.
Why the hell isn't he
answering his cell phone?
It's not on and even if it were,
he wouldn't answer.
Checking GPS.
We'll track him soon.
- Toby, what about Richter?
- I'm getting a bead
on his phone, too.
I got Richter's cell records.
Last call was to Governor Lane,
15 minutes ago.
I warned the governor
about irrational behavior.
I told him not to do anything stupid.
Got him! Got the governor.
- He's at Marina Beach Plaza.
- Really?
Well, then we got a problem,
'cause so is Richter.
Spread out! We need to find the governor!
I got nothing up here!
Ditto that in the...
rotunda.
Lower level's clear.
Okay, okay.
Think about how this would go down.
He sees the police and knows it's
got to happen fast but private.
Toby, anything?
He wouldn't wait in the open.
Not with all the police.
Someplace in here, but someplace quiet.
Side hallways maybe.
I found Richter!
We're on our way.
He's moving towards the target.
I got eyes on him!
Cabe, if he even gets close,
Governor Lane is dead!
Homeland Security! Don't move!
He expelled the virus!
- It'll be aerosolized in...
- Ten seconds!
Based on where the governor is standing,
the interior wind patterns
and s-scattergrams!
Now, you have seven seconds.
- What are you doing?
- Making it rain.
- What?
- To take down the virus.
Two seconds, Walter!
How do we know this worked?
Well, if it didn't, he'd be dead by now.
- He said he had an antidote!
- No, sir.
We already sent the
antidote for your daughter.
He was trying to kill you.
Agent Gallo,
she's gonna be fine.
So glad to hear it, Governor.
I'll tell my team.
The antidote the CDC synthesized is working.
Helena's fever broke.
We're getting reports of the
same from the other victims.
You think I care... getting caught?
Dying in prison?
I died when my daughter did.
I just didn't feel
that I should be the only one
to feel the pain I experienced.
You're not.
I know what it feels like to sit
at your child's bedside.
Watching each breath they take,
praying it won't be their last.
To hold your daughter's hand,
trying to memorize what it feels like
so you won't forget.
Your daughter
too scared to close her eyes,
even when she's so tired,
because she's worried
she won't be able to open them again.
Some things you just can't fix.
You got to live with them.
You don't take innocent lives.
We shouldn't be listening to this.
That man deserved to die.
They all deserved to feel my pain!
No, they didn't.
No one deserves it.
Hey, I'm going to get Ralph.
I got him a new telescope.
And I thought we might set
it up on the roof and grill.
Want to join us?
Uh, maybe later, but thanks.
Okay.
Isn't that called "trying to unring a bell"?
Sometimes it's okay to admit
you don't have all the answers.
You know about my sister, don't you?
How she's still sick?
It's not really my business.
I was just trying to help you today.
For me, my mind...
every problem has a solution.
There must be a solution for her.
Hey.
I should never have yelled at you earlier.
You're the bravest person I've ever met.
That girl would've died today without you.
Without us.
Federal transpo just came
around back and picked up Richter.
I'm on my way out.
Ralph and I were gonna barbecue
some burgers up on the roof.
It would really help if you could keep
an eye on him while I work the grill.
Can I help you?
Yes, uh, this is for the kids.
But nothing for the biology department.
Or a-a lab of any kind.
Something fun?
And safe.
- Hi. This is Dr. Tobias M. Curtis.
- Please leave a message.
Hi, Toby. It's me.
I'm really glad things
are going well for you.
But I don't care about the money you owe.
I moved on.
Please do the same.
And don't call again. Bye.
All in.
You didn't even see your cards yet.
I don't have to.
I see you.
Hey.
Hi, Walter.
Your sister is the best patient we have.
Never quits.
I got my first paycheck.
Well, I hope you're gonna do something fun.
You deserve it.
Yeah, I'm gonna do something for you.
Hey.
MS is my fight, not yours.
I'm not gonna let you die, Megan.
I'm going to fix you.
Cabe, another medium-well?
"Another"?
The last one was raw.
Hi, Walter.
Ralph.
There, I think I'm done, Ralph.
Come check this out.
See all the stars?
There's millions of them up there.
You got a notepad?
Thank you.
You know, having a family
can be a hard thing.
Makes you vulnerable.
I know.
It can be a good thing, too.
Hey. Hey.
Hey, Ralph? If you look at the curvature
of the moon's surface, Orion's belt makes
a perfect horizontal tangent line.
- Isn't that cool?
- It is cool!
Thank you.
No problem.
sync and corrections by dreaMaker7
www.addic7ed.com
BRANDS YOU LOVE,
PRICES THAT WORK FOR YOU.
YOU DESERVE IT.
MAXX LIFE AT T.J.MAXX.
When was the last time your wireless
company made you feel like this?
The new Cricket Wireless believes you
should be doing a lot more of this.
So we don't have any of
those silly annual contracts.
But we do have a whole lot of coverage...
..for not a lot of money.
So everyone can feel like this.
Switch now and get a free 4G smartphone
on our reliable 4G network.
After $50 mail-in rebate
Cricket Visa Promotion Card.
The new Cricket Wireless.
Something to smile about.
MUSICAL CHAIRS. FUN, RIGHT?
WELLLLLLLLL,
NOT WHEN YOUR TRAVEL REWARDS CARD
MAKES IT SO HARD TO GET
A SEAT USING YOUR MILES.
THAT'S THEIR GAME.
THE FLIGHTS YOU WANT ARE BLACKED OUT.
OR THEY ASK FOR SOME
RIDICULOUS NUMBER OF MILES.
HONESTLY, IT'S TIME TO SWITCH
TO THE VENTURE CARD FROM CAPITAL ONE.
WITH VENTURE, USE YOUR MILES ON ANY AIRLINE,
ANY FLIGHT, ANY TIME.
NO BLACKOUT DATES.
AND WITH EVERY PURCHASE,
YOU'LL EARN UNLIMITED DOUBLE MILES.
FROM NOW ON, NO ONE'S TAKING YOUR SEAT AWAY.
WHAT'S IN YOUR WALLET?
www.tvsubtitles.net