WALTER:
My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
Orange, purple, tan, pink,
blue, blue, green.
870!
Don't hit it so hard,
you'll mess up my wiring.
I am going to slap it
like it owes me money.
Speaking of which--
890.
I can do it
with my eyes closed.
Green, purple, purple, pink.
I don't like you
when you're cocky.
Hey! Picked up some
healthier fare for the fridge.
You know, tuna, yogurt...
brain foods...
So glad I try.
Ka-ching!
Come on.
Should I ask?
I rigged the game
so it'll generate a thousand
sequence color pattern.
And you're betting on whether
Sylvester's memorized it.
That's sane.
Where's Walter?
PAIGE:
Hey!
Finally got that Reseda client
to pay for their system upgrade.
I sent them
a lawyer letter.
We don't have a lawyer.
They don't know that.
What's this?
Well, if I can map and download
this fellow's memory
of the maze pattern,
then I can do the same for a human.
Losing me.
I can transfer someone's
thoughts, consciousness,
their very
being forever.
And, unfortunately,
I happen to be working
with a stupid mouse. Hey!
Are you doing this
for your sister?
Yeah.
And for anybody else
whose body betrays them.
What's his name?
(phone rings)
Why would I name a mouse?
'Cause it's fun.
(phone rings)
The phone's ringing!
TOBY:
We're gambling!
This mouse is difficult
and stubborn.
I'll call him Cabe Junior.
(answering machine plays)
That's good.
Remind me why
no digital voice mail.
'Cause you can't hack analog.
(answering machine beeps)
MAN: Um, hi, this message is
for Paige Dineen.
This is Drew Baker.
I know it's been
a long time, Paige,
I got your info from the diner.
I was hoping that we could talk.
No... no, no, no.
I'd really like to see you guys.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Really would.
No. No. No.
I'm at the same cell number.
No. No, no.
Okay, bye.
No, no, no, no. No. No.
The hell was that all about?
Nothing. An acquaintance.
You don't sprint down stairs
for an acquaintance.
Who's Drew?
Old friend.
Bumped from acquaintance
to old friend in three seconds.
Interesting.
Look, it's really not important.
You just put your hand
on your stomach.
A subconscious protection marker
where you once carried a child.
Is Drew Ralph's father?
I didn't know Ralph had a father.
How exactly do
you think babies are made?
You know what I mean.
Not that it's any
of your business,
but Ralph's dad is a minor
league baseball player...
Great, a jock!
We bounced around a lot,
team to team,
and we agreed Ralph
should have some stability.
We settled in L.A. and Drew was
gonna come out after his season.
He got a job pitching
in Mexico, then Tampa,
then you can fill in the rest.
How long has it been
since he's seen Ralph?
Seven years.
Oh, that's great.
Father of the year...
uh, excuse me, seven years.
Drew's a difficult part
of my life
that wasn't easy
to put behind me.
And I'm certainly not dusting
it off with you guys,
so there'll be no further
discussion on this issue.
Paige, you want to know
if he's a good guy?
Watch him eat fruit.
If he digs into the flesh
with his fingernails--
a primordial sign
of aggression.
But if he peels it in one long
curl, that is a planner.
He's right;
I'm very gentle with plums.
Guys, we are not
giving him fruit.
Thank you.
I can just hack his credit info,
see what he's been up to,
if he's any risk to Ralph.
Absolutely not.
This isn't communal
child rearing.
I'll decide if I call Drew back.
No one else.
CABE:
What's going on?
Ralph's father's back in town.
Oh, I see.
Is that something you want
to discuss with everyone?
No.
CABE:
Then it's settled.
Personal business
stays personal.
Besides, we got some real
business to attend to.
Three cons just escaped from
Hamilton Federal Penitentiary.
High-tech prison.
Inmates had
morning exercise;
when they called line-up,
they were gone.
No tunnels,
no compromised
fences, gone.
They want you to determine
how they beat their
state-of-the-art security.
You want us to go
inside of a prison?
Are you serious?
Like a Peek Frean.
The hell's
a Peek Frean?
It's a cookie.
Kind your grandma used
to give out?
They had that slogan--
“Peek Freans are
a very serious cookie.”
How young are you guys?
How old are you?
Let's get in the car.
You know, eight
out of ten inmates had dads
that were in and out
of the picture?
Just saying.
Shut it, Doc.
I may be overstepping my bounds...
You are.
But a quick run of
potentialities yields few,
if any, positive outcomes
from that phone call.
An absent father returning
out of the blue
is fraught with peril.
I know none of you have any idea
how inappropriate this all is,
but it's off the charts.
You've been quiet.
No advice on how
to run my life?
I don't know
anything about dads.
CABE:
Welcome to prison.
Don't worry, son.
You just tell me
how you hacked into NASA,
and I promise everything
will be okay.
(prisoners catcalling,
whistling)
Should Happy and
Paige be here?
They're talking
to you.
Sergey Antonovich and
Roman Volkovsky's cell.
Russian outfit.
Both doing a dime
for identity theft.
Well, clearly scumbags,
but they don't seem
to have the technical acumen
to break out of this place.
This one does.
Here, let me look.
Percy Tate.
You know the guy?
Everybody does;
he's a “hacktivist.”
Borderline genius, IQ-- 150.
The sweet spot-- it's high
enough to be mentally gifted
and low enough
to not be like us.
A few years ago, he didn't like
the voter fraud tactics of a
couple congressional candidates.
So he embedded a virus
into the electoral system.
At the end of the election, he
reset all the votes down to zero
with a message-- “Do it again;
don't cheat this time.”
What the hell is the
Robin Hood of nerds
doing with Russian
outfit guys?
No idea.
Was a model prisoner till he
disappeared without a clue.
Now, our gates are wired
to a central system.
We show no breach.
Security film's clean.
Are all your gates
under surveillance?
All but...
but one.
This is it.
It used to lead
to the loading dock,
but not since an
upgrade 20 years ago.
It ends five feet in.
I don't think they went
through this gate.
I think they just
used it to escape.
Happy?
Right here.
It's been spackled.
Matched the color
with toothpaste.
I'm so turned on.
This wire runs to the gate lock.
And this is
a wireless transmitter
that's been spliced into it.
The escaped cons worked
maintenance duty?
Moved about freely?
Cons with privileges
can move about
during specific periods
during the day.
Including work detail
and morning PT,
when they broke out.
You want to know
how they did it?
When the prisoners returned
their supplies
to the maintenance closet,
they knew that no cameras would
be watching a defunct gate.
So they only needed a minute to
get through that wall.
HAPPY: They attach a transmitter
to catch a signal
to open the gate, which is
then sent to a cell phone.
A transmitter is small.
But a cell phone?
Nothing that big could get
in or out of my prison.
Except convicts.
What?
Hey, has this door been opened
anytime over the last few days?
Antonovich dropped a can
of cleanser through the bars,
and we opened it
to let him get it.
You know, the gates
would only need
to be opened once
to get the access signal.
If the other gates are under
surveillance, they'd be seen.
Not if their phone was
programmed with an EMP device.
Localized burst would disable
a camera for three seconds.
SYLVESTER: That's enough time
to get through any prison gate
and get out of camera range.
I think I know
how they got the phone in.
I'd like to go
outside now, please.
(cell phone buzzing)
WARDEN: This is
the field out here.
Drew didn't get a return call,
so now he's e-mailing.
Focus.
WALTER: Warden, when was the last time
the cons had extended yard time?
Three days ago,
cell-block baseball.
One of the escapees
played right field.
How do you know that?
My dad made me play right field.
The worst player's
always put there because
the ball is usually hit
to the center or to the left.
If a convict was receiving
contraband out here,
like a cell phone,
he'd definitely want
to play right field,
because nobody pays attention
to the right fielder.
So, they smuggled in
contraband during a game.
Surely, you can't be serious.
Serious as a Peek Frean.
And don't call me Shirley.
Bam! That's how you do it, Cabe.
WALTER: It's easier than
you realize, Warden.
See, the Russians are organized
crime, they have outside help.
So, while everyone else
is watching the game,
a bird flies 30 feet
above the yard.
Except, it's not a bird,
it's an MAV,
a micro air vehicle.
Now, black market drones go
for low five figures.
And the drone
drops the phone
right into the right
fielder's glove.
These guys like baseball,
just like Drew.
Did he ever play
in a penal league?
Here you are.
Surveillance of Hamilton
Penitentiary ball game
three days ago.
How did you get that?
Ah, it's
not that hard.
Look! Right there.
There's the drone.
Maybe that's
just a bird.
TOBY: Well, that bird is taking
one heck of a dookie.
CABE:
I'll be damned.
That's a phone.
Whoever made
that drop wasn't far
outside these walls.
Soon as
they were done,
I bet they stopped flying
that bird and just took off.
Assuming a two-pound drone
with a lithium battery,
12-inch wingspan,
six-knot winds,
it would have glided to a stop
roughly 1.37 miles
southeast of here.
Take Sylvester, find that drone.
Look, I don't care about
the location of the drone,
I care about the
location of my convicts.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Here's a satellite image
of one of the cons
running
by the tree line.
I really don't want you
hacking into U.S. satellites
without permission.
I'm not; these are China's.
TOBY:
Hold on.
Look at how that other guy
is grabbing Percy.
How much time did he have left?
Ten months.
Why would he want to break out
now with short time left?
Yeah, maybe he didn't want
to break out.
He's got a funny way
of showing it.
What if they forced him to?
They needed him to escape.
The odds are-- they need him
for something else.
Otherwise, you would have
already found his corpse by now.
Warden, the chances are--
you're dealing
with two jailbreaks,
one kidnapping.
Let me see this.
You know, Percy Tate's
highly intelligent
and was vulnerable here.
He was quite possibly
taken advantage of.
Ralph's also
vulnerable,
like most child geniuses.
I can see you're
getting to something.
I was about
Ralph's age
when Cabe suddenly
appeared in my life.
My dad was a good man,
but he never really
understood me.
So Cabe filled a void.
But when things got
complicated between us,
it was hard to bounce back.
I get it.
But I can handle it.
Okay?
This would be
a tough situation
if Ralph were
a regular kid.
We could look
into the guy.
Ah, she told me not to.
That's right.
She told you not to.
♪ Scorpion 1x07 ♪
Father's Day
Original Air Date on November 3, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
SYLVESTER:
Whoa, whoa, careful.
Don't hurt Birdroni.
You named it?
I didn't have
any pets growing up.
(door opens)
Anything?
The bird wasn't on recon mode,
so there's no film to help us.
But I did
study the code
that Percy used to
rig the election.
It was able to change
vote tallies
in the one-tenth of a second
it took to digitally
transfer the data
from the various districts
to the election commissioner.
He expertly
exploited
a miniscule point
of failure.
He's quite bright.
Make sure you get him
to sign your yearbook
when we arrest him.
You see?
That is the problem.
Percy Tate's a brilliant mind,
and you mock him.
He's a criminal, who clearly
masterminded this breakout.
He's mentally enabled,
and I think he may have been
taken advantage of
because of it.
I'm amazed that geniuses
can even get duped.
WALTER:
Easily.
We become so focused,
we lose peripheral vision,
and it's on the outskirts
where ulterior motives lie.
Geniuses
state facts,
so we assume others
state facts, too.
WALTER:
If you become ostracized
from an early age
for being different,
or if someone targets you
because they have something to gain,
you don't see their motives
until it's too late.
After a while, it starts
to affect your core self.
You trust no one.
Grow up to be distant...
Like Walter.
...or scared of
your own shadow...
Like me.
...angry...
Present.
...or a condescending jerk.
Like Toby. Toby.
Where the hell's the doc anyway?
I have him looking
into something.
Not all smart people
are saints, O'Brien.
Stop letting that genius-sized
chip on your shoulder
cloud your judgment.
(phone ringing)
Gallo.
Really?
Well, “gentleman genius”
Percy Tate and his pals
just carjacked a ride and
sent two guys to the hospital.
Let's move.
TOBY:
♪ Another round ♪
♪ She sells them
whiskey and wine ♪
♪ The sailors say, Brandy ♪
♪ You're a fine girl ♪
♪ What a good wife
you would be... ♪
Sprinkles!
Sprinkles...
Hey.
Excuse me,
have you seen my dog?
No, sorry, I haven't.
See, he's a teacup Chihuahua.
You could easily miss him.
That's probably why
I didn't see him.
He just took off,
and I know a coyote is
gonna swallow him whole.
I'm sick over this.
Well, I'm sure he'll turn up.
Could you drive me
around the neighborhood
to look for Sprinkles?
No, sorry.
I got someplace to be.
Oh...
Excuse me.
(car engine starts)
Condescending jerk.
CABE: There's the security
footage of the carjacking.
Percy's car was found
in the woods a mile from here--
caught a screw in a tire.
Odds are it's the getaway ride,
stashed in the woods
near the prison.
WALTER: Well, that's why
they did this carjacking.
They needed a
new vehicle.
HAPPY:
Civilian clothes, weapons...
I bet that duffel bag has
food, water, money in it.
And a laptop.
For what
other reason
would Percy
still be alive
other than they have some
need for his coding skills?
They're gonna
have him working
at whatever it is
their larger plan is
as soon as they're settled.
If there's a bigger plan
at play here, what is it?
HAPPY:
Hold on.
Rewind that.
Look at Percy's hands.
He's messing with something
behind his back.
He took this number five
from the price sign
and stuck it next to the “X.”
And he pushed it
all the way to the right
from the middle of the rack.
Why?
Okay, the “X” is Roman for ten,
plus five
is 15.
He wasn't pushing it right,
he was pushing it east.
I-15.
I-15 East!
You're reaching.
No, no, no. He knew the cops
would investigate
this crime scene.
He had seconds to leave
a message... he did.
Or he just bumped
into the display.
Let's just assume the guy
with the 197 IQ is right.
We could use
AMBER Alerts on the 15
to send a coded message
so he can contact us.
This guy is borderline genius.
We make it too hard,
he won't get it.
We make it too easy,
we're gonna get responses
from every math geek
out for a ride.
We need a sweet spot.
CABE: Well, you guys do
whatever it is you gotta do,
but I'm gonna need
actionable intelligence
that Percy Tate is
trying to contact you
before I send in personnel.
That's protocol,
and I'm following it.
CABE:
I had to follow protocol.
We had to hold him
until determination
he wasn't a threat.
But three days?
Well, it wasn't ideal.
But now we know
he's just a curious boy,
not a bad one.
Truth is, more we got
to know each other,
I realized he's
pretty amazing.
So amazing,
I think he earned something.
Go ahead.
FATHER: Isn't that
one of the damn things
that started all
this trouble?
Well, I think he'll be
more careful moving forward.
Right, kiddo?
Yes, sir.
On one condition:
You use that to stay
in touch with me.
I'd hate to think
that this would the last time
I'd see someone like you.
SYLVESTER:
Anything?
Walter.
Any-Anything?
Um, made the alerts look like
they're malfunctioning,
but no response yet.
PAIGE:
There's a message
in those I-15 signs?
There's a pattern mimicking
Pascal's triangle.
Each number is the sum
of the two numbers above,
except for the edges,
which are all ones.
If you shade in all
the odd numbers,
what you're left
with is an address
for an online bulletin board
that is secure,
which he can
reach us at for help.
After passing a few signs,
a coder like Percy
should pick up on it.
How could he miss it?
I got general background
information on Mr. Drew Baker.
Great.
What'd you find?
Lots.
From a personality standpoint,
he displayed
just moderate empathy
for someone who just lost a dog.
And when I made
physical contact with him,
he defaulted
to a combative stance
instead of one of defense.
He might have a short temper.
Where'd you touch him?
His lips.
Very softly.
I touched his arm, potato-head.
And not for nothing,
but he was
a little judgmental
when I told him I had
a teacup Chihuahua.
He's a macho putz.
Even worse,
background check shows
he plead guilty to
a battery charge
12 years ago, before
he knew Paige.
I couldn't find
the details online,
but I'm still
looking.
Battery?
And he wants to see Ralph?
This guy, he
seemed impulsive.
I wouldn't put it
past him coming here.
(door bangs)
I'm always right.
Hey.
Can I help you?
DREW: Hi... yeah.
I'm looking for Paige.
Drew?
Walter, I got it.
Why don't you come over here?
Thanks.
Makes me nervous.
PAIGE: What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
It's inappropriate,
but I never heard
back from you
and I'm only in town
a couple of days...
You wanted to see the
child you abandoned?
I don't blame you for hating me.
Has nothing to do with me.
It has to do with my son.
Our son.
My son.
Fair enough.
Look, I know the damage
that I caused
because I just wanted
to run around,
play ball like a child,
act like a child...
But baseball
is going away.
I'm a 31-year-old
washed-up reliever.
Only good thing
I did in my life...
I deserted.
I just...
I want to see
that little baby
that I used to hold.
Well, he is not little anymore.
And he is special
in more ways than
you could imagine.
I know you've
had your hands full
with his developmental delays,
I just...
(Sylvester clears throat)
Would your guest
like some fruit?
Excuse me?
He's fine.
He doesn't want fruit.
Come on, Babe Ruth,
take a peach.
I'm good,
thank you.
Okay.
You were always
an amazing mother.
So whatever you decide to do...
that's the right move.
Just know my
intentions are good,
and I just want Ralph to know
that I never stopped
thinking about him.
WALTER:
It's Percy!
The kidnappers must
have him on the computer!
You need to
leave now.
What do you guys do here?
I need to take
care of this,
so I will let you
know what I decide.
TOBY:
Where is he?
WALTER:
“312 Rural Route 9.
Help.”
That's way out past Newhall.
Not much is out there.
Except
Percy Tate.
Possibly.
But like you said,
someone else could've
cracked the code
and is messing with us.
Cabe wants
“actionable intelligence.”
So we'll confirm he's
there, then call Cabe.
How do we do that?
We can't just walk up and knock
on the door
of their safe house.
We won't have to.
No, no. Birdroni? No.
Looks like the make and model
of the car they stole.
I can't get
a good look.
Oh...
You need to swoop down
past the window on an angle.
You can't let 'em get
a good look at that thing.
I know.
Why are you flying it so low?
I'm just getting the hang of it.
You're scared it's gonna crash
and hurt itself.
It's not a real pet.
I know what I'm doing, Toby.
Just let me do it.
No.
Happy built this for me.
Let... go...
of...
Guys...
Stop it!
SYLVESTER:
Oh, no!
I know I've said
this before,
but not good.
(automatic gunfire)
Stay down.
They don't see us.
Well, this is gonna be
a tough one to explain.
You like those encryptions
I sent you last month?
Only the last few
were difficult.
It took the navy's best
cryptographers weeks
to do what you did in days.
I got something else
I'd like you to do.
Trying to develop a
new tracking software
to drop aid packages
to refugees.
You think that's something
you want to take a crack at?
You want my help?
For a real project?
I'll set it up.
You want to tell me
how you got that shiner?
It's just bullies.
They don't like me
'cause I'm different.
They don't like you
because they're scared
of what you can do.
What do you say I teach you
a few things before I go?
Stand up, get on your feet.
Come on, up.
Get on your feet.
Keep your feet under you.
Get your hands up like this.
All right?
When they come at you,
you're gonna block and counter.
All right? Rule number one.
Always go for the nose.
Hands up.
You ready? Here it comes.
There you go, perfect.
You got to be more
careful, Walter.
You guys could've
been killed.
All right, it didn't go
according to plan,
but I was right
about the kidnapping.
Now's not the time
to poke the bear.
This Russian outfit
has safe houses all over L.A.
and the Inland Empire.
These guys are in the wind now.
SYLVESTER: Uh, Walter?
Seems when Birdroni went
through the window,
he smashed Percy's computer,
but he caught an image
of the laptop.
That is the code that Percy used
to hack the election,
but he's changing it.
He's got
an account-siphon router
with a foreign prefix.
Which means...
Which means
the Russians are making him
modify his software,
and part of it has to do
with sending money overseas,
but I can't tell where
just from looking at this.
I'll have
the Treasury Department
trace this account number.
Percy should be traced as well.
After what happened here,
the convicts must know
that he's the one that tipped
their location.
He won't be able
to contact us again.
They'll be watching him
like a hawk.
So then we'll be watching them.
If we can capture
the digital I.D.
from when Percy IM'd us,
we should be able
to track it
to his computer's IP address.
We can hack his webcam
and watch him,
and maybe we can get a clue
as to where he is
or what they're forcing him
to do.
It's worth a shot.
Let's do it.
PAIGE:
The sitter will be here soon,
but I wanted to talk
to you first.
Okay?
It's a tangram.
It's shapes made out of shapes.
It's squares squared.
Wow.
That's very cool.
Sweetheart,
what do you remember
about your father?
He was tall.
He liked his toast burnt,
and he left to see a movie.
What?
When we left for L.A.,
he said he'd catch up
with us later.
He was just going
to see a movie.
There were 12 theaters
within 20 miles of our home.
48 screens, 227 showings.
Average run time-- 112 minutes.
Maybe he just wanted to stay
and see more movies.
TOBY:
I know you're gonna tell me
to “shut it” again,
but watching a kid learn
that Daddy's come back
has got to be hurting you.
I'm not your patient, Doc.
But you are my friend.
Here.
While checking on Drew today,
I also hacked Social Services,
pulled your records.
There is some photos in there
of your dad, your mother.
My mother died
during childbirth.
You have the wrong paperwork.
Your dad put photos in there in
case you ever pulled your file.
I'm a decent hacker.
I could've gotten this
myself if I wanted.
But he left me.
I am not chasing him.
I don't need him.
I love you, Ralph.
Hi, Ralph.
I'll see you
when I get home.
Hi.
Drive carefully.
Okay.
Bye!
Bye.
Hey.
Uh...
(clears throat)
I don't want
to butt in, but, um,
can I at least ask
how he took it?
I couldn't tell him.
Not yet.
That's prudent.
Maybe the best course is
to never tell him.
What happened to not butting in?
Hey, hey, hey.
People change a lot
over seven years.
You don't even
know Drew anymore.
He might not be
this sweet baseball player
from St. Louis. He may be
a danger.
How do you know
he's from St. Louis?
Um...
You looked into him?
Yeah, we did,
and be thankful that we did,
because he has a conviction
for battery.
“We”?
That's it.
Paige. Paige.
No, no.
No, hold on.
Paige.
Hey!
Listen up.
I don't remember any of you
in the delivery room with me,
or at the E.R. when Ralph
had whooping cough,
or at a single PTA meeting,
but somehow you all
have an equal vote.
Hell, no.
SYLVESTER:
We were just worried.
We love Ralph.
We're only trying to
properly analyze the situation.
This isn't an
analytical issue.
It's emotional,
which means you're ill-equipped.
You're too involved.
You are not Ralph's father,
and whether he meets his dad
is my decision.
SYLVESTER:
Holy smokes!
Guys, it's Percy!
It's Percy, guys.
I tracked his IM handle.
Turn the webcam light off
so the Russians can't see it.
Start recording.
Oh, God.
CABE: What are they saying?
SYLVESTER: No sound.
Mic must have broken when
Birdroni smashed Percy's laptop.
HAPPY: If we could hear them, we
might get a clue where they are.
Oh, zoom in on that chip bag.
Look at it.
The polypropylene film
is vibrating from the sound
waves of the convict shouting.
I know what you're thinking.
I think we all do.
I'll prep
the wave imaging software.
Where are all the chips?
I replaced them with healthier choices.
TOBY: Okay.
CABE: What the hell
are you guys doing?
Do you hear the gravel
in that voice?
You're our guy.
Wait a minute,
I'm nobody's guy
until I know
what the hell's going on.
Russians, from a historical
genetic standpoint,
have more elastic soft tissue
from folic acid deficiency.
A thousand years of vodka
and cigarettes
will do that to you.
The result is long vocal cords
and deep voices.
You're our closest vocal match.
You'll say the phonetic alphabet
near that bag,
and these sensors will record
the ripple waves on the bag
that correspond with each sound.
WALTER: Now, we'll compare
them to the waves
Sylvester's software
picks up from the film
on Percy's bag.
And when the waves match,
we'll know the sound
being said on film
even though we can't hear it.
You got it?
Does it really matter?
No. Now start.
A.
B.
C.
What are you doing?
It's not ABC, it's phonetics.
Ah-A-eh, B-beh-buh, like that.
All right, take it easy.
It's my first time yelling
at a bag of chips.
A.
Ah, eh.
TOBY:
Good job, Cabe.
It's working; keep going.
B, buh...
A moment while Cabe finishes up?
Yeah.
C.
Uh...
Not that I need to explain
anything to you,
but Drew was pitching in Toledo,
and he nailed a batter
who had homered off him earlier.
He broke the guy's forearm.
Prosecutors brought
charges to get some press,
and Drew took a plea.
That's the battery charge.
I'm a little overprotective
of Ralph,
which I'm sure you understand.
Look, for what's it worth,
I am gonna tell Drew no.
I think it's too confusing
for Ralph right now.
Maybe when he's older.
It's your decision.
SYLVESTER:
The software matched
Cabe's waves to the waves
on Percy's bag.
It couldn't pick up everything,
but we got an “S,” an “O”,
a “C,” a “K”.
“Sock.”
“Change.”
“Sock change.”
What the hell does that mean?
Wait.
Percy's election code
took advantage
of a tenth of a second gap
in vote reporting,
and the cons are forcing him
to change it to siphon money.
Could he be tweaking it to
exploit the split-second gap
from when a stock price is set
to when it's publicly posted?
Sock change, stock exchange.
Okay,
if this virus code gets uploaded
to the stock exchange server...
They could trade stocks on price
data before anybody has it.
They could make billions
with no one ever knowing,
but why do all this now?
Quick Google
on the exchange software
shows a major upgrade
for next month.
Percy's code wouldn't work
when that happened.
No one who's planning
something like this
leaves witnesses behind.
Percy is dead the minute
he finishes that code.
He needs to know we found him.
The Russkies ain't looking.
Flash that cam light.
TOBY:
There.
His eyes locked in on the light.
They're not looking,
you jackass.
Tell us where you are.
Sweet baby Jane,
is that Morse code?
You know Morse code?
How old are you?
Vandekarp...
Farm.
Building “S”!
Let's go.
(phone rings)
Hold a beat.
Just got a text from
the Treasury Department.
They ran a trace
on that foreign account.
It's only in Percy's name.
What does that mean?
It means that Percy was planning
on ripping off the Russians
this whole time.
He's not as innocent
as we thought.
TOBY:
Percy's ingenious.
He has a code that can steal
billions with no one knowing,
but in a month it's useless,
so he knows he has to break
out of prison now,
but he doesn't have
the wherewithal
to get a phone smuggled in,
a getaway car, a safe house.
He needs the Russians.
So he breaks out
with them,
sets up his
get-rich-quick scheme,
and figures
he'll just do something
to get them all busted.
Like stick a screw in the tire
of the getaway ride.
Enough to get the cops
on their trail.
We played
right into his hands.
Once he gets caught,
he plays innocent,
says he was forced to run,
maybe gets an extra year.
He gets out,
he's got a fortune overseas.
But his plan was to be captured,
not almost captured.
So after we almost nabbed him
at the safe house,
the Russians knew
he tipped us off.
They beat the truth out of him,
and now his last act on earth
is gonna be to make
those guys rich.
Walter, does that
sound right to you?
CABE: Walter,
are you still there, son?
I know that's my software
they're using to drop bombs,
not aid packages.
It'll kill thousands
of innocents.
I didn't know that was
the endgame, son.
I swear.
Yeah, it sounds right to me.
He deceived us.
He took advantage of us.
Everything that normals
usually do to geniuses.
I thought
he was one of us.
I want to nail this guy.
CABE: Homeland will come in
from the south
to Building “S.” Your
men will hit the north.
It's a silent maneuver in case
they have police scanners.
So comms off.
We'll drive halfway there,
then we'll hoof it
so they don't
hear our approach.
Copy that.
Target's 800 yards on
the other side of the compound.
So you'll be safe here.
See you when
we got the bad guys.
My team, with me!
It looks like Percy's
getting close to finishing
that code for them.
He's Morse-coding again.
“Near... done.
Selp?”
He means “help.”
Oh, my God, “S” is three dots;
“H” is four dots.
I sent Cabe to Building “S”
instead of Building “H”!
Oh...
Hey, Cabe!
He's going to the wrong side
of the compound.
Call him.
We can't.
The comms are off.
Once Percy sends that code
to the stock exchange,
he's as good as dead.
We gotta get him out of there.
We're not putting
ourselves in danger
for someone who's been
playing us this whole time.
WALTER:
We're gonna save him
because I want the satisfaction
of looking him in the eyes
when he's cuffed.
Let him know:
the people he manipulated?
They're the ones who are
sending him back inside.
How do we rescue a man
being held by armed Russians
in an abandoned dairy farm
outside Camarillo?
TOBY: You have no idea
how many times
I've been asked that question.
Guys, Building “H” is close.
Follow me, follow me.
Okay, Happy, see if you can get
any gas out of that tractor.
Paige...
find her something
to collect it in.
You got time to fill me in?
The farm was built
in the '20s.
Means old knob
and tube wiring,
so no grounding conductor.
Now, if I target concentrated
micro-frequency waves--
which this remote emits--
to the second floor
circuit breaker,
then I can cause it
to short out.
But I will need
an accelerant.
Which I almost
have for you.
Even if we get
a fire going
to flush them out,
they have guns.
Then so will we.
I have an idea.
Doc,
come with me
and bring your laptop.
WALTER:
Okay.
I should be getting
some short-circuiting
and smoke through
the circuit breaker by now.
Can't take my hands
off the remote control,
so I'm gonna need
one of you to throw
that accelerant
through the window.
Hurry.
Me?
I couldn't hit a donkey's ass
with a banjo.
You played baseball.
I played right field.
Are you serious?
As a Peek Frean.
Please.
You can just let me go.
No one will know.
Shut up and finish!
I need that accelerant.
Sylvester, this is your
chance to show your dad
he was wrong to stick
you in right field.
I know you can do it.
Come on.
You can do it.
One more time, go.
Okay.
Yes.
(laughs)
(groaning)
(yelling in Russian)
(all gasping)
There's fire everywhere!
Let's get out of here.
(speaking Russian)
TOBY: Freeze! FBI!
Drop those heaters
before I put more
holes in you
than a salt shaker!
Yeah, that's right,
turkeys!
Got you lit up
like Chinese New Year!
(quietly):
Happy...
stop shaking that DVD laser
so much.
Shut up.
THUG: If you shoot,
we kill this guy!
TOBY: Oh!
Oh, you want to kill
a convict?
Go ahead!
But you want to dance,
let's dance!
I got nothing to lose, comrade!
What is wrong with you?
Russian men grow up watching
bootleg American
'80s action films.
I'm the crazy, unpredictable
cop with a suicidal streak.
It's working.
What the hell's this?
HAPPY:
Oh, man...
Your laptop is dying.
If you're FBI, show yourself.
No.
We're in trouble.
TOBY:
Okay! All right! Don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
Who else is with you?
No one.
Just us.
(clattering)
THUG: Show yourselves
or your friends die!
Walter...
Take Paige. Go.
We are not leaving you.
Walter's the boss, okay?
You were right.
Ralph needs you to
look out for him.
Not a bunch
of geniuses.
Now go.
Go.
Coming out!
Unarmed!
Come on, come
on, let's go.
THUG:
Hey, who are you?
Federal agents.
You're surrounded.
Nice try.
We'll shoot
them inside,
let the fire take
care of the bodies.
Let's go.
Move!
CABE: Drop your weapons!
(gunfire)
(grunting)
Don't move.
AGENT:
Freeze!
AGENT 2:
Let me see your hands!
Look at that...
you remembered
to go for the nose.
Come on, in the truck,
all the way in.
WALTER: It's bad enough when people
who aren't enabled exploit us,
but if we can't
trust each other...
(scoffs)
...there's no one left.
I know you're not wrong
often, but you're...
taking this miscalculation
of Percy pretty strong.
I don't care
about Percy.
Is this about
you and me?
What happened with Baghdad
when you were a kid?
You were the closest thing
I had to a father
and you betrayed me.
I don't think
I've ever really
forgiven you for that.
And that's why
you've been worried
about Ralph's old man
coming around.
You're worried
he might get hurt
just like I hurt you.
We should get back.
HAPPY:
Hey.
I know we don't know
each other that well,
but I gotta say
something to you.
Please don't talk
to me about Drew.
You are the only
one who hasn't
tried to tell me
how to parent today.
I don't want to talk about Drew.
I want to talk about Ralph.
Oh, well, it was nice
while it lasted.
Listen to me.
Walter thinks he knows
what's best for that kid.
You think you know
But the truth is,
I know what's best
for that kid.
Happy...
My dad disappeared.
Ralph counted all the movies
his father may have seen;
I watched from the windows
of a dozen foster homes
for a red truck
with a dented fender.
We have both spent
our lives waiting
for someone to come home.
Just to know
we still matter.
So if there's even a chance
you can end what
Ralph's going through,
then you do it.
That's it; I'm done.
Hey.
You're going to let him
meet Ralph.
No.
I'm going to let
Ralph meet him.
I'm doing it for my son.
Not Drew.
You're going to tell him
Ralph's a genius.
That carries risk.
If Drew's going to have
a relationship with his son,
he needs to know who he is.
And Ralph's mind
is one of the things
that makes him special.
Moving forward,
no more interfering.
But if Ralph
does need me...
I will be
close by.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
I, uh, was wondering
if you're hiring.
Sorry.
I'm barely keeping this
place afloat myself.
Okay.
Thanks.
It's tough out there, huh?
Been outta
work long?
No.
I got a job.
It's just intense at times.
Wrenching relaxes me.
Me, too.
Okay...
Take it easy.
Hey...
Yeah?
You know, you can,
uh, save some time
if you come in underneath
the oil gasket.
Is that right?
You mind?
No.
Why don't you go ahead?
Little light?
Yeah.
You're good.
Thanks.
Hey...
Hi, Ralph.
Want to sit?
I'm really happy
to see you again.
WALTER: How'd you know
I'd be here?
You look after the kid,
I'll look after you.
Just like I used to.
That's how this is gonna work.
Okay?
Okay.
Peek Frean?
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net