My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
♪ ♪
Hey. Uh, reservation for two,
under Curtis.
Can I get you a drink
while you wait for your other party?
Uh, no, thanks.
He'll be here any minute.
One and one.
Baker waiting again.
Brock at second,
Russell on first.
And the pitch on the way.
♪ ♪
One and one.
Another refill?
I'm gonna kill him.
♪ ♪
Probability
theory dictates
that one cannot
predict the future
with any absolute
certainty.
But this is an exception--
there is zero chance
that she will accept
your apology.
I'm not gonna apologize;
I'm gonna grovel.
Understood, but still
there's a high likelihood
that she will throw something at you.
Stop talking.
Good luck.
Peace offering.
These chocolates have nuts.
Get it? Nuts?
Is this thing on?
I don't have
any feelings,
and even
I'm uncomfortable watching this.
John 8:32. "The truth
will set you free."
The truth is
I'm an idiot.
I was nervous
about our date,
so I took an Alprazolam.
Apparently, I should've
taken a half.
Because I didn't wake up
till 6:00 a.m.
So I'd be so humbled
if you'd please
accept these.
I anticipated that.
Frank! You're on!
♪ To err is human,
to forgive divine ♪
♪ Toby'd like to buy ya some
cheese and some wine... ♪
Frank, get out of here.
It's not safe.
♪ ♪
Well, that didn't
go so well, did it?
Wow, that's very
astute, 197.
An observation?
You learned
a very inexpensive lesson.
Workplace entanglements
are ill-advised,
destined to fail,
not to mention disruptive to...
business.
Oh, well, business
will have to suffer,
'cause I'm not giving up.
I'm imploring you to let it go.
Romance and work are...
oil and water.
Um, this is...
exhibit A
for Affective
Dysregulation,
the inability to
regulate feelings.
You couldn't even bring yourself to
erase stick figures
of you and Paige
holding hands.
I just wiped down the board--
I didn't pay attention
to every last mark.
Even more
Affective Dysregulation,
you emotional Dumpster fire.
This clearly
a psychological marker
of your feelings for her,
and Drew's coming back soon.
So all I'm saying is,
if you sit on the sidelines,
you are going to lose this game.
Oh. Sports.
My favorite.
Yeah.
Maya Hernandez, an accountant
for the violent
Nicaraguan criminal organization
known as the DL,
was shot at yesterday
while being transferred
to court,
barely escaping with her life.
Hey, Happy is smelting
titanium over copper,
resulting in an inefficient
transfer of electrons.
Should I call the cops?
What?
No. She's...
clearly distracted
by her issues with Toby.
Discord is...
bad for the team.
You need to make sure
that things go back
to the way that they
were prior to this dating nonsense.
Consider it done.
I have a problem.
Okay.
Hello.
Uh, this is the last cup
of the discontinued
Boysenberry Blast
that was in the fridge.
The "sell by" date
was two days ago.
And?
And do I eat it, risk a
raging bacterial infection?
That's what you're worried about?
Uh-huh.
That woman there...
is the target of
a vicious crime syndicate,
and you're worried
about yogurt?
Hernandez, who has
Well...
intimate knowledge
of the financial workings
of the deal,
is set to testify
against the cartel next week
in Ventura County,
where the venue
has been reassigned
after this recent attempt
on Ms. Hernandez' life.
The DL is led
by Hector Menjivar,
seen here in a 2009 mug shot,
when he was sentenced to three
years for aggravated assault.
Poor lady.
Yeah.
Imagine having those guys after you.
New case.
Oh. Well, what is it?
Them.
The DL crept up from
Nicaragua in the '80s.
Started out in
carting, trucking.
Small-timers who did little more
than rigged bids to get jobs.
After a while, they graduated
to shipping for hire.
Drugs, guns, bodies, whatever
you wanted to move discreetly,
they carried in their trucks
for the price.
Their boss,
Hector Menjivar.
Government's been trying
to nail him forever.
Guy's slippery.
And this witness, Maya Hernandez,
- she was part of their group?
- She's a civilian.
A neighborhood girl who took
a job as their bookkeeper
when she was 19.
Her husband was a driver.
They had no idea
who they were really working
for until it was too late.
Did you say her husband
was a driver?
He was killed
a few months ago.
Rival runners took him out
just north of San Francisco.
Collateral damage in Hector's war to
expand his territory.
That's why she wants
to help shut down the DL.
People are scared of these guys.
They don't normally testify
of their own free will.
But we can't find the books
outlining
these guys' activities.
She's the linchpin.
So you trumped up
a conspiracy claim,
make it seem like
she was part of it,
and then told her you would drop
the charges only if she testified.
That's scummy.
We are giving her protection.
She almost got shot to ribbons
under your protection.
That's why we're here.
To assist the U.S. Marshals
in strategizing
a safe means of transport
for the witness
from L.A. to Ventura. Sly?
We suggest
losing the standard parallel
formation, instead employing
a convoy configuration,
which reduces surface area
and vulnerabilities
that were exploited
by the DL's last attack.
We put Ms. Hernandez
in the fourth SUV,
owing to the rule of threes--
the human brain fatigues
after viewing the third object
in a row of pattern,
making the fourth vehicle
the safest spot psychologically.
Also, we use
decoy cars, because,
well, decoys work.
Lastly, Maya needs
to be wearing this.
She's a witness,
not a prisoner.
Yeah. There are prisoner transfers at
the courthouse every day.
The DL will be looking for
someone in civilian clothing.
So the bright orange jumpsuit
actually disguises her.
All right. Anything else?
My team will follow the convoy
with Cabe,
providing a mobile tech hub.
Sylvester will hack the GPS
systems to clear traffic.
Happy will handle any mechanical
issues; Toby will scan
the route to predict
attack patterns.
I will ride with you and Maya
to quarterback
and make real-time adjustments.
So, are you capable
of keeping up with us?
Well, you know
what they say:
good, fast, polite--
pick two.
Lady, this jumpsuit
is too small for me.
It's a four.
You said four.
Oh, I guess prison fashion
runs really small.
I can get you another.
Whatever.
I'm sorry about
your husband.
We'll protect you.
Protect me? Lady,
Paige.
please... Paige...
You guys are
just taking me to my funeral.
So what the hell
do I care
what I'm wearing, right?
I'm just gonna be buried in it.
I'll be with Cabe.
Be careful.
♪ ♪
Sylvester, do you have a clear
path for us to the freeway?
I'm spoofing fake phones
with static GPS
all along our route
to simulate gridlock
all the way
to the entrance ramp.
It'll be
a virtual car-pocalypse.
No one will be on our route.
Smooth sailing.
All right, we're
passing Grand Avenue.
Straight ahead
for another 5.6 miles.
Roger that.
Excuse me. Why are we slowing down?
School bus ahead.
Not a neighborhood
you take class trips to.
There are no schools
in this area.
I don't see any children
on that bus.
It's an ambush.
They're cutting us off!
Oh, my God, they've got guns!
All SUV's scatter. Repeat:
scatter!
Walter,
you have any eyes on them?
Nothing. Passing
38th and Spring.
Got it. Recalibrating route.
♪ ♪
Check this out.
Truck at six o'clock.
No front license plate.
Coming in fast.
Turn into the alley.
Changing course.
False alarm.
False alarm. We're clear.
Okay, continue north.
There's a highway entrance
half a mile away.
Copy that.
Oh!
It's him.
How'd they know
which SUV we were in?
What's going on?
Cabe, it's Hector.
He's on us.
Get us the hell
out of here!
Axle must have cracked.
We're not goin'
anywhere.
Shoot them!
This entire vehicle's
bulletproof.
If we shoot,
it'll ricochet
off the glass
and kill us.
Get down!
What is he doing?
I want the girl.
♪ Scorpion 1x20 ♪
Crossroads
Original Air Date on March 30, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I want the girl.
I said give me the girl!
Do something.
We need backup.
Impact destroyed
the radio.
Cabe, we need help.
We're near 36th and Avalon.
We'll be there in four minutes.
Sending for backup now.
He knows.
He can't break the windows
so he's going
for the door locks.
The shotgun.
The shotgun. Give me the shells.
Give me the shells. Now.
Come on.
Okay, okay.
If we can get these shells
hot enough, they'll combust.
He's gonna get in!
The gas! Floor it!
All right,
there's a hose in there
that leads to the heater core
which is next to the engine.
Keep the pedal down
and get the temperature up.
But if this thing
blows up,
we're five feet
from it.
A bulletproof vehicle
with a reinforced cage.
Still, you're up front so you'll
take the brunt of the force,
so I suggest you get down now.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on.
Meet us at end of
the 6th Street Bridge!
Comin' up on it now.
Five blocks from the courthouse
and the DL was already on us.
The route was classified.
We maximized security
at the weakest points.
We had less than a .1% chance
of failure.
It was a mole, someone inside
the LAPD or the Marshals.
There's no other
explanation.
Those bastards have their finger
in every pie you can imagine.
Wouldn't be the first time
that law enforcement
took a payout from scumbags.
So now we're on our own.
No convoy. No backup.
No chance in hell.
No. No, I said
we'd protect Maya,
so we will. We just need
to readjust our plan.
We don't know who
we can trust.
We're gonna have to
get her back ourselves.
Hector will spot this
government SUV in a second.
I'm gonna have to get
a new vehicle.
There's an Earl's Used Car Lot
not far from here.
When I'm done with Earl, he is
not gonna know what hit him.
Look,
this is clearly
a government vehicle,
not in any of your names.
Hotter than the devil's armpit.
You want to make this swap,
you got to throw in some cash.
It needs brakes, brake liners,
shocks, new transmission,
and the engine's
barely an engine.
Got to buy the last vehicle
they'd ever expect
to find us in.
Okay, Earl, let me guess.
You're thrice divorced.
Four to six kids.
One bad knee
and two blocked arteries.
How do you...
It's a gift I have.
You had a woman
you cared about once,
hence that 1968-era necklace
around your neck--
clearly a gift from her.
But you messed up.
Now you wish you could do things
over and take away that hurt
you caused her.
Throw in cash
or no deal.
Earl, you haven't had
a full bank account
or a decent BM in years.
You're overplaying your hand
because you think
we're desperate,
but the truth is we're
just desperate enough to trade
a $40,000 car for a $2,000 piece
of crap. You do that,
you can belly up to the bar
with a fat wallet
to impress
the ladies.
You've been lonely for a while,
Earl.
It's about time you feel good
about yourself again. Hmm?
♪ ♪
I feel like we should be
cranking some Skynyrd
in this thing.
Takes me back.
To what?
The '70s.
I wasn't born yet.
Screw you.
You okay?
I'm on the run with a bunch
of geeks in a conversion van
that smells
like a dog dipped in soup.
You just seem a little flushed.
Oh, you think we got away?
We didn't.
Hector doesn't give up.
And odds are overwhelming
that we won't outrun him
in this vehicle.
They have cars from this decade,
not to mention
semiautomatic weapons.
I heard over
the comms,
they got 44 rounds off
in a matter of seconds.
48 rounds. I heard them ricochet
off the hood.
Well, uh,
since we have a-a break
from action,
Walter wanted me to talk to you.
Nothing to talk about.
The doc is dead to me.
I know
bouncing from foster home
to foster home,
you probably feel like people
let you down your whole life.
But I-I think you should give
Toby another chance.
I guarantee that's not what
Walter wanted you to say to me.
He wants you to get along,
and I think you can.
As more than friends.
It's just gonna take time
because you're...
both different.
Unique.
Odd. Weird.
I'm dust, aren't I?
Pretty much.
Damn it. We're overheating.
Our man on the inside
has Maya on the road
with something
called scorpions.
The band?
Nerds.
Whoever they are, we'll find
them and smoke them, too.
Maybe sooner
than we think.
It's a beaut.
Owned by a family that just
puttered around town in it.
We know
who owned the car.
Now we need to know
which way they went
and what they were driving.
A piece of crap.
Great pick, Doc.
We needed a ride that would
keep us under the radar.
We under the radar now?
Out in the open
with a smoking van?
They're not looking
for a van.
They're looking for an SUV.
And you're the mechanic.
You should've figured out
this thing was a dud.
Cut it out. Both of you.
I thought you were gonna fix
things with them.
It's a work in progress.
Gonna need some coolant
and a new radiator hose.
All right, kids.
If you need to hit the head,
now's the time because we're not
stopping once we hit the road.
You know you're not our dad,
right?
Stop acting like kids,
I'll stop acting like your dad.
♪ ♪
Bathroom?
Through the back.
Excuse me. Do you carry
the yogurt Boysenberry Blast
but fresh?
So you like salty sweet.
I liked that, too,
when I was pregnant.
The cravings,
plus your clothes not fitting.
Let me guess,
end of first trimester?
11 weeks.
It's great.
My child gets to be born
with a target on his back.
You really don't think
the government can protect you
from Hector after you testify?
I don't think
you guys can even protect me
the rest of the way to Ventura.
♪ ♪
Cabe!
Oh!
Get the girl!
Over here, over here.
Ladies.
I only want one of you.
But I'll kill all three of you.
We need to get
this van running.
The hoses and the
coolant are inside.
That's not really
an option right now.
I'll take care of the hose.
You find
a temporary coolant, okay?
Okay. I have an idea.
I need this, uh, CO2 canister,
but I also need
a-a PVC pipe and some kind
of small, hard object.
Top of the aisle. Paper towels
are on the second shelf,
six and a half feet away from
the cookie rack. Urinal cakes
are on the third shelf
just below the arthritis cream.
Maya, I'll go. Happy,
work on the canister.
You don't cross the DL.
Aha!
Huh?
Beer, Toby?
It's malt liquor.
All right.
That's good.
I know what that sound is.
You're as good as dead.
Ladies, get in the van!
Actually, not the first time
I've said that.
Come on! Let's go!
All right, hold on, guys.
We got to hurry,
that was close.
Um... what's that new smell
coming from the vent?
40 ounces of smooth,
satisfying flavor.
And they're going to be back
in a few seconds with more guys
and we're dead.
I know a way out of this--
you can just let me go.
I'll just disappear.
You'll have no protection.
Oh, as opposed to now?
Going 85 on a front left
and back right tire
that are both a 16th inch
from being totally bald?
Okay, that's it,
you are not normal.
Who besides these guys computes
tire tread on wheels
they've seen a split second?
And you knew to the inch
where the supplies would be
for my urinal cake cannon?
Your what now?
You corrected me on the amount
of the bullets fired
by Hector and Jorge,
and no one corrects me
when it comes to math,
but you were right.
I'm good with numbers.
When you watch a pinwheel,
can you replay it in your mind
in slow motion
to count the revolutions?
Only when I'm bored.
Yeah, you're a genius.
I'm guessing 164,
with a specialty in visual
inferential mathematics.
You can record and compute
what you see.
Now that explains the low EQ.
What the hell is a low EQ?
That.
Okay, well,
I can take care of myself.
It's not just about
you anymore.
You think being on the run
will be good for your pregnancy?
You're pregnant?
Oh, boy.
We are averaging
70 miles per hour
and the goons are gaining
on us at at least a hundred.
We'd need a racecar.
Actually, I-I know a place near
here where we could get one.
Who owns this place?
Guy named Ricky Lambert.
He's a hacker who does contract
work for the DL.
He hacks into government
databases
and then he makes fake IDs
and passports
so they can smuggle contraband
overseas.
Pays better than
what we're doing.
Actually, he's broke.
He had to take
a loan out from the DL.
Dude likes to blow his money
on bad habits.
I wouldn't know anything
about that.
Lamborghini Aventador LP 700?
It's great.
We'd only need four of them.
What about that?
That's a top-of-the-line,
655-horsepower, diesel RV.
With the latest
in smart car tech,
including digital load
balancing, four-wheel braking.
We could modify the onboard
computer to maximize speed.
With that, we could outrun
the DL and get Maya to safety.
Again, being forced
to testify against the DL
is not returning me to safety.
For now, we just gotta make sure
the DL doesn't catch up to us.
Security's tight.
It'd be tough to sneak through.
Don't even try.
Lambert likes to use his muscle.
He likes to pretend he's Hector.
Problem is, we don't have
any muscle of our own.
Yeah, but Lambert
doesn't know that.
Mr. Lambert.
These men claim
to have business with you.
Who the hell are you?
Well, the organizations
who hire me call me Mr. Green.
This is my associate.
Afternoon.
I've come on behalf
of Hector Menjivar.
I believe you know him.
He's someone you owe
in a substantial way.
I suggest you invite us in.
Yeah, sure thing.
Yeah, I don't want any trouble.
Thank you.
According to our information,
Mr. Lambert,
you owe Hector
a quarter million dollars
and he doesn't believe...
What? No.
No. I don't owe him
anywhere near that.
Allow me to refresh your memory.
You borrowed $170,000
at 19 points, which bumped up
to 20 points after six months.
After compounding interest,
you owe $252,187.63.
Sly, I think
you've met your match.
After compounding interest,
you owe $252,187.63.
So, did I...
did I miss anything?
No.
Ooh, the timbre in his voice
means you were right.
Seal the deal; intimidate him.
Tell him you want the money now.
I want the money now.
What?
Tell him he wouldn't want
to make you angry.
You wouldn't want me
to get angry.
Tell him he wouldn't like you
when your angry.
Okay, what is he, the Hulk?
You wouldn't like me
when I'm angry,
because my adrenal cortex
releases stress hormones,
I become irritable
and I might possibly even
raise my voice.
Nevermind, just slam the table.
Come on, Walt, harder!
Is this guy crazy?
You have no idea.
Now, Hector told me
to leave here
with either collateral,
or your left hand,
so which one is going to be?
Close the door.
We got to get out of here
before he catches on.
All right, done.
Let's go.
Hector, it's Lambert.
Look, I want you to know
I wasn't...
I wasn't trying
to dodge my debt. Okay?
Your guys are on their way
with my RV now.
I'll get you the rest
in a week.
The hell are you talking about?
Hurry up.
It's hard to see behind you
in this thing.
I think I hit one of the rocks.
All right, floor it.
Come on.
Come on!
What is that noise?
We gotta move, Cabe.
Come on.
I can't! We're stuck!
Open the gates.
All right, okay, okay.
Okay, close the gates.
Mm, got it.
Happy, where are you?
Come on, come on, let's go.
Oh, oh, no.
Come on, come on, come on.
What are you doing?
I'm making it so
they can't follow us!
Open the gate now!
Everybody okay?
Still here.
I dropped my yogurt
when we were running, so no.
This guy has a lot of toys.
What about you, Maya?
You all right?
No.
This is never going to end.
I know that Agent Gallo thinks
that the government
can keep me hidden,
but you see now the fear that
Hector strikes into people.
Just the idea
that he was angry
got Lambert to hand over
a luxury RV.
He has people who don't even
work for him, shooting at us.
I mean, people kill for him.
And after I testify,
he will kill me.
And my child.
I get it,
but what are we going to do?
The Feds want her to testify
or do time for refusing.
They need her.
There's nothing
we can do about it.
I don't like it
any more than you guys.
What if they didn't need her?
They're building a case, Walter.
She's their evidence.
She knows their books,
their operation.
She was their bookkeeper
for years.
What if we can create
the books.
Books that Maya
has the information for.
We all heard her back there.
She knows every detail
of their operation
down to the last penny.
We create a computerized diary
of all the DL's dealings.
We just need to make it look
like it was created
a couple years ago
with digital imprints
that even the best forensics
won't be able to tell are fake.
If it contains everything
in Maya's head,
then the Feds don't need Maya
and Hector and his pals
still go up the river.
Can you guys really do that?
Yes.
No.
That's fabricating evidence.
The Feds want her on the stand,
under oath.
Um, Maya.
Do you swear everything
you're going to tell us
will be the truth, the whole
truth and nothing but the truth?
I do.
That works for me.
That's a dirty magazine.
Yes, it is.
It's revolting.
Cabe, we need a solution,
so if you're just going
to shoot this down,
then I hope you have
another plan to save Maya.
Happy, take the wheel.
I need to make this
as legal as possible.
Hector. Look, Hector,
if I knew who they were,
I would've killed them on site.
Okay, please.
I thought they
were with you.
And I thought you were
someone who was smart.
You take your time
paying me back,
now you let a bunch
of computer nerds
slip right through your fingers.
Computers.
That's it.
We got 'em.
And the phony alcohol stamp
business netted 128?
$128,040.12 in
September of 2008.
In one month? All right.
What's the next entry?
Hey.
Can I tell you a story?
I'm driving a 30,000
pound vehicle.
I am focused on the road.
I'll be quick.
When your mom is bipolar
and your dad is so passive
that he sometimes doesn't talk
to his son for weeks on end,
not because he's mad at you
but because he forgets
you're there,
you grow up with nothing good,
and you begin to think
you deserve nothing good.
So when something good
is right in front of you,
or next to you,
you self-sabotage
because you wouldn't know
what to do
with something good
if you had it.
I'm truly sorry, Happy.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I have worn perfume
once in my life.
Last night.
And I won't do it again.
Look, last
night saved us
a year of nonsense
that would've resulted
in us not
being friends.
It's better this way.
Going back to normal.
I think it can still work.
We have problems.
Yeah, we all have problems, Happy.
No, we have serious problems.
Who doesn't have serious
problems, you know?
That's what makes us human.
No, idiot. I'm not
in control of the RV.
Someone's hacked
into the onboard
computer and taken
control of this rig.
I have complete autonomy
over the vehicle.
There's nothing they can do.
Oh, man, we're still
accelerating.
Pull the emergency brake.
Uh, nothing. They cut
the power steering.
Okay, I've basically got no
control of a 15-ton vehicle.
We're screwed.
Hector must have Lambert doing this.
I'm buckling up.
I can barely keep this thing
on the road.
I'm burying the needle
on these guys.
Someone grab the wheel.
I've got it.
According
to the navigation system,
we're coming to
a three and a half-mile
straightaway,
ending in a sharp turn and a
steep drop off. At this speed
we won't make that turn.
That gives us
two minutes and 38 seconds
until we drive off of the cliff.
Yeah, not if we regain control
of the onboard computer.
Ah, he cut off the wireless.
I can't hack in.
We have to manually
access it. Happy,
can you get it
through the dash?
Not in two minutes.
But there's another way to it.
And we are gonna
need this stuff.
No more than
six feet of rope.
I got it. Be careful.
If you're off
by more than 2 .9 inches,
she'll get
sucked under the wheel.
Appreciate the info.
We got less than two miles,
then we're going over the cliff.
Give me some slack.
♪ ♪
When we regain control,
Paige, you steer us to
the side of
the road.
Okay.
Be right back.
Or not.
A minute, 32 until impact.
What took you so long?
Oh!
Uh, please tell me you did not
just drop the screwdriver.
Okay, I won't.
Try and think of something.
I got it, I got it.
Got it. Think I can reach
the hard drive from there.
Time to make
a little room for me.
I'll see you up top. Or not.
30 seconds.
All right.
Hi.
15 seconds.
Eight seconds!
Oh, he shut down the computer!
Cut the wheel.
Oh.
Walter.
Oh, God, no,
no.
What is it?
That's the worst roadkill
I've ever seen.
Okay, we can celebrate our
near-death experience later.
'Cause Hector...
...is still on our tail and
it won't be much longer until
he catches up with us again.
We kind of stand out
in the middle of nowhere
farming country.
That might not such a bad thing.
What the hell does that mean?
I got an idea.
This is federal agent
Cabe Gallo, badge number 2835.
Get me the local
sheriff's office.
Vamano, Jorge, vamano, vamano.
Come on,
come on, faster,
we got to catch 'em!
There they are.
Gun it.
Come on, around the side,
let's go, let's go, let's go!
Get around 'em!
I can't get past 'em.
I can't see ahead of 'em.
Hit the brakes!
Hands up. Don't move.
You pull
that trigger
and it'll be the last
thing you ever do.
Hey. Thanks for hacking the RV.
Gave us the idea to operate it
remotely ourselves.
Except it worked out
for us. Enjoy prison.
Prosecutors
are gonna be pissed.
Well, they won't
be too happy with me.
But at the end of day,
with the data you gave us,
they'll be able to make a RICO
case and put Hector and his boys
away for life.
That's all they care about,
so they'll let it go.
Well,
guess this is good-bye.
Before you go, let me
hear it one more time,
for my own piece of mind.
After Sheriff Barnes
takes me to the bus station,
I buy a ticket to Vancouver.
Once I get there
I go straight
to the U.S. consulate,
request a package
from Cabe Gallo,
and they'll hand it over to me,
no questions asked.
That's right. Inside
you'll find 20 grand
and a brand-new Canadian
identity for you.
Best of luck, kid.
Why are you all
doing this for me?
We promised to protect you.
And you're one of us.
A new country,
fake I.D.s...
Not without
its risks.
She's going to have a child.
When it comes to someone you
love, you have to take risks.
Do you hear that, pal?
You got to take risks
when you love someone.
Authorities have
finally brought down
the notorious leader
of the DL, Hector Menjivar.
The break in the case
was the stunning discovery
of the DL's electronic
financial ledger, recovered
from Menjivar's laptop.
Members of his crew
are already cutting deals
implicating not only Menjivar
but a member of the LAPD
who was allegedly
acting as a mole
for the criminal organization.
You were right
about the mole, Toby.
Good night, guys.
That was distant.
That's 'cause she cares.
If she didn't care,
she wouldn't be upset.
What are you doing?
Me? Nothing.
I'm not doing anything.
Okay. So, I found another
Boysenberry Blast
in the back of the fridge
and it is past due as well.
Are you kidding me?
You need to take a risk, son.
You see what I did with
Happy? I opened up.
I wore my heart
on my sleeve.
Toby. You were severely burned.
Yes, but I'm living. And
I'm gonna get her back.
Give me this.
Toby.
Mmm, mmm, mmm, oh, my God.
Oh, mmm. Delicioso.
Mmm. It's fine,
you big baby.
And because you
didn't take a risk,
someone else got your yogurt.
If you don't take a risk, my
man, Drew's gonna take Paige.
Paige isn't yogurt.
No, she's a risk. One you
need to take. So you need
to get in your car, drive to
her house, knock on her door
and tell her how you feel.
Thank you!
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net