My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
Did you hear that?
Nothing to hear,
Octavio.
Transport isn't due for an hour.
Settle down.
You haven't seen what they do
to people like me.
Two years we've been working
to take down the cartel.
We've seen plenty.
I swear I hear something.
There's no place more secure
than this middle-of-nowhere
desert dump, Octavio.
Guaranteed by
the U.S. government.
We are alone.
Ralph?
It's 2:00 in
the morning.
And you're supposed to ask
to use my laptop, buddy.
My game got weird.
I unlocked a hidden level.
It took me someplace.
But there was no one there.
What game is this?
A new one.
Online.
You know we don't play games
I don't approve of first.
Right? Sleep.
Now.
You're late.
You don't speed when you're
hauling this kind of load.
Got to ask, is this
thing radioactive?
Shouldn't be.
♪ ♪
Hey, go grab that shadow
box for your show-and-tell.
I'll make you a quick
breakfast. Five minutes.
What's Walter working on?
I don't know.
What's that?
It's a booster
decoupler.
For what?
Wow!
“Wow” what?
What's he up to?
No idea.
So...
what are we doing?
Ah-ah! Reactor core.
Please do not
touch that.
Am I looking at
a dismantled CL-450?
It's a CL-460.
Polish this for me?
Oh, she can polish
the reactor core,
I'm Lord Numbnuts.
You're no good
with your hands.
You're a spiller.
Am I?
Toby!
Yeah, numbnuts,
yeah, mm-hmm.
Whoa.
Why don't you go do
a psych eval on the coffee pot?
Where is the Olds?
I was gonna use that
as a make-out hut.
With who?
A lucky lady.
Whoa, Walter!
What is this?
You're building a spaceship?
Hold on, hold on.
I'm studying
jet propulsion.
For the Karman Line Prize.
It was announced
last week.
An anonymous billionaire
is awarding $15 million
for significant aerospace
advancement.
Just imagine what I could do
for Megan's MS for $15 million.
Hey, Walt, can I get a sec?
There's a lot of ways
to make money.
That much at once?
It's a short list.
And I don't have
an oil well.
Whoa, a rocket.
When we're done
with the reactor core,
can we repair the control drum?
We probably need to get the
rust off the turbo pumps.
Maybe a vinegar bath.
I should skip school
until this is done.
Nope. We're leaving.
Now. In the car.
You sure this is about Megan?
'Cause Ralph is
certainly hooked.
You're reaching for something.
What?
Just pretty cool project,
building a rocket ship.
What little boy
doesn't dream of that?
Your dad's back
from Portland.
He's gonna pick you
up after school
and take you
for a milkshake.
I'd rather work
on the rocket.
Well, he's looking
forward to it.
He said he
got you a hat.
But I'd rather work
on the rocket.
The plans are set.
No more tug-of-war.
Come on.
Ralph, come here.
Paige Dineen.
Agent Wilson Eckherd,
Department of Justice.
This is Ralph?
What do you want?
You need to come with us,
both of you.
It concerns
national security.
What did I do?
It's not you, ma'am,
it's your son.
Let's go, come on.
Uh, okay.
Hold on.
Mom, am I
going to jail?
Of course not.
I am sure it's a mix-up.
Miss Dineen.
I'm not leaving my son alone.
My office is right
on the other side of that glass.
And you don't really
have a choice.
I'll be right in there.
Okay.
What the hell is going on?
Oh, my God.
Agents Daniel Cullens and Kate
Stellan were killed last night
in a CIA safe house
in Culiacan, Mexico.
They were guarding
a turncoat captain
in the Jotas
drug cartel.
What does this
have to do with Ralph?
The location and layout of
the safe house were leaked
as a secret level of
a game posted online.
Again, how does this
concern Ralph?
Thousands of people
played this game,
but only two parties found
the secret level
and decrypted
the safe house information--
the drug cartel who murdered
our agents and Ralph.
So it's something
he stumbled on.
Ralph was in a map ten
encryptions deep into this game,
something that would take a good
hacker months to accomplish.
He couldn't have
just stumbled on it.
The issue is
the safe house information
was classified CIA Intel.
Our concern is that Ralph may
have helped design the game
that delivered it
to the cartel.
How on earth would he have
access to CIA intelligence?
You work for a
government contractor.
Your team has specialized
expert hackers.
None of them would
allow him to do this.
Scorpion does nothing
but help people.
Miss Dineen, we don't
grab children randomly
off the street.
Either he knew where the secret
map was and how to access it,
or had something to do with
the design of this game.
Which disseminated
CIA intelligence, okay.
This is a very,
very serious situation.
I need to speak
with Ralph.
You can be watching
from right next door.
I need to speak
with Walter O'Brien
and Agent Cabe Gallo
from Homeland.
This is your mom's
laptop, Ralph.
That game you were
playing, Overt Target,
where did you find it?
Playing around.
You know what
a dark Web site is?
They're inaccessible
to normal search engines.
You don't just play around
and find them.
And Overt Target
was in the dark Web.
I know you're
a-a smart boy.
Genius.
So you need to know that
when my forensic team goes
through your mom's computer,
they're gonna
find everything--
every game you played,
how you got there,
who you chatted with.
How did you find the secret
level, the safe house level?
I just found it.
No. No, that's
impossible.
Did you have anything to do
with the design of this game?
No.
Do you know who
created the game?
How did you find the dark site
where it was posted?
And do not tell me
that you just found it.
Walter showed it to me.
Walter?
Walter O'Brien?
And he taught me decryption.
I didn't know it was bad.
This is over now.
Agent Gallo,
Homeland Security.
What did you teach him?
So these dark sites,
it's where the most interesting
coding is; it-it's cutting edge.
Walter.
I thought it would be
interesting for Ralph to see
where the smartest people
on the Web are designing.
And doing what else?
Did you think of that?
I was just showing him
a beta game site.
People post for feedback
to drum up buzz
before selling to big companies.
You get to see the game
years before anyone else does.
Stop. Now.
Got here as
quick as I could.
Hey, buddy.
Scary day, huh?
Somebody want to fill me in?
It's nothing, he did nothing.
But he got hauled
off the street
in front of his school, and
we're at the Justice Department.
Can you sit with Ralph?
Yeah.
Hey.
You want to tell me
what happened?
I just want to
talk to Walter.
Okay.
Eckherd's not buying him just
stumbling into the secret level.
That is the likely scenario.
He just can't comprehend
the depth of Ralph's
intelligence; maybe no one can.
They should be talking
to Walter. Why aren't they?
I can explain everything.
Not now.
I've lawyered up
for the whole team.
In the meantime, Ralph's being
released back to you.
Thank God.
But he's my responsibility, so
you need to stay close to me
in case Eckherd wants
him to come back in.
Cabe, let me talk to them
and clear this up.
They're being
extremely aggressive.
The safe house Intel in the
game was stolen in a hack
of the CIA mainframe
three weeks ago.
Details from six other
unknown operations
and safe houses
were taken.
Ralph had nothing to do
with hacking the CIA.
I know.
But they don't.
Okay, so we need to find out
who hacked the CIA.
That's who likely put
the information in the game.
Why are we standing here?
Hey.
Fill me in.
There's no time.
He's my son. Make time.
You know, with your history,
I would be cautious saying that.
This is not
about either of you.
This is a mess you got
Ralph into, and you need
to get him out. Do
you understand that?
I will make this right.
Stop talking
and just do it.
♪ Scorpion 1x13 ♪
Kill Screen
Original Air Date on January 5, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Where are we?
Walter, are you okay?
Where's Ralph?
Coming with
Cabe, Paige and Drew.
What's our progress
tracking the developer
of the Overt Target game?
We're into it,
but on the deep Web,
multiple shifting identities
are the norm.
Whoever designed this game
is using an anonymous proxy,
which means any traceback
will be TOR'd
and encrypted
to the hilt.
How is narrating our process
helping our speed?
Walter?
The CIA and the
Justice Department,
they're certainly working
to find this game designer
and coming up blank,
meaning this may take a minute.
They're not us.
And anything that Ralph
was doing on Paige's laptop
will be backed up
to our cloud server.
We know.
We're already
tracking his steps.
I only showed him
the deep Web because
it's where he could find people
like himself, people like us.
I'm certain your
intentions were good.
He was engaged,
he was asking questions.
It was like the first time
that I used the Internet.
We were just having fun.
You're reading my body language
and analyzing me.
I was absolutely
doing that.
I'm determining
whether you know
that mentoring a young person
is about more than just fun.
Of course I know that.
Hey, Ralph,
how's it going, pal?
Heard you
held up like a champ.
Better than my first arrest.
That was inappropriate.
Use the loft.
Back to work.
Walter.
I may have found
the game designer
buried beneath seven layers
of encryption
on the Overt Target
message board.
Took me, like,
15 minutes to crack.
An eternity.
There's something
you need to see.
Get a little rest.
I'll be downstairs.
If you need me,
tell Drew.
Look, um...
I can handle what Walter said
earlier, and I accept it,
but this situation, his
exposure to the team...
You don't see
the amazing things they do.
They're brilliant.
They're adults,
in an adult world.
You don't know them like I do.
They would never hurt Ralph.
And yet, here we are.
Look, I don't have
any right to push you.
But his Internet usage...
Oh, he's never playing
that game again.
All his Internet
will be monitored.
Good. So we're on
the same page.
I appreciate you being paternal.
Walter is Ralph's friend
and a huge asset,
but this was not
his finest moment.
We're trying to give
Ralph some time to rest.
It's important.
Hey, Ralph.
Hey, buddy.
In the Overt Target chat room,
did you ever communicate
with someone called
“Minidanger”?
Son, just tell us what
you talked about, that's all.
I just said the level one entry
into the abandoned warehouse
was too easy to find.
There should be
a hidden entrance.
And he responded to you?
He said, “Okay”"
And then what happened?
He changed the game.
I assume it's bad he was
talking to the game designer?
Ralph made a suggestion
that helped modify the game.
Do you know how that's
gonna look to Eckherd
when he finds out?
Ralph did nothing wrong.
He was asked if he helped
design the game, Ralph said no.
But we have proof
that he did help.
Unknowingly.
American agents were killed
as a result of this game.
And the CIA has been
searching like hell
for the culprits.
If need be, they may just
make an example out of Ralph.
They'll cut his computer use,
put him on a no-fly list
for the rest of his life.
He may never get a job
beyond flipping burgers.
Basically,
everything that would've
happened to Walt
if Cabe hadn't shown up.
So now we need to locate
the game designer,
Minidanger.
He's the only one
that can confirm
that Ralph's game suggestions
were innocent.
Guys, I'm actually communicating
with Minidanger right now
in another chat room.
He just responded to you?
I called him
a “no talent,
dimwit, fart
of a game designer.”
I said his work reminded me
of something
a dog might deliver
after eating old cheese.
What are you talking about?
It's egomania.
It runs rampant with artists,
writers and game designers.
Especially the latter,
who grew up maligned by jocks
and ignored by cheerleaders.
- Like us?
- Yeah, so now these guys
have this muscle to flex.
And these chat rooms?
Just a constant joystick
measuring contest.
Best way to get a response
is with insults.
Admittedly, it's a shot
in the dark, but he responded.
From a mobile device?
Which can be traced.
Keep insulting him.
Keep him responding.
Happy, you'll trace
from the SUV.
Okay, guys, let's go!
Of course he's here.
Three times
I've called Minidanger
an undescended cat gonad,
still no response.
The last communication came
from inside the building.
Oh, and, Cabe, stay here.
Why the hell
would I do that?
I think you might stand out
as a federal agent.
Exactamundo.
What are you doing?
Excellent question.
These
tournaments can be
a crucible for hackers,
dark site trolls.
Never bring your credit
cards to a place like this.
Less savory types
will carry
pocket scanners
that'll get your numbers
from the magnetic strips.
My God.
All right, we're on comms.
I've seen pictures
of these conventions.
They don't do them justice.
World's largest
gathering of virgins.
I don't know.
The after-hours parties at these
things can get pretty filthy.
So I've read.
The last signal leads
to the room down there.
Hi. Hi, there.
Uh, we need access to this room.
That's the VIP tournament area.
Access is by game play only.
30 Dino kills
in 30 seconds.
30 kills in 30 seconds on a game
no one's played in ten years?
That's the rule, Grandpa.
I didn't make it.
“Grandpa”? I'm 32.
Hey, guys,
the last ping from Minidanger
came from in that room.
If I can get 30 kills
in ten seconds,
can all my friends get in?
Not possible.
Thirty-three.
I've never seen anything
like that before.
Can we go in now?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Wait, I have seen something
like that before.
Hey, wait.
Is he El Guapo?
“El Guapo”?
What's our progress?
Nothing more
from Minidanger.
Makes it a bit of a needle
in a haystack.
Unless he's playing.
Maybe the guy on the left.
Sensitive face.
I can see him
being easy to offend.
Catch this guy,
and Ralph's off the hook.
So figure it out.
Mind reader,
get in the game.
You know, I could just
yell out, “Hey, Minidanger,
your government would like
to speak with you.”
But that might
get him running, Cabe.
The kid on stage
just got very alert to you.
Talking with your finger in
your ear might have tipped him.
And I think he made me, too.
Yeah!
He's running.
Keep your eye on him.
Great, we lost him.
I got this. I can fix it.
Attention, fans of this game.
We trust you're enjoying
your promotional hooded capes.
You mean Vontanian
cloakings.
That's exactly right.
Now, sewn into the lining
of one, and only one,
cloaking is a ticket
that grants you a small role
in the latest version
of the game.
Yes, that's right!
You could literally be
in the game!
He'll be the only one
still wearing a cape.
I see him, I got him.
There!
Cabe, he's on the move.
He's wearing a red cloak.
Cover the exit
off the main hall,
we'll check the southeast doors.
Out of my way.
Excuse me.
Thanks.
I'm telling you,
swearing to you,
whatever you think I did,
you have the wrong guy.
Did you design the game Overt
Target and post it online?
Then we have the right guy.
All right, this is good.
He admits to
designing the game.
Yeah, but why so easily?
Wait, stop.
What secret level?
There's no secret level
in my game.
The Justice Department calls
it “the safe house level”"
It's awfully authentic.
What do you know about the hack
of the Langley mainframe
at CIA headquarters
three weeks ago?
Oh, my God.
God ain't here with you, kid.
It's just me.
Now answers.
You can have my laptop,
all my hard drives,
all my data, everything.
If you're so squeaky clean, then
why'd you run at the convention?
All right, all right,
I may have made a few bucks
hacking the DMV to take points
off a few people's licenses.
Well done.
He's telling the truth.
Then how the hell did...
Walter. Walter.
Hey, buddy!
Then how the hell
did the safe house level
get on your game?
Walter, what are you doing?
A ten-year-old
who you involved in this
hangs in the balance right now.
I don't know any kid.
ScorpJr1.
You communicated with him.
ScropJr1 is ten?
Wow, he's a smart kid.
But it was just about game play.
No CIA secrets.
I didn't have anything
to do with that.
Neither did my partner.
Partner?
Calvin Thorne.
Or maybe you're just
pulling a name out of a hat.
He's not.
Calvin would take
the hard drives, do revisions.
He'd never do anything
like this.
When did you hook up
with this Calvin?
He noticed an early version
of my game online,
then offered to come on board
as a collaborator.
Coding, research.
These spy games
can't write themselves.
I am sensing
integrity markers
in his voice,
his pitch consistency,
lack of shifty eye movement.
He's telling the truth;
there's a Calvin.
Maybe this Calvin
did the CIA hack.
And he commandeered Nate's game
to deliver the intelligence?
Meaning the guy
that stole the CIA Intel,
maybe Calvin, is out there
peddling more information.
Eckherd claims that six other
operations were compromised.
We're talking a hundred
more lives are at risk.
Explain how this worked.
If I stole CIA intelligence,
then I'd need buyers
and a way to deliver the Intel
that wouldn't trace back to me.
He used the black sites
to find the buyers,
then find a patsy-- Nate--
and piggyback the information
into his online project,
in this case, a game.
You tell the buyer
when the game goes live.
You give him the password,
and then he finds
the stolen CIA Intel
hidden in the game.
It's just sitting there,
waiting for
the right person to access it.
Except in this case,
the wrong person
found the hidden level-- Ralph.
It made him look guilty
because it was hidden so well.
And we're certain that Nate's
told us everything
that he knows?
When it comes to
Russian rockets, I'm all thumbs.
This is sort of my thing.
Wanting Nate to be the bad guy
doesn't make him the bad guy.
Okay, then we should be
talking to Calvin,
'cause he's the one who actually
might have hacked the CIA,
who actually might be
the bad guy,
or we can stand around all day.
Maybe if we take him for
a walk around the block,
he'll get his
appetite back.
No, we need to stay close.
Okay, I'm not trying
to make things worse,
but a few weeks ago, the garage
was torn apart by killers.
It's not exactly a Gymboree.
I've been thinking
the same thing, too, but...
I know you feel Walter
is good for him...
Drew, the whole team
is good for him.
I'm no genius, but I was a kid,
and so were you.
Ralph is special, but that
doesn't mean these guys
should be treating him
like an adult.
Maybe they didn't have
normal childhoods, Paige,
but I'm worried that they may be
taking one from Ralph.
Any luck at Calvin's apartment?
He wasn't home.
Wait, why do you have a safe?
There were no
computers in sight,
so whatever tech he's got,
guaranteed he keeps it in there.
You stole that?
Let's go with “seized.”
With CIA operations in jeopardy,
not to mention Ralph, we're not
looking for permissions.
Okay, well, if he wasn't there,
how'd you guys get in?
I picked the lock.
I've been watching Happy.
Yeah, we've noticed.
Speaking of which, where is she?
Keeping an eye on Nate.
No, we got to crack that safe.
Go get her.
Hello, didn't I just get
us into that apartment?
You know, she's not the only one
on our team with skills.
All right, you're insulted
because earlier she called you
a spiller.
We can't waste time
just so you can prove her wrong.
I wasn't insulted.
I just have
psychological insight.
I got it.
It's Calvin--
he's cold, precise,
detail-oriented.
I looked around
his place.
With him, it's the
little things.
Pile of mail told us
that his middle initial is “W.”
That is a powerful letter,
and 23rd in the alphabet.
Get Happy.
Cabe, Walter,
Grimace.
How long?
Uh, 30 seconds, tops.
There's no computer
in there?
No.
Just a two-terabyte hard drive.
That's our main backup storage.
There are multiple index levels
to this thing.
Deep encryption
in the lower depth.
Oh, but look
at what I just found.
CIA files.
Okay, so we know that
six of them were stolen.
Now we know
who stole them.
I-I don't get it.
What is this?
He played you.
Six files means
six more safe houses.
CIA operations
and multiple identities
that he can sell and expose,
resulting in how many
more dead agents.
These files
are so heavily encrypted
that the only thing we can tell
is that they are CIA files,
but to know which six locations
are at risk would take hours.
We don't have
that kind of time.
Odds are Calvin's
already sold the Intel
for delivery in the game,
and buyers are waiting.
Statistically,
I'd say that's 91% likely.
Nate, where's Calvin?
First place I'd try is the Brick
and Porter Café on Angel Street.
That's mostly where
we worked on the game.
We're headed there now.
What about me?
You could use a good lawyer.
Wait.
You'll have an easier time
putting him away
with a confession, right?
I can get him to talk.
Please, you got
to let me help.
Can you wire him up?
I can do it on the way.
All right, I'll have Eckherd
meet us at the spot.
Happy, you drive
like a maniac.
Get us there fast.
Sweet.
You stay here.
You keep digging
into Calvin's hard drive.
On it.
Calvin's settling into
his second cup of coffee.
The guy's in the zone.
Agent Eckherd's
got his team rolling.
They'll be here
in three minutes.
We're almost done.
We'll be recording everything
you and Calvin say.
I'm sorry I got
that boy involved.
You're not the one
who got him involved.
I'm surprised
he was so young.
Dark site board's no place
for a kid.
Please keep your remaining
thoughts to yourself.
Good to go.
Start by telling Calvin
you found the hidden level.
Ask him what he put in the game.
Hey.
Are you sure about this?
Yes. I want to make this right.
Just maintain
eye contact
and keep a calm tone
of voice, piece of cake.
Department of Justice
is coming to back us up.
Just stay cool.
Okay.
Hey, man.
Hey, Nate.
What brings you?
I was...
just in the area.
You're sweating like a pig.
It's hot out.
That tone of voice
is anything but calm.
- Yeah, Sylvester?
- Walter,
I found some bad stuff on
the hard drive, personal data.
He erased it a while ago,
but I was able to dig it up.
Turns out, Calvin's name
is not Calvin.
It's Donald Chen,
and he's got a record.
Weapons possession,
black hat hacking, assault.
Man, Nate had no idea who
he was getting into bed with.
Nice work, Sylvester.
So what you working on now?
Finishing up six new levels
for the game.
Launching them in an hour.
That's got to be the other
six stolen CIA files.
He's gonna blow the operations
in one hour.
As soon as he gets a confession
from Calvin,
we go in and it's over.
So-so, look, I, um...
I got to ask you something.
It's pretty weird.
I-I found a hidden level
in our game.
Tell you what...
I need a smoke.
I don't like the sound of that,
but we don't have
a confession yet.
We got to get Nate out of there.
Let's talk out back?
They're on the move.
What's out back?
According to satellite maps,
that's an alley.
Calvin,
what are you doing?
We lost contact.
Pull around back now.
Agent Eckherd will meet us.
There he is!
He's on the ground.
I think I see blood.
Nate, what happened?
He stabbed me and ran.
Buddy, hey, hey, buddy. Hey.
Nate, you're gonna be okay.
Hey, look at me, look at me.
You're gonna be fine.
Did your team botch this
all to hell, Gallo?
Not now!
Suspect's in the wind.
Fan out, find him!
Nate, Nate, Nate?
Come on, keep
your eyes open.
He's fading fast.
The Whitehull Hospital
is four minutes away.
Okay, we're on it.
20 cc's of diesel therapy, stat.
Toby, keep him breathing!
This neighborhood's nothing
but abandoned buildings
and warehouses.
Yeah, plenty of
places to hide.
Oh, this looks familiar.
So you got the bridge,
you got dozens of factories,
you got this café.
We're in the game.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Nate and Calvin designed
the first level
based on what they knew best,
what they were looking at
every day and night
while they were coding
in that café.
So if Calvin's gonna hide,
this is the perfect spot.
No one knows this area
better than he does.
Except Ralph.
He knows the game,
which means he knows this area
like the back of his hand.
If we're gonna find Calvin
before he leaks that CIA Intel,
Ralph has to play
that game again
and lead us to him.
Are you kidding?
This morning,
that game landed him
in a room with federal agents.
It's the only way
to find this guy in time.
We only got a half
dozen people searching,
and it's a
massive search.
But right now,
we need an advantage,
and that advantage is Ralph.
I thought he was never
playing that game again.
Mom, can I?
All right,
got to open this up a little,
see where the damage is.
His internal
epiploic artery is cut.
I'm gonna need more pressure.
Hey, Happy,
I got to cross a line here.
Do you have a tampon?
Excuse me?
It'll absorb the blood,
expand, increase the pressure
and stop the bleeding.
Uh, toolbox, bottom compartment.
Yeah? Ah!
Uh... ah...
It's working!
Hold on!
I don't like this.
Neither do I, but
they need his help.
I'm in.
Okay, Walter, Ralph's in the game.
Copy.
The best way for us to help you
is to pinpoint
your exact location,
go to that same spot
in the game, and guide you.
And, Walter, you need to hurry,
because there's
a countdown clock
with six new levels coming
in 19 minutes and 50 seconds.
We need to catch Calvin
before they're released.
All right, well,
we're on the east side
of Angel Street
outside a factory.
What color is it?
Uh, it's gray and white.
That one has a hidden entrance.
Look for an alley
straight ahead.
The A/C grate
on the north side
by the telephone poles,
enter there.
It accesses a lower level
you can't get to
from the main floor.
I'm playing that level now.
Calvin's got to be
hiding in there.
Look alive.
All right, we're heading in.
Did you find hallway PW-99?
Yeah, it's where you
said it would be.
This floor
has the most hiding places.
They should go southeast.
Okay, guys, you heard him.
Hey!
Cabe, Cabe, you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Let's go catch
that son of a bitch.
Okay.
Two minutes to the E.R.!
Bleeding's under control.
Maybe too much.
Ah, damn, the bleeding slowed
down 'cause his heart stopped.
Where's the quick jump?
Happy!
The jumper cables, now!
Uh, it's, uh...
it's under the console.
Okay, here we go.
So, Doc, clamp the black one
to the metal part of the seat,
and then take the
red one and zap him.
Uh... clear?
All right, he's back.
Holy crap, Dr. Frankenstein!
All right, he headed south.
I need a shortcut.
According to Ralph,
look for a door on your left
marked 6-5-9.
That's how Calvin would escape.
Got it. Got it!
Okay, head through
the opening in the fence,
and hang a right.
You should
catch up to him there.
Is this my only way out?
It's the fastest.
Stab wound, upper abdomen,
and there's a severed
epiploic artery.
He's gonna need
a couple units in the O.R.
Oh... I'm rocking so much
adrenaline right now,
my blood is basically Red Bull.
Impressive.
Guys, guys...
I'm looking at a...
a rather large drop.
It's unknown depth.
It's, uh...
Yeah, no...
it's too far to jump.
You can jump down
and walk across.
Are you sure?
Yes.
It's only a seven-foot drop.
I can tell by how
the graphics are composited.
I can't see the bottom.
It could be seven feet or 70.
Now, are you sure, Ralph?
Scoop.
What?
It's about a scoop
of ice cream after school.
He-He'd make me “scoop swear”
that we'd actually go.
It's the strongest promise
he can make.
Okay.
I trust you, Ralph.
Walter?
Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks to Ralph.
I got a visual. He's fast.
You can stop him.
There should be a lever
in front of you.
It opens the storage bay
in front of the exit.
I see the lever.
Pull it! Pull it now!
Did it work?
Walter?
Yeah, it worked.
You're really going
at that thing, huh?
It calms me.
After today... calm is good.
Hey, E.R. doc called.
Looks like Nate's gonna make it.
You know, no one on
this team could've
pulled off what
you did today.
Well done.
You know,
something occurred to me.
For your rocket--
with trauma wounds,
the body protects the head
and the heart and the gut
by focusing blood flow
in those areas,
just like Nate's body
did today.
So, with your rocket,
what if you adjusted
fuel flow the same way?
Cover the injector head
with a metal plate
that's perforated with holes,
like stab wounds.
Covering more or fewer
of the holes
will allow for
a variable fuel flow and...
increase throttleability.
That's a good idea.
I got a million of them.
Hey, Walt...
about the kid?
Yeah, we were having fun.
Um... too much fun.
Look, he needs you,
you're a huge part of his life,
but you can't just
be his friend.
You got to be
the grown-up, too.
Yeah.
We have a celebrity
in our midst.
Oh, stop,
you're making me blush.
Not you, idiot.
An online video?
What...?
“El Guapo sets another record.”
What is that?
What?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Wait a minute.
Is that
a young Sylvester?
Yup.
Earlier, that gamer girl
asked me if Sly was El Guapo.
Now we know why.
Please... no.
Those are some
fascinating moves.
Hard to look at,
but impossible to turn away.
El Guapo!
Life will never be the same.
I can't believe
this was online for seven years
and you never said anything
about it.
The fashion is unflattering,
and the dance is derivative.
You're their hero.
Well, I guess we all have
our hidden talents.
That's beautifully put,
El Guapo.
For what it's worth,
I know it's my fault
that you're here
in the first place,
so I'm gonna make it right.
I'm gonna work my ass off
for that gig in Portland,
give you and Ralph a
shot at something else.
This is not about you and me
getting back together.
This is about us being a family,
all in the same place, all safe.
What if we don't want to leave?
Well, before you have a choice,
how can you know?
Uh, we're heading out.
Just packing up Ralph's things.
Take your time.
I apologize for everything
I did to contribute
to what Ralph
went through today.
But...
There it is.
But I do want to note,
those stolen CIA files
contained the identities
of 43 undercover operatives.
They, in turn,
protected 356 source assets
relating to drug trafficking,
gangs,
loose nuclear material.
By preventing the release
of those files,
Ralph saved
innumerable lives today.
I'm glad he could help.
I'm just not sure
it's a good idea
for him to grow up this fast.
Ralph sees us
using our heads for good.
He's learning how to be
a grown-up genius someday.
We're not trying
to make him a grown-up now.
I'll meet you downstairs.
I'm aware I screwed up.
I just wish
I could get a guarantee from you
that this won't happen again.
I'm not sure I can give you one.
I know you can't.
So what do I gamble on, Walter?
I couldn't advise you;
gambling is Toby's department.
Paige, I care about
this team and our work...
but what I care about most...
...is giving Ralph a safe place
to reach his potential.
He has a lot of it.
I know that, too.
Oh. Do you remember
when you and Ralph turned up,
and I gave him that riddle?
What is a group
of jellyfish called?
Yeah. A smack?
If you want to give me one now,
I would understand.
That's funny, Walter.
I do try.
I know you do.
Good night.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net