WALTER:
My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
MAN:
Looks like we're about 15 miles
outside of Pendleton.
Not a moment too soon.
I got to waz again.
Hey, what's this guy doing?
Whoa, whoa. Whoa!
What the hell?!
Out of the truck now!
Get out!
Please, don't shoot! Please!
Take the rockets.
Leave the bodies.
Got it.
TOBY:
Well, this is highly illegal.
I'm simply expediting things
through technological
intervention.
You're hacking into a site
that charges for reservations
to save the 20 bucks.
Nope.
They were fully booked.
Dinner for two at Escala?
One of the ten hottest
spots in town.
Yes, Walter, I would be
happy to dine with you.
Oh, nice try.
It's a business dinner.
Need to go over some office
data entry protocol with Paige.
You are taking Paige
to a top L.A. eatery
on Valentine's Day?
Just one week after Drew
signed a month-long contract
to pitch in Portland.
How convenient.
Is Valentine's this weekend?
I had no idea.
Should I get the extinguisher?
'Cause your pants
are on fire, liar, liar.
You don't think Paige
notices the timing?
It is a business meeting.
Valentine's is a scam created
by the greeting card industry.
The only reason why
I picked that place is
because Paige mentioned it.
The cherry on top
of the denial sundae.
You're being attentive
to her wants.
PAIGE:
Good morning, guys.
Paige.
Ms. Dineen.
I brought donuts.
Oh, thank you.
It's a date!
Grow up.
For dessert, you should order
Phoenix dactylifera.
Why? Because that's
the botanical name for dates?
Yup.
This conversation's over.
What you got there, pal?
Nada.
CABE:
Hope you're caffeinated!
'Cause it's time
to punch the clock.
Last night a weapons
manufacturer was ambushed.
A shipment of high-tech,
lightweight, shoulder-launch
rockets were stolen.
Oh, God!
Homeland has received Intel
that an arms dealer,
who we only know as Christoph,
is behind it.
He's never been
photographed or I.D.'d.
But he's known to sell across
the globe to Rwanda and Somalia
Any weapon to suit
your genocide needs, huh?
This is a bad, bad man.
Yes, and he's stolen
a very bad piece
of experimental hardware.
These rockets have
a range nine times
the standard with
laser guidance
technology that makes
them impossible
to shake once they
lock on target.
All in the size of
a Louisville Slugger.
So, if the rockets
were stolen last night,
they're already on the move.
Correct, but we've
traced them to the Port
of Long Beach through
satellite footage.
So, you want us to identify
the shipping container?
There is no shipping container.
Apparently Christoph is using
a luxury cruise line
as transport.
He's one of 100 passengers.
The one percent
of the one percent.
Ride in style,
avoid airport security.
I want to be rich just once.
Stop gambling.
Stop judging.
PAIGE:
So, if you think you know
the boat he's using,
go take him down.
We're looking for a bigger fish.
Not that simple.
Homeland wants us to hack into
the guidance system
of each munition,
and plant GPS tracking software
so that we can find out
who Christoph sells them to.
So, there's no time to waste.
Now...
who's up for a little
James Bond action?
Sweet.
Cool.
Not me.
Let's do it.
Now, I just have to save it
with the virus I embedded and...
done! How long?
14 minutes and 32 seconds.
I just downloaded
the blueprints.
I'd say he'd put them near
the engine room or cargo hold.
It's secluded.
CABE: You got 20 rockets to
disarm in 14 minutes a pop.
We're never gonna get
five hours alone.
We won't need it.
These rockets are
interfaced like
a laptop, phone and tablet.
I program one, they all link up
disabled and trackable.
How do we get aboard?
We go as passengers.
It's fully booked.
But we can create a vacancy.
Just got to find the right guy.
Haven't rich people ever heard
of Legionnaire's disease?
Ahoy, mateys!
It's Chaz Bonesteel.
It must be a family name?
From what I see here,
it's the only name that matters.
At 21, he invested
his life savings
in land thought
to be valueless.
At now at 25,
he's worth nine figures
and at the epicenter
of the oil shale boom.
He's considered
an investment guru.
Oh, and intense
about his privacy.
Known for not having
a single photo online.
No one's even sure
what he looks like.
Okay, so what does
that have do with us?
Well, he booked
the Excelsior Suite
for himself, his wife, Alissa,
their personal valet
and trainer.
That's four people.
WALTER: Okay.
Cabe, Sylvester, Paige, myself.
We'll pose as them
to get access to the boat.
Okay, uh, here's a shocker.
I don't like boats.
Primarily because they're
on the water.
And I don't like water.
We'll need three minutes
to get up the plank,
five to get
to the bowels,
approximately five minutes
to locate the weapons
and 14 minutes
and 32 seconds
to disarm and reprogram them.
That's 27 minutes
and 32 seconds.
So, we'll be off the boat
by the time it departs.
Besides you're
the only one of us
that can pass for a 25-year-old.
Guess I'll be the trainer.
(laughs):
Right.
Oh, you're serious.
Okay.
You'll be the trainer.
I will be the valet.
Sylvester, you'll be Chaz.
And, Paige,
you'll be Alissa.
And the real Alissa and Chaz?
Uh, aren't they boarding
in a few hours?
I'll make a call.
They'll have a little
trouble at customs when
they get in from Canada.
Walter, gear up.
Happy, counterfeit some I.D.'s
and tickets.
Toby, put together a file
of everything you can find
on the Bonesteels.
And, Sly?
The shirt's not gonna cut it.
SYLVESTER:
In 2013,
the Triumph Carnival fire
left 4,000 passengers
floating in the Gulf of Mexico.
2012-- the Costa
Concordia tragedy.
Not to mention a little film
starring Leonardo DiCaprio
and a giant boat?
Okay.
We'll be in and
out in 20 minutes.
Hello!
Hi! Welcome to Pacific
West Cruises.
There are four of us.
Mr. And Mrs. Bonesteel!
Mm-hmm.
We are thrilled
to welcome you aboard.
Thrilled to be here.
The VIP cocktail reception
is on the Lido deck.
Wonderful, we'll be
in our room, so...
No. We will do
what we normally do, Chaz.
Where is the Lido deck?
The Lido deck is the top deck.
Wonderful.
Top deck above it all.
20 minutes.
The clock starts now.
Mm-hmm.
Tickets?
Ow!
(grunts)
Took us substantially longer
to board than we estimated.
Blame the inefficient
cruise line.
We still got
to locate the rockets,
disarm them and
get off the ship.
And we're way behind.
Yeah. No, I'm working on it.
My software can test whether
the rockets are reachable
across an IP network,
thus creating a traceable ping
for lack of a better word.
So, where the hell's the ping?
Give me a minute.
(thud nearby)
(shushes)
We've got company.
Everything looks good.
Pressure readouts are normal.
I'll run a systems check
just to be safe.
It'll just take a few minutes.
MAN:
Copy that.
You're calculating this into
your 20 minutes, right?
We're minutes
from the boat leaving.
Can't you, uh,
put him in a sleeper hold
or... something?
Someone will find him and alert
the boat and the bad guys.
Just sit tight.
Captain, we're
all clear down here.
Roger.
CABE: See?
Patience.
Securing the bulkhead.
Walter?
I don't like the sound of that.
(alarm blaring)
Whoa, whoa!
Hold on, hold...
Can you get us out of here?
Yeah, I can.
But by the time I do,
we'll be in the middle
of the Pacific.
(ship horn blows twice)
Paige!
That was the "get off
the boat" noise.
Where the hell are they?!
SYLVESTER:
Oh, this is not good!
I am on a boat!
In the middle of the ocean!
Have you seen the movie
Open Water?!
Those people were stranded
in shark-infested waters.
You're on a luxury cruise boat.
Paige, I can't swim.
Maybe you can't.
But Chaz Bonesteel can.
In fact, Chaz Bonesteel
is a champion swimmer.
And Chaz Bonesteel
can keep it together.
Come on, Walter,
I've seen you
diffuse bombs faster than this.
It's a simple door pane.
I'm trying to open
the bulkhead door
without alerting anyone
that we're down here.
Can you give me a minute?
Please?
(cell phone ringing)
Oh, geez!
Ralph, are you okay?
I think I'm sick.
Ms. Dineen, he has
the chills pretty bad.
Teeth were actually chattering.
PAIGE:
Okay, well, I'm a little...
unavailable right now.
Uh, I'll have to have
Toby and Happy pick you up.
All right, honey?
Thanks, Mom.
I love you.
Would Chaz be worried that
everything's going to hell?
Appreciate it, nurse.
No problem.
Feel better, Ralph.
It's a bummer
you're feeling sick.
You know, when you
get the chills,
it means your body's
fighting an infection.
(school bell ringing)
A knapsack full of ice packs
to make your teeth chatter?
I've seen you hack
a thermometer, Ralph.
This is amateur hour.
I had limited resources.
Where the hell
have you been?
We're out to sea.
What exactly is the plan here?
Well, once we locate
and reprogram
the rockets, we'll ride on
to the first stop in Cancun.
Homeland agents will meet us
and get us across the border.
My God, the kid's green.
WALTER:
Okay, let's all
get our comms in.
Link them up, come on.
I'm gonna call Happy, make
sure that she's connected.
This whole thing has not
gone according to plan,
so we need to make sure
that we stay
in constant communication.
CABE:
All right.
Listen, keep an eye
on the kid.
Get him to lie down or
something, and whatever you do,
don't leave this room
and don't talk to anyone.
I'm gonna call Happy,
find out why it was so difficult
to get a signal in the hull.
Keep you posted.
(knocking)
CAPTAIN: Mr. and Mrs. Bonesteel?
Paige, come answer it.
Yes?
Mrs. Bonesteel.
I'm Captain Steven Caine.
Welcome aboard.
I wanted to personally
invite you
and Mr. Bonesteel to join me
at my table for lunch.
Oh, the captain's table,
that sounds lovely.
Wonderful.
Many people are very excited
about dining with Mr. Bonesteel.
Good, now I have to have lunch.
Hm.
WALTER:
Okay, so we meet back
at the room after our
respective missions, okay?
And, uh, Sly, please, uh,
WOMAN: Walter?
try to lay off the Dramamine.
That's an ex.
Handle it fast.
Hey.
Are you working on the ship?
Um, yes.
I am, uh, currently,
uh, working.
Tech support on a cruise
is a nice step up.
Well, you know what they say.
Onward and upward.
Walter, we are going to lunch.
Meet my dad at the shuffleboard.
Okay.
Is that woman the waitress?
From that diner
you used to take me to?
Yes, she did, uh,
work there for a while.
So she's here with you?
Are-are you two dating?
No, we work together.
Oh, the waitress
is a tech expert, too.
Come on, Walter.
No, you don't understand.
The truth is
(whispering):
we work for the government.
The government?
You expect me to believe that?
MAN:
Janice!
Come here; there-s someone
I want you to meet.
My fiancé.
Enjoy the cruise, Walt.
Happy, the signal's
still jumping around.
The girders are
just steel alloy.
They shouldn't be interfering
with the signal.
Yeah, well, I'm down here,
and I'm telling you,
I can't get a proper signal.
Calm down. I'm trying to find
an answer.
Excuse me, I am perfectly calm.
Yeah, you sound perfectly calm.
Enough.
This thing's echoing in my ear
from you two acting
like children.
Get it together.
Echo?
Wait.
That's it, Walt.
There's got to be a hollow space
located in the hull somewhere
that's causing the signal
to bounce around like an echo
whenever the boat swells.
Yes, there should be
a crawlspace above you.
Eight, maybe ten feet up?
Oh, oh.
Oh, yeah, I see it.
Hold that.
Yeah, they're here.
Hand it to me.
Oh, Cabe, Happy was right.
They're here.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
Mr. Bonesteel,
I read the article
where you mentioned
seared frog legs were
a particular favorite of yours.
So I had some flown in.
Here you are.
PAIGE:
Oh.
Chaz just...
loves his amphibious meats.
(clears throat)
Thank you.
You almost done?
I'm only a few minutes in.
Besides, it's dark in here.
You got 197 IQ,
and you don't know how
to operate a flashlight?
Are you kidding me?
(gun clicks)
Who are you?
Just a little lost.
Lost, huh?
Down here in the cargo hold?
Turn around.
On your knees now.
Okay, okay.
Don't move.
Who you working for?
I said, who do you work for?
I'm not gonna ask you again.
(grunting)
Damn it.
Our cover's blown.
In a few minutes,
whoever he's working for
is gonna be looking for us.
Oh, we don't have enough time.
Forget about
installing the GPS.
Just deactivate
the damn things.
Grab them and go.
Chaz, when did you know
that you'd made it?
(clears throat)
Tell them the story...
Chaz.
Well...
My grandfather
once took me ice fishing.
And we dropped our lines
and we waited,
but I was impatient.
So I said to my grandfather,
"Grandfather,
my feet are frozen and I'd like
to go home, please."
(chuckles)
And he said, "Son, grandson,
"when your feet are frozen,
"that is when the fish
are the warmest."
MAN:
Excuse me, Captain.
If you'll all excuse me,
I have a call I have to take.
SERVER: Excuse me, sir,
your next course.
Oh.
Escargot.
Oh, that's a lot of snails.
Please, no.
There's some light over here.
Here, hold that.
Yeah.
Hurry up.
(engines whining)
This is your captain.
All passengers
report immediately
to the casino on the main deck.
No, that's not good.
Thank you.
Put the ship into idle.
That's no coincidence.
They can't find us,
so they're going
after the passengers.
Please, keep coming in.
Yes, that's it.
Just this way, folks.
That's right, right in here.
Do you think
Chaz would find this odd?
Not sure, but I certainly do.
CAPTAIN:
Plenty of room.
Please, please keep coming.
That's it.
Yes, ma'am. Yes, I know.
Make your way
to the back of the room. There
is plenty of space for everyone.
All is fine,
nothing to worry about.
I'm feeling very
strange about this.
PAIGE: They don't look
like ship security.
SYLVESTER:
Why are they blocking the doors?
(doors close)
All right, everyone, please,
do not panic.
Everything is going to be
absolutely fine.
(groans, passengers scream)
Thank you, Captain.
I'll take it from here.
(gun clicks)
(gasping)
Ladies and gentlemen,
if you want to live,
there's one thing
that you need to understand.
Oh, my God.
This is my ship now.
Hurry up.
HENCHMAN:
Electronic devices in the bag.
In the bag.
HENCHMAN 2:
We searched the ship.
This is everyone on board.
I looked for the rockets;
they're not where we left them.
Cell phone in the bag!
Cell phone in the bag now, lady!
(gunshots)
Do I have everyone's attention?
One of you knows
where my cargo is.
I intend to get it back.
This is a passenger manifest.
So,
if you cannot produce
an identification
that's on this list,
well then,
today is not your lucky day.
Roger that, sir.
We'll be prepared.
Navy's sending a military copter
to handle the hostage situation.
They're linking up our comms,
but if those goons find us,
they can't
have live rockets with
helicopters approaching.
I'm almost done.
Walter, where are you?
We got caught in the bowels
of the ship.
Why? What's going on?
We are in the casino.
Christoph is reading
the manifest,
and once he gets to Bonesteel,
we are in big trouble.
The laminate that Happy used
on both of our I.D.'s
is only a few hours old,
and if he shines a light on it,
it'll read as fake.
Time frame?
Well, okay, statistically,
B is the fifth most common start
to a surname,
and A is the twelfth.
How much time, Sylvester?
Okay, three minutes, tops.
New plan.
You have to finish disarming
the rockets first.
We don't have enough time.
The rockets will take
another four minutes.
Paige and Sylvester
will be dead in three.
What the hell do we do?
Grab me a beer.
I have an idea.
RALPH: I wanted to give Sloan
a valentine,
but Jason gave her one first.
Ralphie boy,
you got to be persistent.
There are some girls
who don't know a good thin
when it's right
in front of them,
no matter how many times
it has been offered.
You and Sloan are friends,
right, Ralph?
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
HAPPY:
Well, maybe
she doesn't want
to jeopardize your friendship.
Maybe
she's never had a best friend
like you before
and that probably
means a lot to her.
So don't take it personally.
You just have to be patient.
How patient?
Like, if you had
to put a time frame on it.
I really don't know what
we're talking about anymore.
(phone ringing)
Talk to me.
WALTER:
We have a situation here.
All the passengers
have been taken hostage,
including Paige and Sylvester.
So I need you to find a spot
in the hull
where I can access
the ship's intercom.
Okay, I'm in the ship's
broadcasting system.
What are you up to?
There's no intercom down here,
so I'm building one.
If we're gonna negotiate
with our captors,
we have to able
to talk to them first.
Grab that;
let's go.
HAPPY:
It should be on your left side.
Here it is, here it is.
(grunts)
Ah, thank you, Happy.
Once we get
a current,
the can will act
as a microphone.
I'll have it broadcast
over every speaker
on the ship.
Watch yourself.
SYLVESTER: Okay, Walter, you have
approximately 30 seconds
until they call Bonesteel.
They will kill
me and Paige.
You sure
about this?
There's no hiding
once it's done.
We have no choice.
Barclay, Phineas.
What are we going to do?
When he sees our IDs,
he'll know that they're bogus.
CHRISTOPH:
Bonesteel...
Alissa.
Alissa Bonesteel.
Just stay right here, okay?
It's okay, come here.
Ow!
CHRISTOPH:
I will put a bullet
in her ponytail
if Ms. Alissa Bonesteel
does not step forward.
I am!
I... I am...
Alissa Bonesteel.
(whimpers)
Trouble hearing?
No, I...
I'm just scared
because I left
my ID in my room.
(gasps)
I'm gonna take
a wild guess
that you know where my cargo is.
PAIGE:
I don't know.
I don't know--
No, please, please.
I have a son.
CHRISTOPH:
In three seconds.
your son will
have no mother.
And then...
(whimpers)
...I'm gonna pay him a visit.
No...
WALTER (over intercom):
Release the hostages
or I throw your rockets
overboard.
(passengers murmuring)
Are you kidding me?
All right,
come on.
Yes, this is the man
you stole from.
Who's this, please?
My name is not important;
what I have is.
Correct.
But what I have is
even more precious.
And I will kill them,
one by one,
unless you bring me my weapons
immediately.
(quietly):
You give him those rockets
and he'll shoot that rescue
copter right out of the sky.
Happy?
There has to be
another vessel nearby.
Can you locate anything?
I'm looking.
You have five seconds to comply.
Hurry, Happy.
Five...
four...
No...
A Japanese destroyer
isn't too far away.
Three...
Hack the destroyer's
control system.
Two...
one.
WOMAN:
No, no, no, no....
WALTER:
Okay, okay, okay! You win.
Lido deck, five minutes,
with the rockets.
Perfect.
Grab the captain.
You...
take Tennille.
Let's go.
PILOT (over comms):
Navy 6-4.
Four minutes out and closing.
Okay, hold...
WALTER:
Okay.
Okay, okay.
That's close enough.
Or they go
overboard.
Can I have my
rockets now, please?
Give me your word
you'll let the passengers go.
You see this gun?
It's got a sensitive trigger.
Sometimes it goes off
when I've barely
even touched it.
You guys want to see?
No, no, no.
No, no.
Okay.
Put the gun down.
Thank you.
Search them.
Raul's.
I'm sorry, who are
you two guys working for?
Nothing?
(grunts)
Hey!
(coughing)
(feedback whines)
Oh.
Who have you been talking to?
PILOT (over comms):
This is Navy 6-2.
We are five miles out, roughly
two minutes to intercept.
Are we clear to approach,
Agent Gallo? Over.
Tell them everything is fine.
PILOT:
Repeat. Are we clear to land?
Over.
CABE:
Okay. Okay.
This is Agent Cabe Gallo.
You're clear to approach.
Good job.
Take 'em over there.
Move!
Go, go! To the rail.
You all right?
To the rail. Now, now. Move it.
Now for the fireworks.
Booyah!
We got painted! Single rocket
tracking us now! Slice right!
Verona, this is Romeo.
We have been engaged.
Chopper's
five miles out,
give them standard
approach speed...
impact in 90 seconds.
You ever been scuba diving?
(Cabe grunts)
CHRISTOPH:
Come on!
What are you
standing around for?
Get them!
Okay. We gotta get
in touch with Happy.
Happy, have you hacked
into that destroyer yet?
How much time we got?
45 seconds.
We got 45 seconds
until that rocket
takes out a U.S.
military helicopter.
Thank you for filling me in
on the stakes now.
We're in the ship's
weapons system,
but we need more time.
The Japanese are alerted
to our Trojan horse entry,
and they're
throwing up firewalls.
We can't hack like Walter!
CABE:
Just figure something out.
PILOT:
Rocket closing.
1.8 miles.
Alter our vector!
CABE:
This is Agent Cabe Gallo.
If you want to live
to tell this war story,
do exactly as I say.
We only have 30 seconds.
There's no time
for evasive maneuvers.
Hold your course.
Do nothing?
CABE:
The less you move,
the less the rocket moves.
We're gonna intercept it.
Using what?!
(alarms blaring)
(speaking Japanese)
Wow, you picked a hell of
a day to ditch school, kid.
(missile launching)
CABE: Maintain your position,
lieutenant!
Lieutenant...
Talk to me, guys.
We're good.
We're alive.
Can't say the same
for our fuel line, though.
We shook up pretty bad.
We're pouring gas.
No chance we could
make it to you.
Better come up with
a plan "B," Walter.
How about a plan "C"?
THUG:
Go, go, go.
WALTER:
Okay.
CHRISTOPH:
Here they are!
The men who cause us
nothing but trouble.
In a few moments, the Navy's
gonna send another helo,
so... you can tell me
what agencies
you work for,
or you guys are going
into the sea.
Well...
Yeah, we're, uh...
we're here working with...
(grunting)
Freeze! Hold it!
Hold it!
Hold it right there!
Good work.
Give me the gun
and we'll put 'em in the hold.
Not exactly, Agent.
Hey.
You're with Christoph.
No...
...he is Christoph.
Licensed captain,
legitimate
commercial vessel,
minimal customs issues compared
to big cruise liners...
It's perfect front
for big weapons.
Yes.
It surely was.
Raul.
We've wasted
enough time.
We need to get these rockets
off the ship.
Grab the girl,
meet me on the lower deck.
Move!
(screams)
Come with me.
Hey! Hey. Take me. Take me.
Hey!
(passengers screaming)
Don't move.
Let's go.
(passengers exclaiming,
shouting)
WOMAN 1:
Hey! Get us out of here!
(indistinct shouting)
MAN:
What's going on?
Okay.
MAN 2:
We can't get out.
MAN:
Wait, wait...
All right, okay.
Hold this.
What the hell are you doing?
Chaz Bonesteel
ain't going out like this.
(groans)
Okay.
Come on, Bonesteel.
(panting):
Okay.
I'm gonna need a boost.
PAIGE: Please, no.
MAN: Come on.
Please, no.
Let's go!
Get her in the raft.
Come on!
We got to move fast.
No.
Please, please.
Let's go!
Hold on, hold on.
You want to guarantee
they don't blow you out
of the water? Take me.
Why is that?
I'm a high-value
government asset.
You take me,
you'll have
a fighting chance.
Let her go.
Walter, don't.
Right. Get on.
No!
MAN: Let's go!
Walter.
CAINE:
Let's go.
(grunting, panting)
CAINE (in distance):
Come on. Move it!
You can do this.
(grunting)
Bonesteel!
Wha...?
(brief burst of gunfire)
WALTER:
Sly, where are you?
Ah, I... I'm tangled
in the rope.
I can't get free.
SYLVESTER: It's dragging me
back. It's dragging me under.
Oh, God.
Walter.
Walter, the suction from the
propeller is pulling me in.
It's too strong.
Hold on, buddy.
Hold on!
Walter?
Walter.
Sylvester!
You got to find the crew.
They need to shut off
the propeller.
The crew's...
locked up.
Happy, I'm gonna need your help.
WALTER:
Cabe! Cabe, where are you?
Cabe!
Cabe, Sylvester!
Here! Grab my hand.
Walter, it's pulling too strong.
Cabe, don't let me go.
Hold on, kid! Grab my hand!
Don't let me go.
Happy, I'm here.
HAPPY: Okay, take
the throttles out of gear.
The control handles are in
the middle of the panel.
(sighs)
Okay, I see them.
Push them both down toward you.
CABE:
Hold on, kid!
I don't think I'm gonna make it.
Hold on!
It's not working.
HAPPY:
Okay, you need to pull
the manual diesel kill switch.
There should be a handle
on the floor somewhere.
Oh, I see it. Okay.
WALTER:
Don't let go!
Come on.
(grunting)
(sighs)
Thank God.
I got it.
It worked.
CABE:
Take a breath, kid.
Everything's gonna
be okay, pal.
(Sylvester panting)
Take it easy.
SYLVESTER:
Cabe, watch out! (gasping)
You really screwed this up.
The people I promised
those rockets to--
they're gonna take my life,
so I'm gonna take yours.
(ship's horn blowing)
WALTER: No, you got it.
You got it.
Was I right about boats?
Yeah, probably.
I was right about boats.
Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, you're
right. Yeah.
(grunting)
Okay.
PAIGE: Yeah, we had
an interesting day.
We were on a
big, beautiful
cruise ship, and, uh...
so, um...
So you really do work
for the government.
Yep.
I, uh... always did
tell you the truth,
so, um...
I was wondering if you
could tell me the truth.
What could I do better
so that Th-the mistakes
that I made with you...
that I-I don't make them again?
You are who you are.
But you're challenging
and sometimes
impossible because
no woman can stimulate
that mind of yours forever.
If you want honesty...
...after a while,
you lost interest in me--
I could tell-- and that hurt.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
There's no malice in you,
Walter.
Just facts.
And, um...
Things didn't go
exactly like we planned.
...the fact is,
before you get involved
with someone else,
make sure you can
make a real connection.
It wouldn't be fair
to her otherwise.
Take care of yourself.
Mm-hmm.
(sighs)
You ready, Ralph?
Once I start this fire,
there's no putting it out.
Back up. Let's go.
Come on.
And...
there's the money.
Where's the lucky lady?
Well, I'm breaking
about 12 laws right now,
so I suggest you talk to her
while you can.
I'm gonna seal the deal
for the kid.
(whooshing)
TOBY:
Ah, crap.
"Love, Ralhp."
TOBY: Look at 'em.
They're both content.
Love can be misspelled
and messy, but it still works.
Just needs to be
given a chance.
Oh, forget it.
Whoa, what are you doing?
Are you gonna punch me?
I don't think so.
Okay, then.
WOMAN:
What is going on?!
This is extremely dangerous!
I have called the police.
Damn it.
This cannot happen on school grounds!
Let's go, Ralph.
What...?
She called the fuzz.
What about Sloan?
Don't worry.
Chicks dig outlaws.
Start the car!
♪ ♪
Hey.
Uh, are we
still doing
that business dinner
tomorrow night?
(sighs)
You know, um...
I've been thinking
about that, now.
You've been working hard
lately, and, uh...
I don't want to take up
your Saturday.
If you think there's stuff
we should go over...
You're an incredible asset
to the team,
and I want what's best for you.
That's a weekend off.
Especially with a case
like today.
Okay.
I'll see you Monday.
Monday.
Are you sending
a valentine to Megan?
Why is that a secret?
(whispering):
Because she's Walter's sister.
I know that.
So...
he's my boss
and my best friend.
And she's sweet,
and you like her.
(sighs)
Chaz would send her
that valentine.
Hey, soda?
Figured we, uh,
order some pizza,
pull an all-nighter
on this thing,
you know, like the old days.
You know,
normally I'd love to, but...
I think I need to see
someone tonight.
Oh, Valentine's.
Ah.
Who's the girl?
It's early stages.
I didn't think you went
for the sappy holidays, buddy.
(chuckles)
Yeah.
Whoever she is, she's, uh...
she's lucky to have
a guy like you.
You mean that?
Uh-huh. Of course.
There's a reservation
at 8:00 at Escala,
in my name, for tomorrow.
You should take her.
Thank you, Walter.
Have a good night.
www.tvsubtitles.net