CABE:
Fish.
Okay.
Poodle.
Yikes.
What's this?
Establishing Cabe's
personality baseline.
Spider.
(chuckles) Wow.
I'm researching the use
of behaviorism
into predicting the future.
I say if you know
the psychological ground floor
of a subject,
its tendencies or its maladies,
I'm postulating you can
predict future behavior.
Test will be if he pulls
another shocked face,
will he see my foot flying
toward his butt?
I'll expect it.
PAIGE: Why the sudden interest
in predicting the future?
Where's Walter?
He's at the hospital,
visiting Megan.
Oh, there
a connection there?
Megan and predicting the future?
Paige, you just leave
the shrinking to me.
When did this begin?
A few days ago.
Respiratory infection,
for someone with MS, is very...
concerning.
Did the doctors give you
an antibiotic cocktail?
They just put me on one.
Plus 100 milligrams
of prednisone.
You know, an infection like
this can lead to sepsis
or low blood pressure?
Yes, Walter.
Yeah.
And I'm on several I.V. drips
to make
my heart beat harder.
Did they give you, uh...
I knew the minute I told you,
you would start
spouting research
and second-guessing.
Do I do that?
It's under control.
Okay, get some rest.
Check in later.
Okay.
WALTER:
You know, I'm, uh...
I'm baffled that you didn't
inform me
of her condition sooner.
This only started
a few days ago,
and Megan didn't want you
to divert your attention
over to her.
I need more time.
And in a few weeks,
I'll have the rocket finished
and submitted
to the Karman Prize.
And then when I win,
I'll have an influx
of 50 million in cash
to buy equipment
to finish my research to save her.
Walter,
the doctors aren't discussing
her condition in terms of weeks.
We don't give in.
No, you stay with her today,
and you make sure that
her treatment stays aggressive.
Isn't that up to Megan?
Any sign that her blood pressure
is getting too low,
then you tell them
to increase her meds
or add a new agent
like phenylephrine.
Are you listening to me?
Can we take a breath
and think about her
and her quality of life?
More important...
is preserving her life
and her mind.
We do whatever it takes.
Promise me you will do
the right thing.
I promise.
All right.
So, the initial plan,
uh, for the project budgeted
at 15 months,
but given Megan's condition,
it will have to be accelerated
to being underway within three,
and then Megan's life
will be saved.
Questions?
Yes?
Well, what exactly is the plan
to save her life?
Yes.
So, uh, I am going
to download her brain,
her thoughts,
her consciousness, her memories,
preserve them digitally,
until I can find another vessel
after her body fails.
Not in three months.
Maybe 20 years.
Megan does not have that long.
So, in order
to save her mind,
I need to build something
that does not exist.
It's a-a data server
with the capacity
to store the contents
of the human brain.
That's at least 50 petabytes
of storage capacity.
The immediate issue is funding.
The Karman prize, uh,
won't judge for months,
so I need starter capital,
which means I'll have
to take on other jobs,
so I may not be here.
We all want to do anything
we can to help, Walter, but...
I think our primary question is
how are you doing emotionally?
Oh, I'm fine.
I figure it's gonna run me
a million per petabyte.
About that.
So I'm gonna go call
our wealthiest clients,
see what I can't drum up.
He's officially gone
through the looking glass.
I don't like the way
he's handling this.
I don't think any of them are
gonna be able to handle it.
I think that...
What?
Who the hell is that?
Identify yourself.
Mark Willis,
Central Intelligence.
CIA.
Explains how he came
in like a cloud.
Dark cloud.
Homeland's agreed to lend out
Scorpion's services
to my unit.
Oh, lucky us.
For a significant payday.
We're listening.
This is the 27B/6.
Brand-new flagship of an airline
known as Integrity Airlines.
No such thing.
It's top-secret,
servicing only the CIA.
You guys have
a secret airline?
What kind of snacks
are we talking?
Or is that a secret, too?
Integrity functions
independently
of any commercial or
military frequency.
We have our own call signs,
and we are
undetectable by radar.
Nine hours ago,
this plane was on a routine
mission and went missing.
Define routine.
Running money,
weapons, copy machines
or other tools of
country-building or takeover.
What?
That's not how the CIA
would use a secret plane?
Last location ping?
Over Fort Collins, Colorado.
There's no indication of
a crash and no response
to radio calls.
So hijacked?
Doubtful.
Then the pilot stole it.
Our men, highly trained,
with spotless records.
Sly, anything?
SYLVESTER:
A plane heading west
wouldn't double back
and risk suspicion
by pinging
the same location twice.
Okay, I'm running an analysis
on the sound package
from the last ping.
The plane was tilting down
when the last ping registered.
A plane of that weight,
cruising at that speed,
yields a possible
landing location of...
Oh, my God.
That's Coughlan Air Force Base.
That's Area 51.
Secret spy mission
in Area 51-- spooky.
No pun intended.
The base and several miles
surrounding it
are protected from eyes
in the sky by ambient microwaves
as an active defense system.
It disrupts satellite,
cell and radio communication.
It's all a part
of their moratorium
on communication systems
that haven't been
strictly sanctioned by the base.
Cone of silence.
The better to keep
their secrets safe.
Am I the only one?
Area 51, aliens?
A plane like this
would run quiet,
probably use a tungsten alloy
in the fuselage
for its vibration
stabilizing system.
I can't confirm or deny that.
Get us down to that desert.
I can build a device
to detect
the ionic gamma ray signature
of the tungsten alloy
and find its exact location.
Your superiors at Homeland
will be told
you're upgrading
our data systems in Barstow.
I never came in here.
The size of your payday will
ensure you take special care
to see that doesn't bother you.
$50,000.
$300,000.
150, final offer.
HAPPY: Sold.
Make my check out
to Walter O'Brien
for Megan.
Yeah, ditto.
Same here.
I'll take care of it.
I look forward
to hearing from you.
Excellent.
Can get closer
to my research funding goals.
No, “thank you”? Uh...
We just made
a moving gesture
for Megan and...
We're helping him solve
a problem.
He needs X amount of dollars;
we chipped away.
Math is math.
CABE: I think the
team's gonna need
some hand-holding
regarding Megan.
You deal with them,
and I'll take care of Walter.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
Okay, the gamma ray spectrometer
is operational.
SYLVESTER:
Just don't get too close
to the base. You don't know
what they're working on.
Or who.
Aliens again?
Don't know.
I'm sorry, can you can
this blather?
Sylvester, can I get
an update on Megan, please?
Yeah, well,
I don't really know how well
she's responding
to the treatment,
but the doctor seems to think
she'll be... (static)
We've hit the cone of silence.
You've asked Walter how
he's processing Megan's illness.
How are you handling it?
I'm a physician.
Illness, death, grief--
it's really just an influx
of stress-related,
pro-inflammatory cytokines
which eventually dissipate.
So a friend's illness,
possible death, is...
it's no more than just the...
clinical release of chemicals?
No, no, I'm not discounting
the emotional.
Whether it's
Bonanno's Four Trajectories
or the five stages
of Kubler-Ross,
it's a natural process.
Anything natural,
to me, is fine.
What's with the envelopes?
Predictions of the future.
I think I got something.
The photon energy
is off the chart.
Okay, hit the brakes!
In your face,
unfindable spy plane.
Let's leave.
There's no
tail number.
We're being paid
a bundle--
let's confirm that's our bird.
♪ ♪
No one here!
Incredible photography unit
on the underside of this beast.
You could take a portrait
of a flea at 30,000 feet.
This all beyond
state-of-the-art, and...
all hollow.
I'm assuming hidden
compartments,
in case anybody's ever searched.
They made an effort to steal it
and then just... abandon it?
I don't think so.
I think they're coming back.
There's a whole blood bank
down here.
All AB-negative
with rare proteins.
That's for someone
with aplastic anemia
who needs regular
transfusions.
That's neither
of the pilots.
Not according to their dossiers.
Just a guess here,
but those pilots
might be picking up a passenger
who isn't coming aboard
voluntarily.
I got chloroform and zip ties.
This isn't just a missing plane;
it's a kidnapping.
Remember how you said it
couldn't be one of your pilots?
Well, good chance it is--
so good luck with that.
We'll take our
cashier's check now.
What if I doubled the fee?
No!
Keep talking.
This gets out,
the program is exposed
and years of data go sour.
If you find the agents,
find their victim
and figure out where they plan
on taking him: 300 grand.
Send in your own guys!
They'll be long gone before
I can get a team assembled.
Then get the base commander
at Coughlan to handle it.
That also exposes the program.
350 grand.
Wait...
Deal! - No!
Listen, you know what?
I'll do it myself.
You heard Sylvester--
Megan is not improving.
And I need the money
to complete my research.
We'll all do it.
Good. Thank you.
“The CIA dude will
rope us into something
more dangerous than
finding a plane”"
I hate to say I told you so.
Why are you doing this?
I want it on record that I predicted
that getting led around
by the prospect of a payday
is bad business.
Especially with
the CIA involved.
TOBY: We are gonna sneak into one of
the most heavily guarded
patches of U.S. soil,
with no form of communication
to track down an
unknown kidnapping victim,
who may or may not already be in
the hands of rogue CIA agents.
Yep.
We're going into Area 51.
♪ Scorpion 2x08 ♪
Area 51
Original Air Date on November 9, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
All right, so, one more time
for the slightly less brilliant?
So the people that
work on this base
are experts in fields with
countless applications--
most military,
all dangerous
in the wrong hands.
And that's who they're coming
to kidnap? An expert?
Well, you can't just
walk into Area 51.
So they stole
the only plane in the world
that can fly under
Area 51's security.
Any clue why we don't
just stay here
and wait till
they come back?
Yeah, I'm not so hot
into sneaking into
mysterious Air Force bases.
CABE:
And I'll wager
the rogue agents are armed.
I don't want to get
into a gunfight.
We know the target
has a rare blood type,
so we determine his identity
through the base's
medical records
and we track down
where he works on the base
in order to
rescue him.
What if they already
got their target?
The CIA agents
got here before us.
Could be six hours,
could be 30 minutes.
CABE: But we still don't know
how they're getting on the base.
If they're tunneling,
that's gonna take a while.
Subterfuge,
also a time suck.
We got a shot
at shutting this thing down.
Yeah, but because of
the cone of silence,
we can't just hack the base's
medical records externally,
so we're heading in.
Now, you guys find him,
warn him and get him to safety.
While you're just
catching some rays?
Well, I'm happy to go,
but who is gonna hack
the plane's guidance system
to find its likely destination?
You know, the other
half of our job?
I'll keep guard in case
the bad guys come back.
How do we break in?
With these.
Okay, we aim the plane's
reflective panels
into my magnifying glass.
The heat will be
the equivalent
of 100 solar panels
focused on an area
the size of a playing card,
which I will aim directly
at the tire
of a passing delivery truck.
Boom goes the tire.
And while the driver's
changing it,
he gains extra cargo.
And since this is the only road
into the base,
one is bound to come along soon.
Until then, we wait.
Disgusting.
Dental hygiene is beautiful.
(screams): Aah!
(Walter typing rapidly)
Cabe...
look over here:
Domestic flight paths
circling over L.A.,
DC and Chicago.
Now why is a CIA plane
flying repeatedly
over U.S. cities? Huh?
You're being paid to find
a final destination.
Find it and let's
clear out of here.
And when you're done, son,
I want to talk to you
about your sister
and what may be coming.
Busy.
Uh, I know
you're concerned
about Walt on
the Megan thing.
“The Megan thing”?
Her illness?
Uh...
He'll work through it.
We all will.
It is what it is.
That's a little chilly.
My mother died
the day I was born.
Death has always been
a part of my life.
Now, Sylvester... he's going
to be a basket case.
He won't be able to handle it
as well as the rest of us.
You may consider
it's okay to just...
think about it and be sad.
Or just don't think about it.
Truck!
Oh...
Thing of beauty.
Let's move.
(sighs)
So... not the best news.
The phenylephrine
didn't clear your lungs
the way we had hoped.
So...
the aggressive treatment
would be...?
Intubation.
SYLVESTER: Then that's
the thing to do.
Right?
Not right?
We're gonna need a minute.
(door opens, closes)
I don't want to be intubated.
It's painful...
and I'll have to be
under constant sedation...
No, I...
I have to encourage you
to be aggressive.
You have to stop being
a conduit to my brother
and be the man that I love.
All through here!
Copy that!
Take her to Gate Three!
SOLDIER:
Yes, sir!
Okay. Now all we need to do
is access the base intranet
and hack into
their medical records.
Right. Easy.
Just walk in an office
and find a computer.
No, we can connect via
a peripheral system.
Like the sprinkler
controls or...
The sewer system.
(computer blipping)
HAPPY (quietly):
Okay...
I am in their intranet,
but their medical records
are tight as a drum.
And with our best
hackers elsewhere,
this could take
hours. Days.
So we're stuck in a sewer
for no good reason?
Unless we can call
Sly to hack it.
It's an old-school PBX.
Private branch exchange.
They work best
on ground start trunks,
if the intercom is
connected to an outside line.
Okay, only one way to find out.
PAIGE:
What are you doing?
HAPPY: It's like blue boxing
in the '70s.
Scratching the coin
on the transmitter
generates a 2600 hertz tone.
To this old system,
that tone is code
to open a line.
(dial tone sounds)
Well, lookie here.
(speed dial beeps)
TOBY:
If the kidnapping target
needs a monthly transfusion,
it would normally happen
at the closest hospital
with an extensive
blood bank.
Only a few matches there.
Okay, cross-referencing now
with the rare blood type.
South Nevada Hospital.
Loading transfusion
patient names now...
Loading slowly...
He's searching.
Oh, this would be an opportunity
to ask him how
Megan's doing.
Uh...
What?
Oh, uh, I've got a name.
Dr. Ivan Zahn.
Uzbek national
who defected 13 years ago.
He currently leads a team
at Coughlan Air Force Base
in the computer
engineering division.
His expertise is in
high-capacity compression
and storage.
He's considered by many
to be the best in his field.
Okay, based on
his scientific field,
Dr. Zahn's office is located
in Laboratory Five of “C” Wing.
Sly, hang in there.
Okay.
Honestly, I think I'm
figuring this place out.
Why people are
so scared of it.
It's the mystique.
Come up on a stairwell,
which opens to a door
just outside “C” Wing.
Say a place is full of secrets
and imagination takes over.
Hence, little green men.
Your point?
This place is no scarier
than any other Air Force base.
We just waltzed in here.
SOLIDER:
Hold it!
Nobody move!
(guns cocking)
I have an envelope
in my pocket predicting this.
Okay, almost into
the navigation system.
A couple more moments,
we will know
the plane's destination.
Know that we're here
for Megan.
But in the end, what if
that's just not enough?
Almost finished.
I don't want you to go
into this flat-footed.
Could take you years
to get over.
I know that you've suffered
tremendous loss,
but this is different.
There's time to find a solution.
You got something to say
to Megan, you should say it.
Spend your time
making memories.
Don't bury yourself in
“solutions” that may not work.
(typing rapidly)
Plane's headed
to Uzbekistan.
And I'm certain
it will work.
One person can take care
of Megan: me.
(sighs)
Okay, son.
Let's clear out
of this plane now.
Walter, what's
the holdup?
Hold on, hold on,
hold on.
One second.
(Walter laughs)
Oh, God...
Storage capacity on this
is almost two petabytes.
Shouldn't be possible
for a machine this small.
It's ten years ahead of
anything else on the market.
Camera...
Cabe...
the camera equipment Happy saw?
This plane is used
to spy on American cities.
And they're flying in secret
back to Area 51.
It's a safe bet that technology
was developed there.
By the guy
that they're looking to kidnap.
With this prototype
and the inventor,
they could make a whole
fleet of planes.
Sell it to every
hostile government
in the world.
(vehicle approaching)
Didn't I tell
you to move?
Put him in the hold.
I think we found
our kidnap victim.
(plane engines whirring,
powering up)
Oh, my God...
Agent Cabe Gallo's
right over that ridge.
He'll confirm
we're with Homeland.
These cuffs are a little tight.
Is that necessary?
Please shut up, sir!
Okay, did you even bother
checking on Dr. Zahn?
The man is in danger.
Doctor's on base some weeks,
gone for others.
But I do appreciate your attempt
to bolster
this cockamamie story.
You'll be eating that tone soon.
They were here an hour ago.
Where are they?
HAPPY:
They still on the plane?
The secret CIA plane?
Okay, if they are,
things have gone severely south.
We need to find them.
We can't lose time.
Oh, you'll have plenty
of time in the brig.
I-I can see how this may
look bad, but it's the truth.
I'm not trying to discount
your story, Doctor.
This base has seen its share
of run-ins with rogue men.
Small green men.
PAIGE: Our boss is
Deputy Director
of Homeland Security
Katherine Cooper.
She'll sort this out.
Yes, of course.
Yes, thank you, ma'am.
Sorry for the bother.
Thank you.
Okay.
Well, according to
Deputy Director Cooper,
Homeland team known as Scorpion
are updating data servers
in Barstow.
So who the hell are you?
We're Scorpion.
I'm a world-renowned
behaviorist.
I have a 178 IQ.
170.
Barstow was our cover story.
It was the CIA's idea.
Right.
Put 'em in a cell.
Uh...
What?!
Heartbeat's strong.
He's sedated but alive.
Luckily, this
was designed
to keep us out, not in.
We got to take control
of this plane.
That means taking out one
of the agents in the cockpit
and forcing the other one
to fly us back to Coughlan.
Yeah.
Easier if we
divide and conquer.
I could reprogram
the plane's flight path
from this control panel,
reroute us straight back to Coughlan.
Great.
Yeah, it would be great
if Happy were here.
(groans) I'll never get
this lock open without tools.
Then plan B.
(alarm beeping)
Temperature control
in the cargo hold.
I'll check on it.
How'd you get buckled in?
Sorry about that.
(indistinct radio chatter)
TOBY:
I knew it.
I did, I wrote it down.
What good's a promise of money
if Walter's murdered
by rogue spies?
Curtis, your pie hole, shut it.
Guys, we can get out
of this, right?
Maybe not, this is a
state-of-the-art R & D facility,
meaning everything
is state of the art.
This electromagnetic lock
has a pound force of over 4,000.
Double what I've ever seen.
Oh, that's great.
The one lock you've never seen.
PAIGE: Okay, do
what we always do.
Embrace the unknown
with cold facts.
Someone installed this lock,
then someone can uninstall it.
It shouldn't matter that you
haven't seen this one before.
Okay, hold on, that might be it.
This base is full of things
we've never seen.
If Sly's right
about microwaves
floating around the base
as part of the defense system,
I could use a cell phone
to channel the waves
into the lock
and short-circuit the mechanism.
Then what?
There's literally
an army sitting outside.
We get out, hit the stairwell,
and go to the roof
where the comm dishes are.
Then we can knock out a dish,
poke out a tiny hole in the
base's cone of silence.
Like a, like a hole
in the ozone layer.
Then we can contact Sylvester?
He'll find the plane
and Cabe and Walt.
You said we need a cell phone.
Toby's phone, actually.
Your crippling
gambling problem's
left you unable
to afford nice things,
like the latest cell technology,
but yours is old enough
to have a nickel
cadmium battery.
Insulted, hurt,
but glad to help.
Except all of our cell phones
are in an evidence box.
Remember your disgusting habit?
Which one?
I'm gonna need you to elaborate.
SARDO (over intercom): Shultz,
get back here and buckle in.
Turbulence ahead.
I'm heading
into the cockpit.
It's time to turn
this plane around.
Okay.
Wait at the panel.
HAPPY: Okay, window's thick,
but not soundproof.
We got to be careful.
PAIGE: All right.
Focus.
I'm a little rusty
on my hooking storage bins
with dental floss skills.
Ooh.
Oop...
Oh, I haven't even
used all my minutes.
(beeping)
Walter.
Cabe!
SARDO:
Put the gun down.
Not unless you turn
this plane around.
That's not gonna happen.
Either this plane lands
in Uzbekistan
or it crashes
into a mountain.
The autopilot I programmed
has us heading straight
into Boundary Peak.
Digital cyanide pill--
classic CIA.
I'd drop the weapon.
I can override his passcode
and reroute it.
Shoot him, Cabe!
Shoot him!
(alarm beeping)
Nothing's happening.
It is-- I switched the antenna
from receiver mode to broadcast.
It's channeling energy straight
from the battery into the lock.
Well, how do you know
it's working?
Stick your hand
in front of the phone.
(sizzling)
Oh!
It's working.
(lock clicking)
Well, there's microwaves
up here, too!
We can use the phone
to short-circuit the dish.
No, the dishes aren't
electromagnetic!
Then take it off broadcast mode,
cut off its transmissions,
so we can call Sylvester.
HAPPY: Uh, no, the best way
to interrupt the airwaves
is to interfere with the--
Or that.
Okay... I got a signal!
I'm calling Sly.
Coughlan launches
a dozen drone flights a day.
I should be able
to hack into one from here.
Okay, if you adjust
its frequencies,
you can scan the plane's
gamma ray signature,
and you can locate it
like we did this morning.
Got one!
Hacking in now.
Cabe, keys, keys!
Little busy here!
What are you doing?!
I'm putting us into a nosedive.
Plane's rotation will cause a
g-force acceleration giving us
roughly 20 seconds of
weightlessness-- you hold on!
You're killing us!
(alarms buzzing, whooping)
(alarms continuing)
WALTER: Rerouting us!
Ha!
18 seconds.
Weightlessness almost over.
We need to get to the cockpit!
We got to level this off!
SYLVESTER: Found the plane.
Okay, where are they?
Over Nevada,
near the White Mountains.
They're descending.
Guys, I think
they're in a nosedive.
(alarms buzzing, whooping)
Okay...
Okay.
CABE: Any chance that g-force
thing you were talking about
might be making us lightheaded?
It could cause us
to pass out.
Guys, this is not good.
Are you sure it's
not landing?
SYLVESTER:
I have never seen anything
intentionally land
at that angle.
Get us an image
of the plane.
I'm positioning
drone cameras now.
Move into the cockpit.
Oh, my God!
G-force must've
knocked them out.
They'll regain consciousness
if the plane levels out.
Okay, Sly,
can you use the drone
to hack into the plane
to level it?
That is what I am trying
to do right now.
Okay, Walter left the backdoor
open in the system--
I am in.
Secret spy plane hacking
protections, in your face!
SYLVESTER:
Walter? Cabe?
Walter, wake up!
Not now, Sylvester.
It's too early.
Hurry!
They're gonna crash!
No, Walter, you need
to wake up right now!
(both gasping, grunting)
(alarms buzzing, whooping)
Whew! Whew!
(Walter chuckles)
Sylvester,
how are you talking to us?
Look outside
your starboard window.
(over radio):
That's me.
Can you get us to Coughlan?
I reprogrammed the
navigation system
to send us to the
last grounded location.
But, uh, you know, this
may come as a sur-surprise,
but, um,
I don't know how
to land a plane.
HAPPY: I can walk you through this.
Happy?
Okay, don't worry,
this will be a piece of cake.
TOBY:
Aliens?
Oh, man.
LIEUTENANT: Hands up!
Drop that phone.
Happy, hello, are you there?
(alarm resumes)
CABE: Happy, we're low on fuel.
We need to land.
HAPPY:
A large-body aircraft
is headed straight for this base
and the guy who's flying it--
he doesn't know
what the hell he's doing.
It's gonna crash right into us
if you don't give her back that phone.
I admit I admire
your tenacity with this story.
You can verify it.
You have the equipment.
Okay, you know what?
As soon as it's done,
you can put the cuffs back on.
But that plane is entering
into Coughlan airspace
in less than ten seconds
whether you believe me or not.
Check the tower.
Meanwhile, let's get you cozy.
Happy? Happy?
MAN (over P.A.): Sir, we see a (siren wailing)
heavy aircraft directly headed
for the base.
All right, scramble three fighters.
Let's shoot this thing
out of the sky.
Are you crazy?
Given its current trajectory,
shooting that plane
will turn it into a
flying ball of fire
headed straight
for this place.
Unless you let me land
it safely in the desert.
Happy, we can
see the landing strip.
What do we do?
Fighters stand down.
They're keeping
their guns on you,
so you better be for real.
HAPPY:
Okay, keep it above 180 knots,
pull back the throttle,
the knob between the seats.
Shift it back about halfway.
Okay.
Okay, now gradually
start pulling back
on the control stick.
(Walter grunting with effort)
Doing that now.
Okay, you need
to deploy the flaps.
There should be a handle
next to the throttle.
Pull it back 15%
and move it slowly to 40.
When you hit the ground
kick the throttle into idle.
Holding steady.
Uh, we're coming in too sharp.
We're coming in
too sharp!
Walt, pull back.
Pull up, pull up, pull up!
Brace for impact!
(engines whirring,
powering down)
(panting)
We made it.
I just want to sit here.
I just want one minute of quiet.
Get your hands up!
Hands up!
It was nice while it lasted.
You okay?
We're fine, why?
I saw you guys on that roof,
when the shadow crossed you.
You were thinking alien.
And the unknown
scared the hell out of you.
Did not.
Nice try.
SOLIDER:
Right this way, sir.
Okay, that's got to be the most
confused scientist in the world.
Let's go!
(Hummer engines start)
So, uh, money.
Yeah,
wire transfer
would be preferable.
Oh, you know what?
I'd also love...
(chuckles)
...love an audience
with Dr. Zahn.
He designed
this device.
I'm working on a project and
I really think that I could...
open up...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What the hell?
You nosed around a bit too deep
in the mission of this plane.
I'm afraid you know
a little too much.
I gotta say,
I didn't see this coming.
This one's on me.
Obviously, I'd prefer
not to kill you.
But unfortunately, Mr. O'Brien
knows information
I really can't
have getting out.
NSA spying might've been
shut down, but yours
is expanding.
TOBY: The rest of us
don't know anything
about this plane.
In fact, I was hardly
even on this plane.
Plane? What-what plane?
Toby!
Let's go for a ride.
No, no.
Before we head out
to what is unquestionably
a large hole in the desert,
6,000 feet above
our heads is a drone,
operated by our friend
Sylvester. Oh...
He's filming and recording
this conversation.
And if you kill us...
you go away for murder.
That's good.
Oh, I'm guessing by now
he's downloaded this footage
to dozens of servers
around the country.
You're bluffing.
Walter, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
I'd say he's gonna prove you
wrong by getting that drone
to give you a buzz cut
in eight seconds. Seven,
six,
five, four,
three, two...
SYLVESTER: The drone interface
is malfunctioning!
...one.
Can I interest you
in a card trick?
Oh, no!
WILLIS: Get eyes on that.
You'll note
its high-sensitivity camera
and long-distance microphone.
Walter, I hope Mr. CIA is being
nice, because the drone's camera
stopped functioning and I can't
hear a word you're saying.
Stand down, gentlemen.
Well, we should be going now.
HAPPY: Oh, wait,
wait a minute--
we've got the CIA
by the yabos.
We're missing out on the
opportunity of a lifetime here.
Okay, in April of '71,
there was a video--
an elliptical-shaped object
that was spotted
over Phoenix,
then suddenly
disappeared midair.
What was it?
We still don't know.
Where's Hoffa?
The Meadowlands.
Everyone knows that.
JFK?
Don't push it.
All right, let's head out, gang.
I'm gonna take this.
(train horn blowing in distance)
The storage capacity
is astounding.
I'm pretty sure
my concept
will move from
theory to reality
very quickly.
I learned something today,
about the team.
You know the idea
that nature always fills
an empty space?
“Nature abhors a vacuum.”
Aristotle.
Yeah, well, it really
applies to the genius mind.
You all have a real fear
of the unknown.
You really struggle
with anything
you can't prove
or explain.
There's nothing that
we really can't explain.
What about death?
It is the breakdown
of the biological functions
that support life.
See, you-you throw science
at things that
should be emotional.
We process the world
differently from most people.
That's all it is.
You know, and truthfully,
I know exactly what's
going on with Megan.
There is a process to life
that ends in an unknown.
Toby.
What?
Can you explain
Megan's condition as it stands?
She has a bacterial infection
in her lungs. A pneumonia.
Why is that?
She has scarred, damaged lungs.
Why?
She's inhaled small amounts
of food and saliva
that, over time,
have damaged her lungs.
Mm-hmm.
Why is that happening?
Uh, she can't swallow very well
because of the MS.
Uh, explain.
The MS damaged some nerves
in her brain,
probably her medulla.
How come?
Her own immune system
attacked the myelin sheaths
around the nerves.
Thank you, Toby.
(clicks off)
See? We know everything
we need to know.
(clicks on)
Toby...
why is her own body
attacking her nerves?
You know, we don't know.
(clicks off)
I'm just trying to help.
I need to go.
(grunts)
Wasn't it you that said,
the first time that we met,
that we save everybody?
I am going to save
my sister.
I just spoke to the doctor.
Why is she not on a respirator?
He says it's her best chance.
She didn't want to go on it.
Well, it's your job
to convince her.
She's sick;
she's not thinking clearly.
She was thinking.
I trusted you.
You promised me you would
do the right thing.
I did do the right thing.
For Megan.
She doesn't want
to prolong her state,
so I respected her wishes.
Don't go head to head
with me on this.
You've known her for a year,
I've known her my whole life.
I love her just as much.
And I am sorry, Walter,
but you are wrong.
Fine.
Fine, I'll just have to
take care of it myself.
This isn't over.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net