My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
Remind me what we're doing here
in this heat.
Taking a day off.
It's good for you,
clear your head.
Passing H.R. B6A
would clear my head.
You ruin my day of sunshine,
and I will fire you.
Aye aye, Congressman.
Go ahead, cast off.
The rope.
I can see the appeal
of this place.
You're missing the point.
It's about getting away
from it all.
You know,
now that we have some time,
I've been meaning
to ask you...
All right. A little to the left.
Keep her coming back. Careful.
This is precious cargo.
Happy, just slow
down. Just take your time.
You know how fragile and
important this is, okay?
Keep it coming back.
Straight through.
Hey.
Is that it?
Now, we've all been working
very hard.
So, for our reward...
Oh...
Oh!
An authentic original
Proton Arnold cabinet?
Walter, it's beautiful.
It's all original hardware.
It still takes quarters.
You can fix that, right?
Do not insult me.
Cool.
I loved that game.
Hey.
Your dad's gonna
take you to school.
Hey.
It's okay.
When you get back from school,
you'll have first game.
Okay? Go.
Before we go,
I just want
to have a quick
word with Walter.
Okay.
Yeah, sure.
I used to crush that game.
What was your high score?
Oh, I don't know.
At a certain point,
the counter resets.
Cool.
So, look, I wanted to thank you
for the pitching seminar
we gave Ralph last week.
The kinetic
diagnostic analysis.
Yeah. It's really helped us.
I mean, we do these
game scenarios now.
Like, what's the best opening
pitch with three on, two out,
facing a .280 hitter with
a .330 on-base percentage?
That's interesting.
Yeah, look, also...
you really helped my delivery.
That early release--
I picked up three miles an hour
on my fastball.
I called my agent.
He got me a tryout
with the Portland Sea Dogs.
It's Double-A, but still.
Portland?
Mm-hmm.
Does, uh, does Paige
know about this?
Not yet.
Not until it's real.
The only reason I'm telling you
is because you probably know
Ralph's mind
better than anyone.
You're asking what it will
do to him if you leave.
Or bring them with me.
And, look, we're a long
way away from that,
and Ralph is
my priority, but...
Well, I don't have a ready
answer for you, so...
Well, it's hypothetical,
you know.
I still have to try out.
But, um, just think about it.
Okay.
All right?
And keep it
between us.
Mm-hmm.
Ralph, ready?
Bye.
Come on.
Hey.
Ride with me to Kovelsky's.
Let's grab some bagels
for the team.
I had my eye on
you and Drew.
Looks like you're
getting along well.
Yes.
Real convincing, 197.
I'm preoccupied with
a greater good scenario.
Complicated by
personal involvement?
I know the challenges
of mentoring
a child genius,
remember?
What's that say?
It's from "R." It says "Gumbo."
Text back: "Confirm."
"Gumbo confirmed."
Whatever I tell you to do, you
just do it for your own safety.
Cabe, what is this?
"Gum" is
an emergency code word.
From who? Who's "R"?
Questions will be
answered soon enough.
You just did
18 evasive driving maneuvers.
Are you gonna tell me
what's going on?
Stay here.
Curb your curiosity.
Cabe...
Cabe.
I probably shouldn't have
reached out like this...
out of the blue,
after so much time.
15 years.
Your family--
I know you remarried--
are they safe?
My husband took our daughter
back east to look at colleges.
I just...
I didn't want to scare them
unnecessarily.
With what? Tell me
what's happening, Rebecca.
I'm in-house counsel
at a big lobbying firm.
I think I stumbled
on something very illegal,
and now I'm in trouble.
You know I would never call you
unless I had to.
You can always call me.
Cabe...
It's okay. He's with me.
Damn it, Walter.
What are you...?
What is going on here?
Wait, is this...
Walter O'Brien?
Yes, it is.
And you are?
This is Rebecca. Burns.
My ex-wife.
Someone's trying to kill her.
Part of my job at
The Barnwright Group
is to review our clients'
PAC contributions.
This morning, I came
across a wire transfer
made two weeks ago labeled:
"CA 78 SE"
Okay.
I had no clue
what that meant,
so I opened the file.
There were a number of
contributions but no names,
which is a huge red flag.
So I copied the file
onto a flash drive
to run it by
our co-counsel.
But when I went
to print it,
the file was gone.
Money laundering?
That's my guess.
I guarantee Barnwright
monitors their
whole system.
As soon as you
opened the file,
they knew you were
looking at it.
They had an override word
macro triggered to delete it.
They certainly knew something.
When I packed up to leave,
a security officer in a suit
stopped me in the hall.
I'd never seen him before,
but he had a gun.
He wanted to frisk me,
but a couple of staffers
walked by
before he had a chance.
While he was rifling
through my bag,
I dropped the flash drive
in the nearest planter.
That's impressive.
Then when I got home,
I saw a man
walk out of my bedroom
wearing a mask.
He ran at me.
I barely got
to my car.
I didn't know
who else to turn to.
We established the emergency
code word for a reason.
I'm glad you reached out to me.
After all this time, I'm...
I'm just glad you remembered it.
May I see your phone?
Okay.
He's uncouth
but effective.
We're gonna have to get rid
of any trace of you.
We're gonna leave your car.
You're gonna ride with us.
♪ Scorpion 1x09 ♪
Rogue Element
Original Air Date on November 17, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Here they come.
Intelligent eyes.
Clearly has
a wit about her.
Same carriage as Cabe.
They actually
make a good match.
Toby, Happy,
Sylvester, Paige.
My ex-wife Rebecca.
Wow, Gallo,
you were punching
way above your weight class.
Hello.
I'm Sylvester.
I apologize if I am
inordinately anxious.
The pleasure's mine.
What's that?
That is Proton Arnold.
Unplug it.
Okay.
I think what
Cabe means to say is,
"I've told my ex-wife
what a great team I work with--
smartest I'll ever meet."
You're a Cabe whisperer.
I do the same for them.
All right, now that
the meet and greet's over.
"CA 78 SE"
Decoding that is the key
to the file Rebecca found
and whoever came after her.
"CA" is most likely
California.
78-- a year,
a longitude,
a state highway
or exit on any
interstate.
And "SE" could be southeast,
Southern England.
Or "something else."
California, 78,
something else.
You literally called us on this
three minutes ago.
All Barnwright clients are
multi-billion dollar outfits.
Agricultural companies,
airline unions, 50 others.
Hard to know which one
has their values up their ass.
Boy, you're tough
as nails.
Guess you'd have to be
to be married to Cabe.
Moving on.
So, you said when you
returned to your computer
seconds later, the suspicious
file was deleted.
That means whoever set it up
programmed a Trojan horse
to destroy all data viewed
by unauthorized personnel.
The only copy left
might be that one you left
in the planter at Barnwright.
Might be,
maybe, could be.
Cabe, you got
to be patient.
Guys, look at this.
Investigators have concluded
that the explosion
was the result
of an equipment malfunction
aboard the vessel.
Congressman Gostin
was a firebrand champion
of working people,
making him
a nationally recognized figure,
as well as a local hero
to the constituents
in the 78th District.
"CA" stands for California;
"78" stands for 78th District.
What does "SE" stand for?
"Special election."
Isn't that what happens when
a congressman dies in office?
That's what I saw in that file--
contributions
for a special election.
But a special
election is only held
when an incumbent dies
or is removed from office.
They removed him
from office.
Whoever created that
account was raising money
to replace Congressman Gostin
before today's accident.
So, either they are
clairvoyant, or...
This was an assassination.
But why start transferring funds
before knocking him off?
You're just putting
yourself in a position
to be caught;
that's not too smart.
A congressman is dead.
Cabe, would now be the time
to call in reinforcements?
We're dealing with one of
the largest lobbying firms
in the country.
They have tentacles everywhere--
they pull in
big government money.
Big enough to want
to kill a congressman.
We need to be completely
off the grid on this one.
We have to get ahold of that
drive you left at Barnwright.
That's probably
the only way of tracing
whoever wanted Gostin dead.
You still have your I.D.?
I'm sure they deactivated it.
Oh, that's right--
you just met us.
Speaking of badges, Cabe,
I'm gonna need yours.
To look at that exploded
boat for proof of foul play.
There'll be security
at the marina.
Since when do you
loan your shield
so people can
impersonate federal agents?
Since someone came after you.
I want you by my side;
it's the only place that's safe.
I'm in.
Good.
Making my way
to the fifth floor.
Get in and get out, Walter.
No unnecessary risk.
Assume everyone you meet
in that building is a threat.
These the kind of jobs
you guys normally do?
Mm, yeah, we break
and enter a lot.
He was always very gutsy.
So, Rebecca said that there was
a third plant
from the elevator, huh?
That's right.
Make it fast.
Is that your daughter?
Joanna.
She's beautiful?
Seventeen.
When I picture that man tearing
through my house this morning,
more than anything, I'm so happy
that she wasn't home.
She was such a cute baby.
Look at those cheeks.
No, that-that's Amanda.
That's our daughter
who passed away.
Oh, I-I'm so sorry
for your loss.
You're very sweet.
So, Cabe, there's nothing
in that planter. Is she sure?
I thought so,
but I was so nervous.
He needs to be
careful, Cabe.
These are not good people.
Well, is she sure?
I mean, this is...
Who are you?
Tell him you're looking
for Human Resources
and get out of there now,
Walter.
Hi, I'm Dave
from UCLA botany department.
Operations called about
a-a fungus in the, uh, plants.
That's not what I told you
to say, Walter, damn it!
Well, Dave from UCLA, you're
gonna need to come with me.
I'm almost done
with the samples.
Just, uh, one
left actually.
You're done now. Let's go.
Walter, if that's the guy
that tried to frisk Rebecca,
he could be very dangerous.
I-I can't do what
you're asking me to do now.
I've... it's almost finished.
Get out of there now, Walter!
Sir.
Security breach on five!
Man, blue shirt, gray pants!
Walter, what's happening?
I'm in a bit of a bind here.
But I'm buying some time
by jamming some coins
into the door frame.
That's not gonna hold for long.
That's why I told you
to get out when I did.
Open up!
Open the door!
I have an idea.
You move your car to the side
alley off Fourth Street.
Keep the car running
and stand by.
Okay, we're here.
Where the
hell's Walter?
There.
Oh, my God, Walter,
what are you doing?
Son of a bitch!
You got to kick it
into high gear, son!
Cut the power to the rig!
Let's get down there.
I'll be down in 20 seconds.
Ah! They killed the motor.
There's no guarantee.
You get arrested,
you're gonna have an accident
before you get
to the police station!
You got to get out!
You know what,
I'm 30 feet above concrete!
Give me time to think!
You don't have any time!
Quiet! I'm doing
my calculations.
Pull your car up
two-and-a-half feet.
Create a freefall, 9.8
meters per seconds squared.
Hurry!
What is he doing?
4,000 newtons of energy
to break a leg.
I should be okay...
But I'm not paying
for the damage to your car!
Okay, we can go now.
Cabe...
What happened in there?!
We needed this drive.
When I tell you to
get out, you get out.
You risked Rebecca's life,
you risked your life,
and now they've seen
your face, Walter!
They've got it on surveillance!
We don't know what
the repercussions are from that!
Cabe...
Hey, it's okay.
It's 102 in the Southland today.
Hope you brought your sunblock.
That's a good idea.
Did you guys remember
to apply your sunblock?
Yeah, right after
we took our vitamins.
Guys, focus.
Right, sorry.
You're the shrink.
I need you on point, Doc.
I'm on it. Based on posture
alone, this guy's an easy mark.
How you doing today?
Good. How you doing?
I'm in a marina
in triple-digit heat.
How do you think I'm doing?
Agent Gallo,
Homeland Security.
What kind of name is "Cabe"?
It's "Kah-beh."
My mother's Korean.
Oh, sorry.
I-I didn't mean anything by it.
No one ever does.
This is perfect.
Now he's feeling guilty
and self-conscious.
Drop a little
civics lesson.
I'm here to do
the DHS inspection.
Inspectors were already here.
Local PD was.
Not us.
A congressman died.
Homeland's involved.
This is perfect.
Now he's feeling stupid.
You got him right
where you want him.
Now make him insecure.
I have work to do, so should I
call your supervisor or mine?
And shoulders
will be slouching
in three, two, one.
This is like
fish in a barrel.
Good talk.
It's clean.
Hey, Happy.
Hey, Walt. How'd you guys do?
Oh, we got the drive,
but we need more evidence.
So how is the marina?
Informative.
I think I have
what you're looking for.
So, small crafts like Gostin's
have gas engines, right?
Their fumes have to be
cleaned out by a motorized fan
to avoid an explosion.
Now, if someone
were to cut the hose
between the motor and the fan...
Fan would still be making noise,
but it wouldn't actually
be blowing any fumes out.
Precisely. And if the fumes
aren't being vented, boom.
So, you found a cut fan hose?
Better.
Whoever cut the hose
on the congressman's boat
was smart enough to replace it.
They charred the outside
of the hose
so authorities wouldn't notice
it had been tampered with.
Trouble is, there should've
been fume residue inside.
But the hose is clean.
It's never been used.
It was clearly installed
after the boat exploded.
And a brand-new part
would mean a recent purchase.
So, we just need to link
whoever bought that part
to someone on the client roster
of Rebecca's firm.
Happy, we'll meet you
back at the garage.
Race you there.
Appreciate the loan.
What the hell
happened in here?
I can't believe this.
No. Proton Arnold.
They're onto us.
It's like a tornado
came through.
A tornado that hates computers.
And arcade games.
They took everything--
laptops, hard drives.
Surge protectors.
Who steals
surge protectors?!
It's a good thing our
standard operating procedure
is to heavily encrypt all data.
My house, your garage-- they're
hitting everything today.
Okay, so the question
is: why do all this?
Why not lay in wait
and then take the hard drive?
They know we have it
they'll be back for it.
We need to move.
Oh, God.
I know someplace.
Grab everything
you think you need.
We're heading out in 30 seconds.
Hold on, guys.
Cell phones.
On the desk now.
So they can't
be tracked.
Now, we're going off-grid,
but we still need phones. Happy?
I'm on it.
I want to pull Ralph
out of school.
Drew can take him
someplace safe.
That's smart.
It's better to be safe
than sorry.
Untraceable burners.
Great.
All right, let's move out.
This is Harriman Road.
We're going to
Jimmy's house.
Who's Jimmy?
No one for you
to worry about.
Uninhabited.
What's the story?
We needed off the grid.
That's the story.
Safe house? It's more
like a haunted house.
You see what I did there,
right? That's a joke.
My kind of key.
Ms. Quinn, would
you do the honors?
With pleasure.
There you go.
Oh, dear Lord,
thank you for this gift.
Paige, Sylvester, there's
a fuse box and a generator
in the cellar,
down the hall to the right.
Sure thing.
Oh, '97-- a fine vintage
for Dinty Moore.
Put that down!
You do understand
that we're hiding?
These people have
technology and connections.
If they want
to find us, they will.
We want to wrap
this up fast.
Happy, set up an untraceable
Internet connection.
Walter, what's
our plan of attack?
Well, we've got evidence of
the suspicious wire transfer
on the flash drive,
but we need to link it
to whoever bought
that hose.
Now, we'll dig into records
of every boat supply store
in southern California
and the top ten
online retailers.
Then, once
we have a list,
we can pull the name
of every Barnwright client
from that flash drive
and compare it
with the hose purchasers,
see if anyone overlaps.
Simple human error-- always is.
What is?
The transfer Rebecca saw
for "CA 78 SE"
was made on 11/12.
Safe money's on
a simple digit inversion.
Whoever entered that
meant to do it on 12/11.
After the congressman
was dead,
once that special
election had been set.
This whole thing is very
All the President's Men.
I feel like
I'm giving off
a real Robert Redford
vibe right now.
You're more of
a Dustin Hoffman.
I will take that.
We got an old saying
in law enforcement
about the criminal element:
"Thank God
they're stupid."
Um, start working
on this now.
There is no Jimmy, is there?
This is your house,
yours and Cabe.
How'd you know?
Coffee mug upside down
on a neatly folded paper
towel near the sink.
He does the same thing
every day at the garage.
And your hand
was just shaking.
It hasn't done once all day,
but it was just then.
He always said you were
the most observant person
he'd ever met.
Now, he lied
about the house
because he didn't
want us prying.
This is where...
things fell apart.
You don't want
to be here.
We'll work fast.
Walter...
You do understand
how important you are to him.
That's what that
was all about,
in the car earlier,
when he yelled at you.
He had the same look in his eyes
as he did when we were told
there was nothing more
we could do for Amanda.
He's not just worried
about me today.
He doesn't want
to lose you.
Walter!
List of Californians
who purchased
that exact model hose
in the last three months.
12 people total.
Now, 11 of those buyers paid
with credit or debit cards.
But none of those 11 names
have any direct ties
to Barnwright or
any of their clients.
So we're focusing on the
one cash transaction.
Okay, so that's got to be
our guy. What store?
Lake and Ocean Boat Supplies
in Marina Del Rey,
two weeks ago at 3:15.
Sylvester, can you access
their security archive footage?
On it.
This is her personal drive.
There's a lot more on here
than just the Barnwright file.
There's a folder
full of letters to you.
Multiple drafts,
going back almost 15 years.
I only read the first sentence,
when I realized what it was.
I thought you should
read it for yourself.
Checked up on your family.
But they made all
their appointments.
They're at
their hotel now.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
When we split up,
you let me have everything.
All you asked for
was this house.
Don't forget about
the '73 Le Mans.
I always assumed
you'd sell the place.
No, I'll never sell it.
This is where she took
her first steps.
This is where
she died.
It's killing
me to be here.
Right now, this is
the safest place.
I was so impressed
with you today.
I thought, there's
the man I married,
there's that swagger.
I feel safe.
But then... this.
It brought up all
these old feelings.
From when I couldn't
count on you.
Cabe. We got... something.
I'm fine.
I just need to
get some air.
Belongs to you.
Here's the archived footage
from the boat supply store.
Scanning the
date and time
- of when the pipe was purchased...
- Stop.
What's that?
There's our man.
Got him.
Does he pop up
in DMV records?
No, but he pops up
somewhere else.
Meet our buyer,
one Anthony Cole.
That name showed up
in the clients
I pulled from
Rebecca's flash drive.
Barnwright represents a
big agribusiness venture
called SunDorna Farms.
There's a Cole high
up in that company.
You are correct.
Ben Cole, VP of Operations
at SunDorna Farms.
Brother of the man
who purchased that hose.
But Anthony doesn't work
for the family business.
No, he's been working
on quite the record.
Theft, aggravated assault...
Hang on a second.
You just said "farm."
What...
this is about farms?
No, this is
about water.
It seems like the congressman
was a fierce defender
of small farmer water rights.
Defending them from what?
Big agribusiness,
like SunDorna.
They need the water, and Gostin
was trying to push through
a water redistribution bill.
He was gonna turn off the tap.
And at
stake for SunDorna?
More than $5 billion
in lost venue.
Less water, fewer crops.
Fewer crops, less money--
simple math.
Gostin was taking cash
out of their pockets,
so the company
and their lobbyists
just took matters
into their own hands.
And with Gostin dead,
and a more agreeable party
taking over
after a special election,
that water redistribution bill
will not pass.
SunDorna and
Barnwright make billions.
We've got our smoking gun.
We've I.D.'d the killers, we've
got the evidence to back 'em up.
We're going to the FBI.
Cabe!
No. No!
Yeah, they slashed
all eight tires.
Rebecca.
Catching up's gonna
be a challenge.
Maybe not.
Happy, come with me.
You got three minutes
to get her running!
All I need is a wrench.
Okay.
You three, go inside.
Track the vehicle.
Red sedan, four-door.
There's a strip of rust
on the trunk,
roughly four feet across.
We'll access the CalTrans
cameras and find the car.
How the hell
did they find us?
We were so careful.
We were.
Who knows what kind
of access they have?
Hey. Cabe.
Look at me.
We will find her.
Guys, what do you got?
Picture's up, Walt!
We've got a visual
on a ten-mile radius
around this house.
We're scanning for
that red car now.
We're about a mile
from half a dozen
freeway exchanges;
they could either be going
to the coast or the desert.
You got 45 seconds
to tell us if we're
heading north or south.
It's a whole mess
of cars out there.
It's really tough
to spot the red ones.
Try this: lay a color filter
over the video feeds.
Good idea.
Then we can highlight
the red cars,
make the kidnappers' car
easier to spot.
Nice.
Red station wagon.
Red V6 pickup.
Oh, come on, rusty
four-door, where are you?
Ooh, we got a live one!
Ah!
Red car,
rust patch on the trunk!
That's the one!
They're headed south
on the I-5. South!
Hang on.
They're passing
the Sylmar exit.
That's about five and a half
miles from here.
They're going faster
than I anticipated.
But just over the speed limit.
They don't want
to attract attention.
Just haul ass,
and you can catch up.
They'll kill her and bury her
where no one can find the body.
Cabe, that's not gonna happen.
We got 'em.
Think they see us?
Whoa!
Yes.
Cabe, they're turning off.
Hold tight, Walter!
Cabe?
Cabe? Cabe?
Cabe, wake up. Cabe!
Cabe!
Walter, are you guys okay?
Yeah. We're alive.
You still have eyes
on that car?
We lost visual
when they turned off
on Araiza Boulevard, eastbound.
Go get us a car.
What the hell?!
Homeland Security!
Sorry, it's a national
emergency.
Need to commandeer
your vehicle.
Come on. Sorry.
Let's go. Let's go.
Guys, can you slow them down?
Already done. Happy dropped
a railroad crossing arm
up ahead.
Traffic snarled
to a dead stop.
They'll want
to keep on moving,
and the only other option
is the service road.
But it's green all day,
so guaranteed
they're burning rubber.
Drive fast!
There they are.
Got to do something
to make them stop.
Rebecca in the car,
I can't risk taking a shot.
I'm thinking PIT maneuver.
You're thinking right.
Walter, do you know
how to do a PIT maneuver?
PIT: Precision
Immobilization Technique.
It's how the Highway Patrol
stops a fleeing car.
I've read about them
extensively.
Oh, my God!
You got this?
With a little help.
Happy, based on
the make and model,
how do I make their tires
lose their bead?
Just strike the bumper
at a 32-degree angle.
Ideal impact point?
15 inches from the back bumper,
while traveling
at approximately...
Oh, God.
68 miles an hour!
You ready?
Yeah.
You can do this.
Here we go.
Let me see your hands!
Get rid of that weapon!
Out of the car!
Get over here!
On your knees!
Hey.
Cabe.
How'd it go?
I'm a lawyer. I know my way
around a deposition.
What about the men
who took me?
Singing like the Beach Boys,
trying to cut a deal.
I can't wait to watch
that whole company go down.
Where's Walter?
Cleaning up.
He's a good young man.
The best.
You were tough on him today.
Yeah, well.
You were tough on all of them.
I'm sorry for
how I spoke to you earlier.
You have every right
to live, to grieve,
however you like.
I abandoned you after she died.
All those assignments overseas
that I said were mandatory,
I lied.
It's an ugly thing
that I live with.
Today I couldn't
bear the thought
of letting you down again.
Becca,
I know you've moved on,
but I have to ask you...
do you ever think about us?
You're the love of my life.
I've thought about you
for 15 years.
Tried to write you
a hundred letters.
But I think everything
happens for a reason.
I have to,
or I can't make sense
of what happened to Amanda.
Besides, I have
a family now.
So do you.
Sell the house.
Maybe someday.
You were always really badass.
Take care of him for me.
Okay.
You did right by her.
She's safe.
I always put my
job before her.
The real shame of it is:
the only thing I was ever really
better at than being a Fed
was being a father.
For what it's worth,
when I was young,
you were like a father to me.
Sometimes you still are.
Cabe!
It is a good thing
those jerks didn't
steal my blowtorch, or
they'd have a real problem.
Hey, Cabe,
I'm completing an inventory
of all purloined equipment;
and I expect the government
to compensate us in full.
Homeland will
foot the cost.
Okay, I'm gonna pad
this bill a little.
Ralph. Hey.
Thank you, pal.
They really messed
up the garage.
Yeah, they sure did.
You know, I'm gonna
have to rebuild this game.
Do you want to help me?
Yeah.
Okay.
Sit down.
Here, hold that.
Another time, Ralph.
Your mom says time
to start packing up.
How's it going?
What happened in here?
It was a high-stress day.
But that's behind us now.
Got it.
Then I'm not gonna bother you
about that thing
we talked about before.
I don't have an answer for you.
No, it's okay.
Yeah, I mean...
Ralph is my priority.
I'm just trying
to do right by the kid.
You and me both.
All right.
We, um... are gonna
get some food.
Do you want to join us?
Oh, um...
I'm-I'm not hungry, thanks.
Okay.
Bye.
Bye, Ralph.
I don't know about you,
but I could go for a burger.
Oh, I'm starving.
Sorry about your Le Mans.
Happy said
she'd fix it.
So what if there was
a scenario where, um...
Drew takes Ralph?
Takes him where?
Just a hypothetical.
To another city.
I wouldn't jump off
the bridge just yet.
There was a time when I wasn't
sure if I'd see you again.
Different circumstances,
of course, but... I had faith
that we'd meet
another day.
Appreciate what you said earlier
about me being a father to you,
even if it was said
in the heat of the battle.
Well, you know me.
When have I ever said
anything I didn't mean?
Good Burger.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net