My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
The tranquil landscapes
often praised here in Belarus
may soon give way to rolling
tanks and blasting mortars
as the century-long
border conflict with neighbors
Lithuania and Latvia
has reignited.
With each nation being pledged
military support
by respective allies,
Russia, China, Poland, Germany,
and the U.S.,
geopolitical experts fear
if a resolution
is not reached quickly,
all these countries
may soon be at war.
Flight 5-19,
LAX runway Bravo is clear.
Wind's one niner niner at two.
Permission to land.
Got an unregistered bogey, sir.
It's only 500 feet
below a 747 heading eastbound.
Establish contact immediately.
The hell?
It just... vanished.
I'm pretty sure
I just committed
at least three felonies.
And I've seen Shawshank.
I know what they do to guys
like me in the big house.
D Block prom queen.
That's it? It's gone?
It's still there.
I hacked the icon
and changed its color
so it blends in with the
background of the ATC monitor.
Basically,
I made it disappear.
Sudie.
That's Lithuanian for
“sayonara,” which is Japanese
for “good-bye.”
That plane will be
effectively invisible
when it lands
at your private airstrip.
I am still feeling
very uncomfortable with this.
It's deceptive.
Tensions are extremely high.
If the world knew that the
leaders from Belarus, Lithuania,
and Latvia were flying
to the U.S.
and no treaty was reached,
it could tip the entire region
over the edge.
I understand.
But historically, when
governments try to hide facts
from citizenry,
everyone winds up in hot water.
Oh.
You're still playing
with your toy?
This toy is three-dimensional
viz-surround
software technology.
Oh, it's-it's green screen.
It's been used
in Hollywood forever.
Wrong. It can be used
on a green screen,
but my software allows you
to take various images
from different sources
and layer them seamlessly
on top of each other.
Like Colorforms.
The kids' toy.
I didn't play with
kids' toys. Anyway,
even FBI video forensics
couldn't detect these images
as fake.
They're groundbreaking.
Good. Because
you're gonna need to fool a lot
of people today.
Oh, it will.
So, speaking of today,
did you see my analysis report?
Uh, yeah.
Okay. I know what you're doing,
so let me be more specific.
Did you read my report?
Come on. 25 pages
detailing the customs and
history of the three countries
who are meeting today.
It's important.
I understand.
But, uh, so is this,
and I just didn't
get around to it.
Uh, why did you write it anyway?
I never asked you to.
Well, truth is,
I'm taking night classes.
One's on European history.
Had a paper due. We had this
case coming up, so, you know,
I figured two birds,
one stone.
You dropped out of college.
I re-enrolled
to finish my degree, yeah.
Uh-huh. Why?
To learn,
for the betterment
of myself,
and to set a good example for Ralph.
I get that.
It's great
that you're pursuing education,
but why European history?
Liberal arts
are complete nonsense.
Oh, I couldn't disagree more.
The information that you receive
is strictly dependent
on the beliefs of whoever
authored the textbooks.
There are only four subjects
worth studying: science and math
and math and science.
Okay,
so when you meet the Lithuanian
president, what will you do?
I'll say hello and shake his hand.
Mm-hmm.
And that could be disastrous
because when you shake the hands
of a Lithuanian in the
threshold of a room,
it's considered insulting.
If the fate of civilization
rests on where we shake hands
with these people,
then we're all doomed.
Hey, Hopalong.
We're about to hop along,
so why don't you stop
watching that movie
for the 12th time?
This movie was filmed
on the senator's compound
where the summit's taking place.
I'm studying the layout
of the grounds
'cause some of the sets are
still standing on the property.
You already walked the
ground with Homeland.
You're a fanboy.
Next time, let your horse do
the thinking.
He's smarter.
They don't make classics
like this anymore.
Fanboy.
Hey, you got
a second?
What are you doing?
With what?
Hand, back.
Yours, mine.
Oh.
Sorry, I didn't
even notice.
Yesterday, you brushed
a leaf from my hair,
and on Tuesday
you laughed hysterically
at something I said.
How do you know
it wasn't funny?
I was reading a menu.
Pupu platter?
I can't help but feel
something's changed.
Are you referring to our kiss?
Don't...
say it.
Kiss.
Almost kiss.
It didn't happen.
Yet.
That's Lithuanian President
Dmitri Kreshenko and
his chief advisor Mikko Aleska.
Mikko's a big fella.
Over there is
Belarus President
Boris Sakovich
and his entourage,
and finally
Latvian President Juris Nikonov.
Th-That's actually
Latvian Prime Minister.
Their president's more
of a figurehead.
You didn't read
my report either.
All right,
let's get to work.
Director Merrick.
Ah, Ms. Munoz.
Cabe, this is
René Munoz,
Assistant Secretary,
State Department.
Since there's a good chance
that things could become
tense over the next few days...
I'm here to
keep these guys
away from each other's throats
and at the bargaining table.
Great. Right now we need
to get these men in front
of the green screens and
make it look like they're back
in their home countries
and not here.
Anything gets lost
in translation,
we'll reach out.
Understood.
Excuse me. René.
Uh, I wrote a report
on the historical customs
and traditions of these nations,
if this could be of any help.
Uh, thanks.
I'll refer to it
if I get in a jam.
Okay, cut!
What the hell
is he doing?
What are you typing?
Nothing. I'm pretending.
An eight-year-old
with a DVR can slo-mo this
and see every
keystroke.
If this does not
read as real,
then all of it
was a waste of time.
So can you please stop
pretending
and actually type something?
Thank you, sir.
Walter, you just need to...
Mr. President, you can type
whatever you'd like. We'll just
raise the camera an inch
so no one sees your fingers.
Is that acceptable?
Thank you, sir.
Okay.
What was that?
He was doing it wrong.
And over the next few days,
we'll need to make a half
dozen of these videos,
so I need to nip
bad habits in the bud.
Me, too.
So I'll be clear.
You do not talk to a president
like that.
And, you, you do not
talk to a president at all.
I was just trying to help.
Want to help?
Stay on the sidelines.
Is it just me, or does this feel
like a seventh grade dance?
I didn't go
to the seventh grade dance.
Me neither, but I imagine
this is what it was like.
Typical.
We sit here in silence
while neither of you are willing
to extend
the first olive branch.
We have all traveled
the same distance.
I do not hear
you making offers.
This summit was my idea.
That is my offer.
I suggest this a year ago.
Now it's your idea?
Gentlemen,
I respectfully submit
that we all follow the rules
of parliamentary procedure,
which we all agreed to
- prior to today.
- We also agreed
to no more military border
maneuvers.
And their army
has since positioned...
Hey, you know what?
Uh, I suggest
some honey mead.
What are you talking about?
Come on, gentlemen.
I know someone here brought
the mead.
How else would we toast
to peace when this
is all over?
Drinks are a good idea.
In these nations, you don't
fix emotional arguments
with rules of procedure.
You grease the wheel
with a tradition
old enough
that they all lay claim to it.
I want her off the grounds. Now.
Like hell.
She just did your job for you.
It's just pouring drinks, but
she's got them working together.
She stays.
Okay.
Raise your glasses.
Sveiks.
Mr. President!
Mr. Kreshenko!
I'll get the doctor!
Mr. President!
Mr. Kreshenko!
Mikko!
Whoa, whoa,
what are you doing?
I'm an MD. Shut up.
I need to hear his breathing.
Doc, what the hell's going on?
Well, he's been poisoned.
This is Dr. Chong.
He is a U.N.-certified physician
assigned to the summit.
You will all pay
for what you've done!
Yashin!
Hey, hey, hey!
Put down your weapons!
You're outmanned
and you're outgunned!
Now lower
your weapons!
Actually, uh, Cabe,
you're wrong.
The firepower is...
evenly matched.
If everyone were
to fire simultaneously,
then those two gentlemen
over there
would kill each other,
that Marine over there
would take out Yashin,
the falling bodies would
expose those behind them
to oncoming fire
from the other
Marines,
and we would wind up with--
excuse me-- three dead
security personnel
and three dead politicians.
Based on quick vector
and percentage
calculation,
almost 100% certainty.
Sylvester, how are my numbers?
Sounds pretty good to me.
It's actually four
dead politicians
if Kreshenko
isn't treated ASAP.
This was a setup!
You brought the bottle.
Sakovich poured it,
and Juris passed it out.
Everyone had access.
No one knows
what happened,
except somebody was
planning this all along,
and the mead was the
perfect opportunity.
Now, this man needs
medical care, stat.
No one goes in or
out of the grounds.
From here out,
everyone is
a suspect.
We're on lockdown.
Pulse is dropping significantly.
Heart rate's slowed to 42 bpm.
He's in bradycardia.
Whatever poison he's ingested,
it's taking hold.
I have adrenaline in my kit.
If I mix it exactly
with the atropine
and nifedipine,
that may buy some time.
How long?
Without an antidote?
This man will be dead
in 90 minutes.
We can't access
an antidote because
we don't know
what the poison is.
Things might get a lot worse
before they get better.
Paige, you did a good job
of calming things down earlier.
Go see if you can't
settle them down again.
I'm gonna go with her.
Maybe I can read
some guilt markers.
If we find the culprit,
we'll have a better chance
of figuring out
what was put in his drink.
Go.
We all know what happens
if word gets out
that there was
an assassination attempt
during furtive
peace talks.
Weaponry will be readied,
military strikes commenced.
And that'll be the start
of World War Three.
♪ Scorpion 1x18 ♪
Once Bitten, Twice Die
Original Air Date on March 9, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
I know this isn't good,
but do we really think
a world war can break out
from the death
of the president of the 89th
most populated nation
on the planet?
World War One
started because
of the assassination of
the Archduke Franz Ferdinand,
a man that 99% of the planet
had never even heard of,
so not only is
it possible,
but it's happened already.
We have to prevent these guys
from transmitting any
communications from this ranch.
We could piggyback on the Wi-Fi
to place our own virtual
local area network
around the entire compound.
Like a cyber noose.
We'll capture any e-mails,
texts, phone calls
from anyone on this property.
We can't let them know we muzzled them.
They won't.
They'll think their messages
are being received,
because Sylvester will respond
posing as
their associates.
Remember back at the garage
when I said I was
uncomfortable with deception?
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm.
Still uncomfortable.
Please, if you'll just...
Can you even read them
when you don't know
what they're saying?
Universal micro-tells
transcend language,
but they're politicians;
they're trained liars.
So I'm getting bubkes.
If they calm down,
I might be able
to pick up on something.
I think I have an idea.
Don't keep me in the dark.
What are you up to?
Mitzy Von Schneiden.
Singer from the 1920s
whose mother was Latvian,
dad was Lithuanian.
She studied in Belarus.
They all adore her.
And it's hard to keep
fighting when listening to
the lullaby
your mother used to sing you.
That's actually a good idea.
This song is beautiful.
If Kreshenko dies,
hopefully
a pill-naja-bura
doesn't keep us
from his funeral.
Oh, God.
Toby, I think I know
what was given to Kreshenko.
Cyber noose is trapping
a lot of e-mails
and text messages--
all to colleagues back home,
all of shock and dismay
at the poisoning.
Nothing nefarious here yet,
either.
Hopefully this will
keep his heart going
until we can determine
- exactly what we need to do.
- No!
What the hell?
Gallo...
What is your man doing?
That adrenaline would've
killed him instantly.
Paige. The... the dust storm.
Merrick, it all makes sense.
The guy from Belarus
whispered the words
pill-naja-bura.
That's “dust storm”
in Belarusian,
effectively a curse word
in the nation's history.
And it all started
with the venom from a snake.
In 1897, the
first war between
Belarus and Lithuania broke out
after what was deemed to be
blatant disrespect
by the Belarus government.
I don't need
a book report right now.
She actually has
some good ideas.
- Paige, go on.
- Okay, so,
the Lithuanian
president's child
died after being bitten
by a venomous snake,
and the Belarus diplomats
didn't show up for the funeral.
The excuse was that there was
this terrible dust storm.
But that excuse wasn't accepted,
and what followed
was a four-year war
and the tensions
we're still seeing today.
According to Paige,
the venom in the boy
caused an immediate
red spread, hives
in the arms and neck,
just like Kreshenko.
If the venom was given to him
as a symbolic “screw you,”
then that adrenaline
will make the venom work faster
and kill him instantly.
You know, Gallo,
you listening to these loons
is one thing,
but now you got the waitress
- calling the shots?
- Are we judging people
based on past resumes?
Because you were
a department store Santa to
help pay for your college.
How the hell
did you find that out?
Look, the point is, if we don't
get meds into Kreshenko
and he dies, it's our asses.
If you're wrong,
he'll die instantly.
Yeah, and if she's wrong,
then we had a chance
to save a president
and we didn't.
Debating this
wastes precious time.
Now, Paige,
it's up to you, okay?
How certain are you
of what you heard?
I'm 100% confident
in what I heard
and what I'm telling you.
Then there's our answer.
This is ridiculous.
I started a course
of treatment for this man.
I'm finishing the protocol.
Hey!
Are you out of your mind?
That was the only adrenaline
I had on site!
I trust my team.
The safe call
was to follow procedure.
And if he died, he died.
Now it's our necks.
I'm gonna arrest
President Sakovich,
but the lockdown
pertains to all of you.
Nobody leaves the grounds
until that man
is either saved
or he's dead.
'Cause I am not eating
this bullet alone
if this goes south.
Forget Homeland,
he should work for the Treasury
the way he passes the buck.
Focus. We have barely an hour,
and we don't know what kind
of venom we're dealing with.
There are
numerous deadly
Eastern European snakes,
several of which can cause
reddish hives.
Sly, Toby,
you figure out what kind of
Belarusian snake
we're looking for.
Happy, Paige, and I--
we'll go down to the reptile
sanctuary down the PCH.
Then when we get there,
you can tell us
what kind of snake
we need to procure.
Then we'll make an
antidote with its venom.
You heard Merrick.
No one's going anywhere.
I think I have a way
around that.
Zoom in,
camera one, north gate.
Someone's taking pictures.
Get Director Merrick.
Sir.
Oh, they bought it.
Great, just-just keep that
camera in front of your face.
Come and get me, dummies.
All corps
to the north gate. Now!
All right, come on. Hustle.
Where we going?
Right here.
Okay, hurry.
Okay, come on.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
Come on.
Cabe, I do not mean to rush you,
but if they come back here
and we're trapped...
It's in here somewhere.
DVD commentary on Blackrock
Shootout said they left intact
the secret door
the deputy used to escape.
Pays to be a fanboy.
All right, head east over that
hill; there should be a trail,
take you to a road.
Now go get us a snake.
See you later.
Come on, let's go.
Sir!
I checked the perimeter
from that bluff.
There's no sign of anyone,
not even vehicle tracks.
Well, he's got to be
here somewhere.
It's not like the guy
just appeared and disappeared.
Son of a bitch.
Hurry up.
I don't want any evidence
of what we've been up to.
Gallo!
You two, get out.
Ooh, Cabe's in trouble.
Do you have Stockholm syndrome?
Just do whatever
these eggheads say?
What you did is insubordination,
borderline treason.
I made a choice
to save a man's life.
No, you made a choice to
defy me and to back them.
You don't work as closely
with Scorpion as I do.
You just don't know
how they go about things.
I know that you've
been mesmerized
by this kid Walter from
the minute you met him.
I'm no more mesmerized by him
than you are threatened.
And our job is
to protect people,
Now, let me ask
you a question.
You think that you and Walter
would be such great pals
if he knew what really
happened in Baghdad
with that software
you had him make?
What if I tell him?
Let me be clear.
What Walter knows
and what he needs to know
is up to me.
If you disclose anything to him,
you and I will have a problem
where rank doesn't
come into play.
Do you copy?
Not sure where we are,
but I know it's nowhere
near the reptile sanctuary.
Now what?
Hitchhike?
I'm not showing leg.
No, there's no time
to hitchhike.
Happy, I hear a truck. Quick.
Punch me in the nose.
Finally.
Good job.
What is he doing?
Hey! Hey!
Hey, man, you okay?
Not really. I was hiking,
and I fell on my face.
Have you got any ice?
Some ice? Yeah, yeah, sure.
Come around back.
Okay.
Hey.
Come on in.
Thanks.
Here's your ice.
Thank you. Also, sorry.
What's up?
Hit it, Happy!
We'll return it!
Official government business!
Okay, so we get
to the reptile sanctuary...
find the curator,
have him get us the right snake.
Yeah, what are we gonna do?
We gonna tell him someone
we know, but can't disclose,
has been bitten
by a deadly snake
that may or may not be native
to this area,
and he just has to trust us
and give us that snake,
even though venomous snakes
are regulated by the state,
and giving us one
could land him in prison?
Oh, you got a better idea?
We steal the snake.
This is a violation
of the Geneva Convention.
So is assassination.
You pig!
I will kill you
for what you've done!
Now, I told you once,
you keep cool,
or I'll cuff you
right alongside these men.
There are too many
Belarusian snakes.
There's no way
to know which one it is.
Is that what you're gonna
tell Walter when we call him?
I don't know anything
about snakes.
This wasn't even my idea.
Ah, ah,
there's no “I” in Scorpion.
It's a figure of speech.
Oh.
Cyber noose just got another
text. This one's from Mikko.
I'm putting it
in the translator now.
“Everything is in place,
moving forward”?
I don't like the sound of that.
You know, it's ambiguous.
It could mean nothing.
The man's president is dying.
He's not gonna send
an international text
to someone that means nothing.
That's ambiguous on purpose,
but it means something.
What?
You think Mikko could be the one
who slipped his boss a mickey?
The text was meant
for someone named
Eras Ilgauskas,
and a quick search shows that
he's a wealthy manufacturer in
artillery production
and distribution.
You think Mikko could be
in the weapons game with him?
That would explain
why he did something that could
cause World War Three.
If Kreshenko signs that peace
treaty, then there's no war,
and if there's no war,
there's no weapons to sell.
We arrested the wrong guys.
And we're looking for
the wrong type of snake.
Killer's not from Belarus.
We need something from
the Lithuanian region.
That's where Mikko's from.
And there's only one snake
that matches our specific
set of symptoms.
The adder.
Toby says we got the wrong guys.
It was Kreshenko's advisor.
The snake we're looking for
is the adder.
I hacked
the sanctuary's schematics.
The best route to the snake is
the side employees' entrance.
Once in, to avoid security,
you're gonna have
to use the cross beams
above the displays.
I didn't design
the building, man.
We can still communicate
within the cyber noose,
so we need to
respond to his text.
There's no way Mikko doesn't
expect to hear back from him,
a co-conspirator in
an assassination.
If he doesn't, he'll get suspicious.
What do I say?
Uh, needs to be ambiguous,
as well.
Just confirmation of receipt.
That's what they
would've planned.
Okay. How about “Thank you”?
Sure.
Why don't you put a thumbs up
emoticon at the end of it, too?
Just send “Confirmed”"
No. Send... “Okay”"
No! Send “Okay.
Confirmed”"
You're confusing me.
Just send “Confirmed”"
That's it.
Just send that.
Sent. You think he'll buy it?
Yeah.
Unless they had a specific
code word planned in advance.
Yeah.
Let's go tell Cabe
we got our guy.
I think they had a code word.
Is that him?
No. That's the running
of the bulls in Ventura.
Yes, it's him!
Okay.
What do I do?
You are
the computer experts, no?
No.
We dabble.
Give me your phone.
Easy, Mongo.
I know you texted me!
Hit him, Sly!
Okay!
Hit him! I got him!
Stop! U.S. Marine!
He's the assassin!
Got eyes on him!
Are you okay, Sly?
What the hell happened?
You guys all right?
It was Mikko.
He framed
those Belarus boys.
Big guy's fast.
Welcome, gang.
Got a lot of neat stuff
to see and learn today,
so head on in.
Just follow
these footprints.
Excuse me, sir.
Can you help me?
I am the teacher's assistant
with this class,
but I... I'm so terrified
of snakes, and I was...
C-Can you stand
with me during
your presentation,
please?
Please?
Um, sure, yeah.
I won't leave your side
if you don't want me to.
Oh, thank you.
You're such a smart,
brave man.
I'm so lucky to have someone
like you looking after me.
How long
have you worked here?
Your friend better get back here
with that venom soon.
He's almost gone.
Happy,
am I getting any closer?
All I can see are
a bunch of turtles.
Hang a left.
Okay.
Got snakes?
Mm, yeah, getting there.
You okay?
Sure.
Are you scared of snakes?
Oh, no.
Walter, I've seen you
diffuse a bomb.
That risk was calculable.
You cannot predict
what a wild animal will do.
I'm just gonna reach down,
scoop up the snake
and then get out.
Limited risk.
I will be fine.
Okay, you have to make sure
you don't harm the snake
when you retrieve it.
Do you want to change places?
- Hell no. Those things are deadly.
- Okay, kids.
If I could have everybody
at this window over here.
If everyone stays quiet,
I can tell you about
the over 40 breeds of venomous
snakes that we have here.
Now, many of these snakes
come from
a tropical, wet climate,
but since SoCal is a desert,
who would like to make
our snakes feel more at home?
Me! Me!
You certainly look
like a snake lover.
Press that little red button
and see what happens.
I don't have
a good feeling about this.
You made it rain!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Let's make our way to the exit, kids.
Call security!
Walter.
Okay. Not good.
Oh, boy. A deadly snake.
Walter, don't move.
Okay.
We need a tan snake with a
zigzag pattern along its back.
I think that's the one, the
one that's near your business.
Guys.
There's a tan snake
with a different zigzag pattern
in this tree.
Which one do we want?
How the hell should I
know? I'm a mechanic.
Can we try and capture
both of them, make antidotes
out of both venom,
see which one works?
No. There is barely enough time
to make one antivenom.
I have an idea.
Uh, are you doing
- what I think you're doing?
- What?
Wait. Walter,
what are you doing?
Walter,
what are you doing?!
Process of elimination
is our most efficient
path.
Come on, come on, come on.
Whoa!
Crap.
I think we've got
the right snake.
Okay, move.
Watch the snake.
What the hell is
the plan here?
To make an antidote,
we need a host
to inject a little bit
of venom into, not enough to
kill it, but enough to develop
antibodies. There.
That's our host.
Yeah.
I'm on it.
One ferret coming up!
Oh, no.
Yep.
Ah! Come on!
Don't be stingy!
Okay, I think I got enough.
Uh, yeah. I got enough.
How are you still functioning
while Kreshenko's
barely alive?
Because I'm younger.
But we have to get back
to the ranch fast. Happy.
Hey, I'm doing 90 in a burrito
truck. Cut me some slack.
Okay, hold him still.
Wait, is this gonna hurt him?
I'm so glad
that you're concerned
about the ferret.
I'm sorry.
Okay, buddy.
Help me out here.
Next time...
let your horse do the thinking.
He's smarter.
Freeze!
Stop right now!
Stop the vehicle!
Halt!
Lower your guns.
We're the Homeland guys.
We've got an antidote.
Okay. Come on, Walt.
We're almost there.
Careful on those steps, Happy.
There's taco grease!
Oh, no.
What did you do?
I dropped the ferret.
Oh, he does not look good.
The fuel quotients for
the rockets are off.
He's rambling.
He's delusional.
He's in bad shape.
Walter, what the hell
were you thinking?
The antibodies are
in the host organism.
What host organism?
I slipped on taco grease
getting out of the van,
and when I fell, the ferret
with the venom got away.
That's the first time
anyone has ever said that.
I got to go help
Happy find him.
Paige, I'm sorry. I...
What?
I'm sorry.
I had reservations.
Reservations about what?
I-I never took you to dinner.
Whoa, little sucker's fast.
What am I supposed to do
with this thing?
Oh, no. Really?
I need
a high-speed centrifuge
to separate out the antibody
from the ferret blood.
Yeah, Walter must've had
a plan here.
Walter's not talking
right now, Toby.
Okay, okay...
They're dead men.
They're going to die.
Let me think, okay?
What is there to think about?
I'll just inject them with ferret blood,
without processing it.
Million-to-one shot but
what choice do we have?
No, you're not taking
a million-to-one shot
with my friend's life,
you understand?
You go near him
with that ferret,
I'm gonna cram that furry
little dude up in a place
it can never run away from.
You follow?
We just need to separate
the antibodies from the plasma.
Somehow simulate
a high-speed centrifuge.
You came here
in a taco truck, right?
Okay.
Oh!
Salad spinner! Let's go.
All right, come on!
Okay. Now we wait.
Even if we save
Kreshenko,
these guys are so
distrustful of one another,
they'll never sit
down and negotiate.
Well, then we'll have
to figure out a way
to motivate them
to want to.
How'd we do?
Walter.
How are you feeling?
Oh, terrible.
But, uh, worse
now that I've seen this.
So Kreshenko died,
word got out,
and now we're off
to a decade
of death and destruction?
Not exactly.
Are they...
Signing a
peace treaty?
You bet they are.
We showed them what would happen
if they didn't.
Come with me.
I'll show you.
Gallo,
I know today was rough
and we went at it,
but you got the ball
into the end zone.
I won't forget
what you did.
And you threatened to
disclose something to Walter
I don't ever
want shared.
I won't forget
what you did, either.
Both sides are set
to start pulling back
heavy weapons on Tuesday
to create a buffer zone
of up to 140 kilometers.
You used my software.
Old footage
of Lithuanian tank maneuvers
laid over border territories
they have never
been near before.
Soldiers disembarking tanks,
except we put them
near the disputed boundaries.
Images over images.
Like Colorforms.
The United States and Germany
have promised ground troops
immediately, a move the Russian
government has called
an act
of direct aggression.
She's using my voice dubbing software.
No.
Actually, the British accent's
Happy's real voice.
She's been lying to us
the whole time.
We just spliced the
wiring of our broadcast
to the satellite dish on the
roof, so now everybody thinks
they're watching the real news.
That is fantastic work, guys.
Just call us
the Ghosts of Christmas Future.
We scared the hell out of them.
They ran
to the bargaining table.
So, uh, what happens when they
get back and find out the truth?
What are they gonna say?
That a bunch of schmucks
who work out of a garage
outsmarted them?
Those guys want
to get re-elected.
♪ ♪
Where is it?
Doc.
Come here a minute.
What's up?
When you grabbed that doctor
and put him in his place,
it was hot.
Um...
thank you for that...
Shh.
Just don't talk.
Don't ruin it.
Okay.
Why's it smell like seawater?
I formulated, uh,
an electrolyte solution.
It's more efficient
than the market brands.
It tastes, um...
disgusting.
Taking that bite today
was crazy.
I know we go down a lot of
dicey roads, but that was...
It was necessary.
War was imminent.
Still, I don't like you taking
that kind of risk.
Noted.
You look like you're going
to say something.
You kept it?
He saved my life.
Least I could do
is save it from becoming a...
snake's lunch.
Toby named it Ferret Bueller.
I don't understand
the reference.
I need my
history textbook.
I'm already late
as hell!
And I don't understand
why she didn't tell me
she was taking a night class.
You, this group,
it's a lot to compete
with academically.
She knows
there's no reason to compete.
And that
she can't compete.
Just like we can't compete
with her
in so many regards.
So... why keep
that hidden?
There's a million reasons
why people keep secrets.
Sometimes we just
can't understand.
No! No, no!
What's the problem?
Busted water main on Sunset.
Traffic's gridlocked.
There's no way
I'll make my final.
I'm gonna flunk.
I need a favor.
Oh, my God, I made it.
This is amazing.
Seven minutes to spare.
I-I didn't have a chance
to cram today.
I know you think this stuff
is nonsense, but...
I'm nervous.
You outshined and impressed
a seasoned
diplomatic envoy today.
So if you can do that,
you can crush the test.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you, Walter.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net