My name is Walter O'Brien.
I have the fourth highest IQ
ever recorded: 197.
Einstein's was 160.
When I was 11, the FBI
arrested me for hacking NASA
to get their blueprints
for my bedroom wall.
Now I run a team of geniuses,
tackling worldwide threats
only we can solve.
Toby's our behaviorist.
Sylvester's a human calculator.
Happy, a mechanical prodigy.
Agent Cabe Gallo's
our government handler.
And Paige?
Well, Paige isn't like us.
She's normal
and translates the world for us
while we help her understand
her genius son.
Together, we are Scorpion.
Hello!
Merry Christmas Eve, everybody.
Wow.
Black Sabbath instead of
“White Christmas”?
No way. Okay, we're all getting
into the Christmas spirit.
You know, we're kind of busy.
Shocker. That's why I'm
bringing the celebration here.
Tonight, we're going
to have dinner together.
And yes, you have
to help decorate.
So, Ralph's a
little disappointed.
Drew had to head to Portland--
last-minute tryout
for a minor league team.
TOBY Wow.
Missing Christmas
with his son.
That doesn't sound like him.
No, wait.
That sounds exactly like him.
Drew wasn't happy
about it, but they wanted to see
him throw before the manager
left for vacation
or something.
Anyway, I want to soften
the blow for Ralph.
Tree, lights, Santa.
Gonna give him everything
this Christmas except for snow.
Uh, news flash.
Ralph doesn't believe in Santa.
You can be a genius
and still believe
in things that are magical.
Oh, speaking of... Santa,
I have your gifts.
Happy, Paige got us gifts.
You didn't get me anything,
did you?
No problem. Happy.
Sylvester.
And Toby.
Oh.
I miss my hat.
It's on a cliff
somewhere in Bosnia.
Uh, this wrench
isn't functional.
They're ornaments.
Now all we need is a tree.
And I can't figure out
what to get Walter.
What do you get somebody
with a 197 IQ?
Definitely not this stuff.
Okay.
I could have built
a better robot when I was five.
I did build a better robot
when I was five.
Well, thank you for the gifts, Paige.
Sure.
You know, before my parents
shipped me off
to live with my uncle,
my dad bought me a weight set
for Christmas.
Which is crazy because
I'm big, not strong.
Uh, try a foster home
Christmas.
They'd send me back
to the state
a week earlier so they wouldn't
have to get me a present.
Do any of you have
good Christmas memories?
I loved Christmas.
My dad would wake me early,
and we'd rush downstairs.
Okay, now we're talking.
Then we'd head straight
to off-track betting.
It was magical.
The whole gang
would be there--
Timmy No Shoes,
Smelly Jim, Pooter.
They taught me
how, on Christmas,
you never bet the two
or the five horse.
Nags put there for
superstitious suckers
betting on the twenty-fifth.
Best of all, by the
time we got home,
my mom would be passed out
on the couch from the eggnog.
That was.. that was almost worse
than Happy's.
I've-I've never heard people
so jaded about Christmas.
I mean,
who thinks that way?
While Christmas has zero impact
on me personally,
it does provide people
with, um, psychological uplift,
thus making workers
more productive,
so the holiday
does have value.
The point is to
be with family.
That's what we're doing.
Eating Fat Burger?
It's not exactly
a holiday meal.
Yours has bacon. That's
practically Christmas ham.
That is just sad.
Hmm.
Excuse me. Hi.
The wind's not striking the sail
with enough velocity.
This produces insubstantial
pressure on the face, and,
consequently,
not enough upward thrust
to counterbalance gravity.
Got to turn your kite.
Here.
Thank you.
Oh.
How'd you know that?
I know a few things.
Did you know
that Ben Franklin-- he...?
He discovered electricity
by flying a kite.
No. If his kite
had actually been struck
by lightning,
the key would have
electrocuted him.
It's just a myth.
- I like the way you think, kid.
- Owen,
leave the poor man alone.
- Oh.
- Okay.
Merry Christmas.
Yeah.
Do you think it's ironic
that Mom got you a kite
for Christmas,
and you never used it?
Oh, that's,
uh, not irony.
That's her
not understanding me.
Yeah. You were never into
the holiday, even as a kid.
It's because
I had more important things
to occupy my time,
like the Rohaxinal study.
I pulled
some favors.
You're in.
I...
I don't want
to be a guinea pig.
Well, that drug has
some serious side effects.
It could save your life.
You've seen
the test results, Walt.
At this point,
I don't need a new drug.
I need a miracle.
There is no such thing!
All right, do know how
Jonas Salk cured polio?
With science, not by singing
about snowmen and reindeer.
Well, sometimes you need
a little faith.
I do have faith,
just in things that are real.
Are we having an earthquake?
It's a rock slide.
Owen!
Help!
He's trapped!
Oh, my God.
Owen's down there!
Wait. Down where?
He was in the cave, and the
bluff just started to come down.
Owen! Owen!
The ground just
opened up.
He fell in. It happened so fast.
Owen! What do you mean,
the ground just opened up?
It's a sinkhole.
Rock slides often start
with small seismic shifts
at ground level.
It's common in California.
It can cause
a small, spontaneous hole,
especially in sand.
Oh, my God!
He's buried alive!
No, no, no.
Not necessarily.
Sinkholes very rarely self-fill.
There's a good chance he's stuck
in a hollow right now.
We need the L.A.
Fire Department,
Army Corps of Engineers,
anyone that can help.
Copy that. But who
the hell are you?
I'm with Homeland.
I know some people.
We can help.
Touch it, and you will have
a blue Christmas.
I helped, too.
Walter designed it, Sylvester
calculated it, I built it.
What was your job?
Moral support.
Toby,
a few weeks ago,
I was in a hospital
getting shrapnel
taken out of my chest,
and I still did more work
for this project than you did.
Grinch.
Hey, guys,
Walter just called.
There's a ten-year-old
boy trapped in
a sinkhole at Zuma Beach.
Let's go.
Zuma Beach is on high alert,
as a ten-year-old boy is trapped
one and a half stories
below the earth's surface.
Walter!
We have seen emergency
crews arriving on scene...
Yeah?
We were listening
to the news on the way here.
Okay. We'll start off by
getting you up to speed.
This is Dan Heather,
Army Corps of Engineers,
Geotech Division. Dan?
Mind filling my guys in?
Those boulders up here
are blocking access to the boy.
He's trapped in a sinkhole
14 feet deep underground here.
If we use heavy machinery
to move them,
ground shifts will cause
the sinkhole to collapse,
which means
we have no way to reach him.
Oh, my God.
But it gets worse.
We can't get in,
but water can.
There are gaps
between those rocks.
Waves are dumping down 30
gallons of seawater per minute.
We're putting sandbags
to restrict the flow,
but tide is too strong.
The hole is filling up fast.
Dimensions of the hole?
Best guess: 1,100 cubic feet.
Taking into account
the water displacement
due to an average-sized
ten-year-old boy, he will drown
in one hour and 22 minutes.
You can't drill
to him before then?
A CalTrans team offered
to help.
They have the right drills, but
the sand is incredibly unstable.
Normally, we'd drill
at a steep angle,
but that could cause a cave-in,
killing him instantly.
Instead, we're digging at a
shallow angle, farther away.
But progress is slow.
Doesn't help, this
entire bluff's unstable
and could re-slide at
any time, burying him.
Follow me.
Where's his parents?
Driving back
from up north.
Bringing his grandparents
back for Christmas.
Babysitter's trying
to get ahold of them.
Speaking of communication,
we need a way to talk to Owen,
find out his exact location.
So you don't drill through the
sinkhole wall and impale him.
That's right.
We considered flying in
a high-tech sound wave device
from Nellis Air
Force Base, but...
Even an HH-60
helicopter
with a top speed
of 195 knots
wouldn't get here
for another 86 minutes,
and that's four minutes after
the hole would be full of water.
The sinkhole is in there,
under that rock.
No way the kid can hear us.
No. I've got a way.
Okay, Walter,
I really don't feel
comfortable being in
a cave that was formed
by a rock slide that happened
less than an hour ago.
Oh, no.
Guys, okay,
Owen is right under there.
But we can't dig a rescue tunnel
this close to Owen, but CalTrans
can auger an eight-inch
diameter tunnel
at a 75 degree angle.
Small enough not
to compromise the sinkhole.
Use a collapsible mast drill
bit so if it accidentally
hits the kid's body, it'll
retract without major injury.
In this soft sand,
they'll reach
him in minutes.
We need a PVC pipe.
I saw some on the
CalTrans truck.
Okay, how do we
communicate with Owen?
Do you have some kind
of high-tech device?
As a matter of fact, I do.
Pipe is secure.
If he's alive, we can
send scuba gear down
so he can breathe when
the water gets too high.
All right. Get that there.
Let me see this.
Come on, Owen.
Come on.
Hello?
Hey.
Owen. Owen.
My name's Walter O'Brien.
I helped you with your kite.
Me and my friends
are here to help you.
- Please, get me out of here.
- We're working on it
now, okay, but it's gonna
take some time.
Where are my mom and dad?
I want my mom and dad.
We're trying to
reach out to them.
Put him on mute
for one second.
That rapid breathing
and confusion--
if he goes into shock, he could
pass out and slump down.
And there's already enough water
in there that he'll drown.
We need to keep him calm.
Walter! I got
his parents.
Uh, Owen?
Owen, we got your parents
on the phone, okay?
Hold on a sec. Hi.
Uh, now I'm gonna hold the phone
up so your son can hear you.
Okay.
Owen, can you hear me?
Dad! I want to go home.
I know you do.
We'll be there soon.
Where are you?
Sweetheart, it's Mom.
We're coming, baby.
We're driving as fast as we can.
The phone's dying.
We don't have a charger.
Owen, listen, we don't
have a lot of time to talk.
Don't hang up!
I love you so much, baby.
Son, we're gonna
get cut off soon.
Please, don't be afraid.
We're gonna get to you,
and when we do,
Mommy and I are gonna
hold you, sweetie,
and we're never gonna let you...
Dad? Dad!
Phone's dead.
Guys, remember what I said
about keeping him calm. Paige.
Owen.
My name is Paige. I'm a mom.
I have a ten-year-old son, too.
Can I sit in for your parents
until they get here
and just talk to you?
It's almost Christmas.
Do you decorate
your-your tree with, um,
candy canes
and ornaments?
My dad strings popcorn.
We do, too.
We make a super long one, and
we wrap it all the way around.
Hey, he's doing better.
Keep going.
What else do you do
for Christmas?
We... we watch Christmas movies.
Yeah?
Something's off
with his breathing.
Hey, Owen!
Listen, I'm a doctor.
Tell me, does your chest hurt?
Yeah.
I hit a rock when I fell.
Oh. Uh, would you mind
looking up for me?
Ah, thanks, buddy.
Listen, you're doing great.
Just hold on one second, okay?
I put him on mute.
He-he has distended neck veins.
That's sign of a pneumothorax,
a collapsed lung.
It's probably from a broken rib
piercing it; but we cannot
use that scuba gear.
The compressed air
will kill him.
And that's gonna be a problem.
Because...
I just realized
I didn't account
for the tidal changes
when I calculated
how long it was going to take
for Owen to be submerged.
I made a big mistake.
I'm so sorry.
What's the adjustment?
We don't have an hour
and 22 minutes to save him.
If we can't get him
out of there,
he's going to drown
in 56 minutes.
Tension is building
here at Zuma Beach,
as we have learned
that ten-year-old Owen Cooper
has less than an hour until
he's completely underwater.
Rescue crews are tunneling in
in an attempt to reach him
and hopefully get him out
in time.
We need this
done now!
Going as fast as I can.
There's no other option?
No.
Walter.
Owen, we're gonna drill to you
and lift you out, okay?
Just hang tough.
- You can't.
- We can.
Our team's handled
challenging situations before.
No. You can't lift me.
I'm stuck.
What do you mean?
A rock has my leg pinned down.
Okay, just point the phone
at your leg, please.
Rock looks to be
a couple hundred pounds.
Even if we get there
before he's submerged,
how the hell do we get
that rock off of him?
I'm cold.
Please get me out of here.
Please!
We're gonna figure this out.
Everything's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna talk
to the fire department.
I'm scared.
I know, honey.
And you're doing so great.
You... I'm so proud of you.
Let's talk about
something nice, okay?
Um... do you like
Christmas books?
My son Ralph's, his favorite is
I Want an Alien for Christmas.
I know that book.
You do? Great.
What's your favorite part?
Paige?
Could I die in here?
Owen...
the people helping you
are special, okay?
They won't let that happen
to you.
Fire department is proposing
a last-ditch idea.
It's not pleasant.
Amputate his leg?
We can't. The vibrations
from the bone saw
would collapse the sinkhole.
We're up against the one thing
humans have never been able
to defeat: time.
When half a million kids a year
were contracting polio,
you think Jonas Salk
felt like you do?
But when he hit
a wall, he shoved it
out of the way
and he kept going.
I have faith in a lot
of things, Walter,
but I especially have faith
in you.
You're right.
In-Instead of thinking
about how to move Owen's leg,
we should be thinking
about how to move the wall.
Or, in this case, the boulder.
Thank you!
Here, Paige, Paige, Paige.
Owen? Owen?
I'm gonna go off Skype
for a minute
to take a look at that video
I recorded of your leg.
Don't go!
It's just gonna take 60 seconds.
No!
Owen, I-I want you
to start counting,
and when you get to 60,
I promise we're gonna be
right back together, okay?
You can do this.
I'll-I'll get
started. Ready?
One, two,
three...
Four, five, six...
Good.
You have 54 seconds.
Then I take that tablet back.
Okay, we need
a device small enough
to fit through
that tiny crack,
but powerful enough
to lift that rock.
As soon as they're done digging,
we'll bring in a car jack.
Car jack's
a brute tool.
We need
something sensitive enough
to exert the exact amount
of force required.
The rocks are so unstable.
We disturb them too much,
one will collapse
after the other, like dominoes.
It'll crush him.
The boulder appears
to be approximately
40 inches high.
We need to raise it
between 1.8 and 2.3 inches.
Any less, we won't free his leg.
Any more, the whole sinkhole
could collapse.
1.8 or 2.3?
Sylvester, that's almost
a-a 28% differential.
It's the best
I can give you right now.
Sylvester, we need...
we need better.
What is wrong with you today?
Get your head on right.
HAPPY Uh, we need something
like a micro-jack.
I could build one with
parts I have at the garage.
It'll go faster
with help.
I'll go with you.
What's the use
if this kid's underwater by the
time they bring back this jack?
I've already accounted for that.
For Owen to stay alive,
he needs to stop breathing.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'll explain on the way.
Come on.
♪ Scorpion 1x12 ♪
Dominoes
Original Air Date on December 15, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Walter O'Brien, Agent Gallo,
we've been expecting you.
The ECMO machine
you requested.
This isn't 40 feet.
We thought you said 14 feet.
No, 40 feet.
Now.
Walter, they're just trying
to help, too.
Find me a U-channel wedge,
a quarter-inch thread drive rod,
a reinforced shoulder bolt,
and three steel lid stays.
I don't understand
half of what you said.
Then start with the other half.
Prepping the kiln.
Uh... got
the wedge,
uh, drive rod, and...
shoulder bolt.
You know more than you let on.
I watch you work sometimes.
Thank you
for making this creepy.
Now find the other parts.
Is it gonna hit me?
It shouldn't.
It won't.
Just lean as far back as you
can, Owen. You can do this.
It's tight in there.
This isn't a science.
God help this kid.
Stop the drill!
All right, guys, I'm gonna
back this bad boy out of here.
Come on. Let's move!
We need some men up here! Now!
Okay, we got it here,
but explain how this helps us.
We need to keep Owen alive
until the jack gets here,
but that's not gonna be
until he's underwater.
So we need to bypass
his respiratory system,
which is what this is for.
It's an extracorporeal
membrane oxygenation system,
or an ECMO.
Where'd you learn how to do this?
On the Internet.
He's not kidding.
Okay, so...
we get the tubes and needles
in the PVC pipe, and then...
Hold on.
We haven't even
started putting supports
in the tunnel
we just dug.
Until that's done,
it's unstable,
and the risk of collapse
is substantial.
I need exact probabilities.
I can't give them.
Okay, I know someone who can.
Come with me.
Paige, tell my mom I'm sorry.
Why is that, honey?
She told me not-not to go
in the caves, but...
I wanted to find
the pink shells,
the ones she likes.
Owen...
It's my fault.
This is not your fault.
It's my fault!
Paige!
Where's Sylvester?
I need him to work out
some odds for me.
I have no idea, but this child
is starting to break.
I don't know
how much longer
he's gonna last down there.
And it kills me,
but the tunnel is not stable.
And neither is Owen.
That's it. I'm going in.
Absolutely not.
None of my men, not the LAPD
or the fire department--
no one has been given
authorization to go down
until the tunnel
is ready.
I don't work for
any of those entities.
I don't need
your authorization.
Hopefully, I'll see
you in five minutes.
Hopefully.
If not,
who would've thought
I'd be the one to outlive you.
Okay, you guys
man the ECMO.
I'll take care
of the rest.
As this saga
at Zuma Beach continues
to unfold, Walter O'Brien,
a freelance contractor
with Homeland Security,
is heading down into the earth
in what can only be described
as a very risky endeavor.
Owen! Hold on!
I'm coming for you!
Owen!
Owen.
It's Walter.
Can you hear me?
The water's getting higher!
Hold on!
I'm almost to you!
Hurry.
Please get me out of here.
Okay.
You've handled
this so well.
You've impressed me;
it's hard to impress me.
Now, my friends
are working
on a device to free your leg,
so I will get you out of here.
Now, you will be with your
parents for Christmas, okay?
Okay. Okay.
But I won't be able to free you
before the water covers
your head.
I-I don't understand.
Well, you have to trust me.
I found a way
for you to stay alive
without ever taking a breath.
All right?
Send it down!
Owen, there's a machine up top.
It'll take the blood
from your body,
add oxygen to it,
and then send it back
into your blood, okay?
It's used in surgeries. Only
you're special 'cause you'll...
you'll be the first person
to ever do it while conscious.
We've been able to jump
on the rescuers' Wi-Fi signal,
and we can now watch this
incredible drama unfold live.
Give me your arms.
You're gonna feel a pinch
when I insert these needles.
It's like a shot at the doctor,
only deeper, okay?
One, two, three.
I know this hurts,
but you're doing great.
Give me the other arm.
All right. Okay, okay.
They're in.
Can't believe this is working.
I know from our Ben Franklin
conversation that you're smart,
so I'm gonna explain
something to you
that I know that
you'll understand.
In less than one minute, we're
gonna be completely underwater.
Your primordial brain
will tell you to breathe in.
You cannot.
No matter how badly
you want air, do not breathe
in once you're under, okay?
That's how people drown.
It's not gonna be easy,
but I know you can do it.
I need to breathe!
No, no, no.
Look at me,
look at me.
You need oxygen.
And these tubes
will bring it to you.
You just have faith
that the science will work.
I can't live underwater.
Yes, you can.
We all have-- in the womb,
w-when we were
surrounded by fluid
and oxygen got to us
without us even breathing.
That's all this is.
Okay? Now, I'm gonna
stay with you,
I'm gonna hold your hand
as long as I can.
And then it's
up to you.
When I go up, I want you
to count to 15,
and then knock on the pipe
so we know you're okay.
After I get the jack
to free your leg,
I'm gonna be
right back down here.
Okay?
Yeah.
So what are you gonna do?
Knock on the pipe.
Okay. Are you gonna breathe?
No.
You promise me?
I promise.
You promise you'll come back.
I promise you
I will come back.
And I only state facts.
It cut out.
Remember, go against
your instinct
and do not breathe in.
Okay.
I will come back for you.
I promise.
How long has it been?
Too long.
After going underground
in an incredible attempt
to keep Owen Cooper alive,
everyone is waiting, praying,
for heroic civilian
Walter O'Brien to emerge
from the tunnel with news
of the child's condition.
There he is!
Are you okay?
Has he signaled yet?
I got a cop
waiting in the cave
by the PVC, but nothing yet.
We're coming up
on half a minute.
Come on, Owen. Okay.
This is Gallo. Anything?
Negative. Still no signal.
We're at 40 seconds.
Look at me.
Don't blame yourself.
Agent Gallo. You copy?
What do you got?
Three loud knocks, sir.
Clear as day.
Give me that.
Give me the phone.
Happy.
Now, Owen is doing his best
to survive,
but we still need that jack.
How much longer?
I'm almost done. Then another
15 minutes to get to you.
That's at least 20 minutes.
Not for us. We called LAPD.
Police escort, baby.
Oh, good thinking.
But hurry.
Okay, two minutes,
gold melts, and I mold it
into a thrust bearing,
and we are done.
Happy, what's this?
Don't look through
my things.
You tracked down your father?
In 100 seconds,
the gold's ready.
So, over a minute to talk about
something very important.
It's not a big deal.
I've been wrenching
at his body shop
for the last few weeks,
that's all.
He's a mechanic.
I love genetics.
Good for you.
What was his reaction?
You didn't tell him who you are.
That is what the card is for,
but I can't
seem to give it to him.
Happy, you clearly
want to tell him.
The card was a mistake.
“There are no mistakes.”
Richard Bach.
“Get out of my face.”
Happy Quinn.
I will.
But consider this.
There are two parents
racing like hell right now
to get to a little boy
trapped in a sinkhole.
And all three
want the same thing:
to be with family on Christmas.
You have that shot, and you're
forsaking it over fear.
Gold's done. Get the mold.
Why are you here
instead of with your team?
I'm leaving.
Because you made
some miscalculations?
That child is living
my worst nightmares.
Claustrophobia--
fear of tight spaces.
Aquaphobia--
fear of water.
Achluophobia--
fear of darkness.
Taphophobia--
fear of being buried alive.
When I was on that
beach, I felt like
I was in there with him.
I couldn't concentrate,
I couldn't calculate.
I am useless to Scorpion.
Shut up. You felt like
you were down there?
He is down there.
My God, Sylvester,
how do you live when you're
constantly scared of death?
You want to go?
Go.
But you'll have to live with
what happens to Owen,
knowing you could've helped.
Or you could
stay strong for him.
Stay strong.
I've never been strong.
Well, that's a “you” problem,
so figure it out.
Faster, Grandma!
I'm right on his bumper!
I should have driven.
I have seen you drive.
We can't save Owen
if we're both dead.
Hold on,
what the hell's this?!
Hey, what's going on?
There's a truck accident
up ahead.
I'll see if I can
clear the holdup.
We don't have that kind of time.
Toby, get us out of here.
I'm driving a Monte Carlo--
it's not like I can split lanes.
No. But Santa can.
Hey.
I know this sounds
crazy, but have you seen
the kid in the news,
the one stuck in a hole?
Heard about it.
We're working on the case,
and that boy needs you to
give us your motorcycle.
No time to explain.
Get lost.
When you remember me,
remember me fondly.
Happy!
Oh, my spleen.
Get on!
I'm so sorry.
O2 levels are steady.
He's not panicking;
this kid's amazing.
Do you know what the odds were
of that weak tunnel
collapsing on you?
42%. Which is a 58%
chance of survival.
The odds are on my side.
Do the math
all you want, but there's
a boy breathing underwater,
still alive.
That's a miracle in my book.
Another rock slide!
Get out of here
before it caves in!
Come on!
This part of the ceiling's
about to collapse.
Then the ECMO goes down,
then Owen is dead.
If that rock falls on you,
you're dead!
Move the ECMO!
Took four people
to get it in here!
The slide's calmed down.
Now get out of here
before that rock falls on you!
Not until you move the ECMO!
I'll get help!
I got it.
No, Sylvester.
Sylvester!
I got it.
You sure?
I got it!
All right. Okay.
No, we can't wait
until the others get here.
We got to move now.
We got to move it,
come on.
Come on!
All right,
one, two, three.
I can't hold it much longer!
Sylvester, it's breaking off.
Get out of there.
You okay, pal?
Walter, we got
a problem.
I'm okay.
Oh, God. The rocks
pinched off the tubes.
The tubing's blocked.
He can't get oxygen.
He's dying.
Now get your men to that
cavern and move that rock!
What, get equipment over
those boulders, in the surf,
with tide coming in?
Yes!
It would take an hour.
He's suffocating down there!
With oxygen cut off
to young Owen Cooper, he is just
minutes now from total loss
of brain function.
I'm getting him out.
Son, his leg is trapped.
There's no way.
I can't let him die in there.
Son.
Walter!
Listen. Son!
Get off of me!
Get off me!
He's been underwater
for three minutes!
He's only got
one functioning lung!
I don't have a
motorcycle license.
Great news.
Stop crying.
We're only 300 yards
from the beach.
Whoa.
You got to be kidding.
We're out of gas!
You know what, give
me that knapsack.
I spent my childhood
sprinting from bullies.
It's about to pay off.
I promised him
I'd come back for him.
Walter!
We got it!
Got it!
You're about to risk
your life again,
when the likelihood that
Owen's still alive after
We've seen worse odds.
No, we have not.
It's not possible.
Cabe's right. The water
isn't nearly cold enough
to put that kid in a full
hypothermic state where
he might survive that long.
I know.
And the brain without oxygen
begins to die after five minutes.
I know!
I really don't
want you to do this.
I know.
The last rock slide completely
compromised the tunnel,
which was unstable
to begin with.
Anyone who goes down there
risks being buried alive.
He knows.
Son, why are you doing this?
I made a promise
I'd come back for him.
Are you scared?
Yes.
Good.
That means you'll be careful.
Walter O'Brien, some
type of government contractor,
is underground,
trying to extract Owen Cooper,
who has now been without air
for almost six-and-a-half
minutes.
Okay.
All right.
Hold on!
Collapsing!
Walter!
Cabe!
Grab my hand!
Got him!
Here on the beach,
on Christmas Eve,
strangers are coming together
to save a child.
We got him!
Clear the way!
It's being hailed
a Christmas miracle.
Doctors say a boy survived
after being underwater
without oxygen
for over seven minutes,
and is expected
to make a full recovery.
We're at St. Stephen's Hospital
waiting to hear
from Walter O'Brien,
the head of the team
that saved Owen Cooper.
It is hoped that someone with
a 197 IQ can shed some light
on what exactly happened
in that hole today.
Miracle?
It's more like the ECMO
artificially pumped up
his O2 levels
high enough that
his organs kept going
a few minutes longer than usual.
It's a million-to-one shot,
but not a miracle.
Press is not gonna like it
when I give them that story.
Guys.
Some people really want
to see you.
Hey.
Thank you, Walter.
What for?
For allowing me
to believe again.
If you trust that drug trial,
I do, too.
I'll do it.
I'm gonna keep fighting.
Guys.
The entire drive down,
we prayed.
We prayed for God
to do something,
anything... to save our child.
He answered by sending you.
And your team.
Thank you.
You came back for me.
Oh, I told you,
I only state facts.
We should let these
folks get some rest.
Come on, guys.
I've got an entire press
corp calling for you to explain
how this little boy lived.
Do you want to talk
to them or not?
Ah, they already have
their answer.
It was a miracle.
Hey.
Hey, Happy!
What are you doing here
on Christmas Eve?
I wanted to, um...
You okay?
Yeah.
I just, I wanted to wish you
a happy holiday.
I'll see you later.
You look just like her.
I knew who you were the first
time you walked into my shop.
After your mother died,
I was lost,
and I hit the bottle, hard.
Still do.
You were so special.
Deserved better than me.
I always loved you.
Hey, everyone.
Uh, this is...
my dad, Patrick.
Hello.
Hi.
Welcome, Mr. Quinn.
You got a great girl there.
It's a real pleasure
to meet you.
Oh, yeah!
That's nice.
Who brought me a gift?
Okay. Touchdown.
Oh, you got
your hat back.
I'm back.
Huh?
Look at this.
This is awesome.
That's very nice of you.
It's silly.
You need a little silly
in your life.
Look at that!
Hey, guys, we got
Ralph's present
in the next room.
Okay, so...
we made all this for you, pal.
All right, press the button.
Oh! Do you see that?
It's amazing!
What?
Nothing. Just, um...
merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net